<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 7/01/2018 -->
<GameData>
	<Language_en_US>
		<!-- Andelsbevægelse -->
		<!-- Created by De_Genius, modified and incorporated by adan_eslavo 10/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DENMARK_ANDELSBEVAEGELSE">
			<Text>Andelsbevægelse</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DENMARK_ANDELSBEVAEGELSE_HELP">
			<Text>+10% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production when constructing Buildings in this City. 10% of [ICON_FOOD] Food created by the City counts as [ICON_GOLD] Gold Per Turn. The [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Farming[ENDCOLOR] Process is 15% more effective at converting [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and reducing [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Distress.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_FOOD] Food to Grass and Plains tiles near the City. +2 [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, and [ICON_GOLD] Gold to Nearby Farms and Pastures.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Does not require [ICON_RES_HORSE] Horses.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DENMARK_ANDELSBEVAEGELSE_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Andelsbevægelse is a Danish unique building which can speed up building production. The building's massive bonuses to growth help your empire to multiply, especially when surrounded by plains and pastures.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DENMARK_ANDELSBEVAEGELSE_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The Andelsbevægelse was a Danish Cooperative Movement, corporations where individual members each owned a share in the risks and profits of the collective. Co-ops, as they are commonly referred to, continue to be popular in the farming industry as a way of mitigating bad harvests on the part of a few members.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]After the disastrous Second War of Schleswig where Denmark lost considerable territory, Denmark began to reclaim moors in central and western Jutland for farming. Shortly after, the rapidly industrializing United States began pouring exports of grain into Denmark's biggest customer, Great Britain, tanking the prices for Denmark's produce. With the livelihoods of many Danish farmers at risk, they formed a new strategy to switch from grain products to dairy and meat.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]This shift in Danish agriculture was full of uncertainty, requiring that farmers form the Andelsbevægelse to share in the risks. By the time prices for grain had finally stabilized, Danish agriculture had completely changed. Dairies and slaughterhouses dotted the landscape; now they were IMPORTING grain from Russia to feed their livestock! 
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Agora -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 3/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_GREECE_PROXENOS">
			<Text>Proxenos</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_GREECE_PROXENOS_HELP">
			<Text>+5 [ICON_INFLUENCE] Influence and +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold in Capital on completion of [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Diplomatic Mission in City-State's territotry[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GREECE_AGORA">
			<Text>Agora</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GREECE_AGORA_HELP">
			<Text>+25% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production towards Diplomatic Units in this City. Diplomatic Units trained in this City receive the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Proxenos[ENDCOLOR] Promotion.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][ICON_INTERNATIONAL_TRADE] Trade Routes other Players make to this City will generate +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold for both the City Owner and the Trade Route Owner.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_SPICES] Cinnamon: +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food and +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_SUGAR] Sugar: +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food and +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GREECE_AGORA_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique Market replacement for the Greeks. In addition to the normal bonuses of a Market, the Agora boosts the production Diplomatic Units. Diplomatic units trained in a city with an Agora gain the Proxenos promotion, which increases influence and gold income from Diplomatic Missions. Use your quick production of diplomatic units to secure a steady stream of gold for your empire.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GREECE_AGORA_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The Agora was the marketplace and beating heart of the ancient Greek city-states. Originally used as meeting places for announcements and a muster point for soldiers, Agoras gradually became centers of commerce and trade. Artisans and merchants could sell their wares either in the open, or along the covered walkways which surrounded the field, known as the stoa.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Often the site of intense philosophical and political discussion, the Agoras have been immortalized as the proving ground of renowned philosophers, writers, storytellers, and orators. Disciplines such as Sophism, Skepticism, Cynicism and Stoicism can trace their roots back to the politicking and squabbles of the Grecian Agora.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Alti Cur -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HUNS_ALTI_CUR">
			<Text>Six-Horns Council</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HUNS_ALTI_CUR_HELP">
			<Text>
				Gain +25 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science as an instant boost whenever a Building is constructed in City, scaling with Era. Provides 2 [ICON_RES_IRON] Iron.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]All Stables gain +2 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production. Receive +6 [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness for 20 turns and +100 [ICON_GOLD] Gold as an intant boost whenever you successfully demand Tribute from a City-State, scaling with Era. Bonus resets on each new Tribute.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Does not require any prerequisite building. The [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production Cost and [ICON_CITIZEN] Population Requirements increase based on the number of Cities you own.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HUNS_ALTI_CUR_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Six-Horns Council is the Hunnic Unique Wonder, replacing the Ironworks. In addition to the normal bonuses of the Ironworks, the Six Horns council increases Science and Culture, and boosts Culture and Production from all Stables on empire. The wonder provides additional Gold and Happiness from demanding tribute from minor City-States.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HUNS_ALTI_CUR_TEXT">
			<Text>The Huns' origins remain shrouded in mystery, but one clue to their Xiongnu heritage is their rule by an Alti Cur, or "Six-Horns Council". The Alti Cur was a small council of nobles, the most powerful men within the Hunnic Empire besides the emperor himself. Each was seated according to their standing with the emperor, with the emperor's favorite seated to his immediate right.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
			An emperor's legitimacy depended heavily on the tributes he could extract from the surrounding kingdoms and distribute to his nobles. It is surmised that insufficient tributes from the Chinese and other client tribes triggered the decline and disappearance of the Xiongnu in East Asia, only for them reappear as the Huns of Eastern Europe.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_ALERT_ALTI_CUR_MINOR_TRIBUTE">
			<Text>
				Demanding tribute from the city-state has earned you {1_Num} [ICON_GOLD] Gold and +6 [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness for 20 turns!
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAYER_EVENT_CHOICE_ALTI_CUR_HAPPINESS">
			<Text>Alti Cur tribute bonus</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAYER_EVENT_CHOICE_ALTI_CUR_HAPPINESS_HELP">
			<Text>+6 [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness for 20 turns.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Armada -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 8/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SPAIN_SANTA_MARIA">
			<Text>Santa María</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SPAIN_SANTA_MARIA_HELP">
			<Text>Unit gains [ICON_GREAT_ADMIRAL] Great Admiral Points [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Kill[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SPAIN_INVINCIBLE">
			<Text>Invincible</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SPAIN_INVINCIBLE_HELP">
			<Text>+6 [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength if [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]at full Health[ENDCOLOR]. -1 [ICON_ARROW_RIGHT] Moves. Lost after unit upgrade.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SPAIN_ARMADA">
			<Text>Armada</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SPAIN_ARMADA_HELP">
			<Text>A Slow, but incredibly dangerous ship. Only the Spanish may build it.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Available earlier, but more expensive than the Corvette it replaces. Gains additional strength when at full HP. Begins with [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Boarding Party I[ENDCOLOR] and [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Boarding Party II[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SPAIN_ARMADA_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Armada is a powerful ship in its era. You are unlikely to chase down an enemy, but brilliant maneuvering could force an engagement. Much more imposing when at full health, make sure to make contact with the enemy before they can get a few ranged shots or you will lose a great deal of power in your initial melee combat.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SPAIN_ARMADA_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The "Great and Most Fortunate Navy", the Spanish Armada, was a fleet of 130 ships constructed for the invasion of England and the overthrow the tyrannical Reformist, Elizabeth I. The Armada was one of the largest fleets ever seen in Europe, raised at great expense by Philip II in retribution for England's break from the Catholic Church, their execution of Mary, Queen of Scots, their support for the Dutch revolt against Spain, and the illegitimacy of Elizabeth I.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Spanish ships were outnumbered by England’s navy, but they easily outgunned the smaller English vessels. In the end, however, it was not firepower, but speed which won the day, allowing the small English vessels to harry the lumbering Spanish Juggernaut, sinking 10 ships. When finally forced to retire to Spain, a navigational error blew the Armada off-course and onto the Irish coast, where fierce storms dashed the ships against the rocks. When the Armada at last reached Spain only 67 of the original 130 ships remained, full of sickly, starving, and demoralized sailors.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				The lessons of the Spanish Armada informed naval strategy for the next two centuries. Cannons and ranged action had now overtaken boarding and ramming as the primary methods of attack; sinking, rather than capturing, was now the priority. With this stunning victory, England had wrested naval dominance from Spain, a lead they would maintain until the rise of the United States in WWII.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				"I sent the Armada against men, not God's winds and waves".[NEWLINE]
				-Philip II
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Baan Chang -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 6/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SIAM_BAAN_CHANG">
			<Text>Elephant Camp</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SIAM_BAAN_CHANG_HELP">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production to all Forests worked by this City. +1 [ICON_PEACE] Faith to Camps and +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture to Lumber Mills and Logging Camps near this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for every 10 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens in this City. Internal [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production [ICON_INTERNATIONAL_TRADE] Trade Routes from this City generate +4 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production in City for every 2 Strategic Resources imported from City-State Allies. +10 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and +10 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture whenever a City-State gifts a Unit, scaling with Era.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Allows [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production to be moved from this City along [ICON_INTERNATIONAL_TRADE] Trade Routes inside your Civilization.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SIAM_BAAN_CHANG_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Baan Chang is the Siamese unique replacement for the Workshop. In addition to the normal bonuses of a Workshop, The Baan Chang increases Culture from lumber mills and logging camps, and gives Faith from Camps. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City-State gifts, both Strategic Resources and Units, provide additional benefits in cities with a Baan Chang, so be sure to make strong alliances to get the most from this building.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SIAM_BAAN_CHANG_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Often thought of as ceremonial and military implements first, perhaps the greatest contribution of elephants to human society has been as beasts of burden. Elephants are prized as a labour force even in modern times for their ability to haul the dense teak lumber found only in Burma and Thailand. The strength of a fully grown elephant is matched only by its grace, navigating difficult and uneven terrain while carrying heavy loads. With their delicate command of the forest trails, elephants also reduce the potential damage of logging roads to the surrounding forest.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				The jobs of Southeast Asia's working elephants have come under threat within the past few decades with the mechanization of logging. Elephants and their mahouts have been forced to look for work in tourism and religious festivals, jobs which elephants find terribly stressful.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Bastu -->
		<!-- Created by pineppledan 25/11/2017, modified and incorporated by adan_eslavo 17/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SWEDEN_BASTU">
			<Text>Bastu</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SWEDEN_BASTU_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The Swedish Bad Stuga (bath cabin), or Bastu, is a small cabin designed as a bathing and dry heat spa. A stove or furnace heats the room to 200°F before patrons enter, where they will recline and sweat. Bastus are a social affair, places for discussion and relaxation with family and friends, but were also places for food curing and childbirth in earlier times.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				It is not known where or when Scandinavian sweat baths were first created, but it was well before the Christianization of Scandinavia, as evidenced by their ubiquity throughout medieval Europe. By the time written accounts first described Scandinavian sweat baths, Nordic countries had already created varied and distinct cultures surrounding them.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				The health benefits of heat baths are many and varied. Sessions have been shown to relieve cold symptoms and increase pain thresholds. They also help with rheumatic pain and fatigue, and may even reduce the risk of dementia. Prolonged use of a sauna has been linked to reduced male fertility, however, and heat baths should never be enjoyed while under the effects of alcohol.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SWEDEN_BASTU_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique Swedish replacement for the Baths. In addition to the bonuses of the Baths, the Bastu provides bonuses for lakes and tundra. Science and Culture is generated whenever a citizen is born, and extra Food is generated during Golden Ages. Unlike the Baths, the Bastu does not require a river,</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SWEDEN_BASTU_HELP">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science to Lake Tiles and +1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science for every 2 Tundra Tiles worked. Gain 25% of the [ICON_RESEARCH] Science and 15% of the [ICON_CULTURE] Culture output of the City as an instant boost when a [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen is born in this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture to Temples, Amphitheaters and Gardens in this City. +10% [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and [ICON_FOOD] Food in the City during [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE]Golden Ages.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Does not require a River.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Black Tug -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 29/10/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MONGOLIA_MINGGHAN">
			<Text>Mingghan</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MONGOLIA_MINGGHAN_HELP">
			<Text>+5 XP [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Pillage[ENDCOLOR]. +20% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength if unit is standing [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Pillaged Tile[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MONGOLIA_BLACK_TUG">
			<Text>Black Tug</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MONGOLIA_BLACK_TUG_HELP">
			<Text>Aggressive and menacing Medieval Era Mounted Melee Unit. Only the Mongols may build it. It is stronger against Wounded Units or while standing on Pillaged Tiles. Gains additional XP for pillaging.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MONGOLIA_BLACK_TUG_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Black Tug is a Mongolian unique unit, replacing the Knight. It is stronger and deals more damage to wounded units, and while standing on pillaged tiles. As mounted unit, the Black Tug is vulnerable to Pikemen.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MONGOLIA_BLACK_TUG_TEXT">
			<Text>
				A tug is a pole with circularly arranged horse tail-hairs of varying colors arranged at the top -- a symbol of the importance of horses in Mongol life. A white-haired banner is used as a peacetime symbol, while the black banner was for wartime. The original white banner disappeared early in history, but the black banner survived as the repository of Genghis Khan's soul. The Mongols continued to honor the banner, building a monastery to guard it, but the tug was eventually lost amidst the Stalinist purges of Mongolian nationalists, monks, and intellectuals in 1937.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				The Nine White banners of Mongolia were revived after democracy was adopted in the early 1990s, replacing the previous communist flags. The modern Mongolian nine white banners are kept in the Government Palace in Ulaanbaatar; the modern Mongolian black banners are kept in the Ministry of Defense.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Barbican -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 14/10/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_POLAND_BARBICAN">
			<Text>Embrasure</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_POLAND_BARBICAN_HELP">
			<Text>+33% [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Range Combat Strength [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Garrison in the City[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POLAND_BARBICAN">
			<Text>Barbican</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POLAND_BARBICAN_HELP">
			<Text>Replaces both the Armory and the Castle.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Requires Walls in this City. +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for Quarries worked by this City. Empire [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Needs Modifier is reduced by 5% in this City and -1 [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Unhappiness from [ICON_PRODUCTION] Distress. +25 XP for all new Units trained in this City. +20% [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Ranged Combat Strength for City Bombardment and +33% [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Ranged Combat Strength for Ranged units, and Siege Units garrisoned in this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Contains 1 slot for a [ICON_GREAT_WORK] Great Work of Art.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POLAND_BARBICAN_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique Polish replacement for both the Castle and the Armory, but a bit stronger than both. Must have built Walls in the city. In addition to the city defense and unit training bonuses, the attacks of Ranged and Siege units garrisoned in the city are increased.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POLAND_BARBICAN_TEXT">
			<Text>	
				A Barbican is a fortified outpost or archery tower, forming part of a city’s outer defense. The towers were often situated with a clear line of fire towards the city’s gates, and connected to the city walls via a walled road called the ‘neck’. The most famous barbican was built in Kraków in 1499 during the reign of Jan Olbracht. Its construction took inspiration from two other Barbicans in Torun (1429) and Chelm (1449), and was built in response to the danger posed by encroaching Ottoman and Wallachian forces.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Barbicans became obsolete in the 15th century due to improvements in siege tactics and artillery. The Warsaw barbican, erected in 1540, was an anachronism long before it was completed. The tower was used only once by the Swedish in 1656, while trying to prevent Poland from retaking the city. The Swedish had captured the city without a fight two years prior.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Ballista -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 30/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ROME_LEGATUS_LEGIONIS_ON_BALLISTA">
			<Text>Legatus Legionis</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ROME_LEGATUS_LEGIONIS_ON_BALLISTA_HELP">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_ARROW_RIGHT] Movement [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]if unit [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]starts turn within 2 tiles from Great General[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ROME_LEGATUS_LEGIONIS_EFFECT">
			<Text>Siege Mobility</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ROME_LEGATUS_LEGIONIS_EFFECT_HELP">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_ARROW_RIGHT] Movement.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Cacadores -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PORTUGUESE_CACADORES">
			<Text>Cacador</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PORTUGUESE_CACADORES_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The Cacadores were the elite light infantry of the Portuguese army in the 18th and 19th centuries. The divisions were famed for their marksmanship and their brown coats, one of the first attempts at military camouflage. After Portugal's sound defeat and occupation by Napoleon, the English intervened on behalf of their ally to rally and reorganize a joint war to retake the country. The British general, William Beresford, formed the Cacadores to fill a skirmishing role analogous to the German jaegers or American ranger divisions. Under this combined military, the Cacadores helped in reclaiming Portuguese independence and distinguished themselves as the "fighting cocks" of the Portuguese army until the units were eventually dissolved in the military reforms of 1911.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PORTUGUESE_CACADORES_STRATEGY">
			<Text>
				The Cacador is the unique Portuguese replacement for the Gatling Gun. It gains recon promotions by leveling up, allowing it to excel in hostile terrain.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PORTUGUESE_CACADORES_HELP">
			<Text>
				Ranged unit of the Industrial era. Only Portugal may build it. Whenever it levels up, it gains a random Promotion from the Trailblazer or Survivalism lines. Starts with [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Covering Fire I[ENDCOLOR].
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_PORTUGAL_CACADOR">
			<Text>Fighting Cock</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_PORTUGAL_CACADOR_HELP">
			<Text>Unit gets a free Trailblazer or Survivalism promotion [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Levelling[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Buffalo Pound -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 4/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SHOSHONE_BUFFALO_POUND">
			<Text>Buffalo Pound</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SHOSHONE_BUFFALO_POUND_HELP">
			<Text>Available at Trapping. Can be built anywhere, including Cities with a Water Mill.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_FOOD] Food for every 5 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens in the City. A [ICON_RES_BISON] Bison Resource appears near the City.
			[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_HORSE] Horses: +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food.
			[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_SHEEP] Sheep: +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food.
			[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_COW] Cattle: +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food.
			[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_BISON] Bison: +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SHOSHONE_BUFFALO_POUND_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Buffalo Pound is the Shoshone unique building, replacing the Well. In addition to the normal bonuses of the Well, the Buffalo Pound provides food from Horses, Cattle, Sheep and Bison.  It can also be constructed in cities with access to fresh water, even if a Water Mill has already been built there.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Buffalo will only spawn on flat plains or grassland tiles, with or without Forest.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SHOSHONE_BUFFALO_POUND_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Buffalo Pounds were large constructions built by many Plains Tribes for the entrapment and killing of Buffalo. Large herds of buffalo were corralled and funneled into the pound, a sturdy circular ring of hides and wood, where tribesmen could throw spears and other missile weapons from the safety of the walls.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Buffalo were a staple food source on the North American Plains, but hunting such large animals was difficult without horses or sturdy weapons. With the arrival of Europeans and the introduction of the horse and musket, Native American tribes could travel great distances and attack bison herds with impunity. The good times would not last, however, as Europeans encroached upon this way of life. Increasingly, the Great Plains were converted into farms and pastures for American homesteaders. The American buffalo was driven to the brink of extinction by a combination of habitat loss, industrial-scale hunting, and culls engineered to starve the indigenous population.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Today, American buffalo have recovered, but their range has been greatly limited to a few national parks. Commercial farming and sport hunting continues, but the buffalo are unlikely to ever return to their historical numbers.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Chaebol -->		
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KOREA_CHAEBOL">
			<Text>Chaebol</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KOREA_CHAEBOL_HELP">
			<Text>City must have a Bank. +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold for every 2 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens in the City and +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold for Towns near the City. Cost of [ICON_GOLD] Gold purchasing in this City reduced by 10%. +3 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for Factories in this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+2% [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Great People Points for every [ICON_INTERNATIONAL_TRADE] International Trade Route controlled by the Empire.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Each Chaebol gains +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold, [ICON_RESEARCH] Science, and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture in the city for every Chaebol on Empire.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KOREA_CHAEBOL_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Chaebol is the unique Stock Exchange replacement for South Korea. In addition to the normal bonuses of a Stock Exchange, the Chaebol boosts the production of Factories in Cities where the Chaebol is built. Chaebols increase the production of Great People for every International Trade Route the Empire controls. In addition, every Chaebol increases the Gold, Culture and Science of every other Chaebol in the empire; the more you build, the more they produce.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KOREA_CHAEBOL_PEDIA">
			<Text>
				Chaebol are powerful multi-national corporations originating in South Korea. Beginning as family businesses, generous government investment allowed the Chaebols to quickly industrialize South Korea's agricultural society, in what was to be called the miracle of the Han River. The Chaebol became central to the South Korean economy and came to represent the invincibility of South Korea’s industrial might until the financial crashes the late 20th century, which saw several important Chaebol declare bankruptcy.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Chaebol continue to dominate the South Korean economy and social fabric, and some like Samsung and Hyundai have become household names worldwide. Today, Chaebol account for over 80% of South Korea's exports, and the largest single Chaebol accounts for 17% of the entire nation's GDP.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Chasqui -->		
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INCA_CHASQUI">
			<Text>Chasqui</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INCA_CHASQUI_HELP">
			<Text>Flexible Scout of the Classical Era. Only the Inca may build it. Heals an additional 10 HP, and gains +1 [ICON_ARROW_RIGHT] Movement in Friendly Territory. Moves at Double Speed in [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Mountains[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INCA_CHASQUI_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Chasqui is the unique Scout replacement for the Inca. This unit moves quickly through Mountains and friendly territory. The Chasqui also heals 10 additional HP whenever it heals, making it recover very quickly when exploring or fighting.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INCA_CHASQUI_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The Chasquis were the messengers of the Inca Empire in charge of carrying messages and gifts up to 240 km per day through a form of on-foot Pony Express. In addition to their physical fitness, Chasquis were well-educated, able to translate the khipus, the Incan knot-based writing system, to each other and higher authorities.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Chasquis were dispatched along thousands of miles of Andean trails, taking advantage of a vast system of roads and rope bridges maintained throughout the mountains of Peru and Ecuador. Tambos, or relay stations, were used for the chasquis to stop at and transfer messages to the next chasqui. Each Chasqui carried a conch trumpet which was blown to signalling to a fresh chasqui that one runner was close so that they could prepare to run.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_INCA_CHASQUIWASI">
			<Text>Chasquiwasi</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_INCA_CHASQUIWASI_HELP">
			<Text>+10 HP [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Heal[ENDCOLOR].[NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_ARROW_RIGHT] Movement Point [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]in Friendly Territory[ENDCOLOR].[NEWLINE]Double Movement in [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Mountains[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Corsair -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MOROCCO_CORSAIR">
			<Text>Corsair</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MOROCCO_CORSAIR_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The Barbary Corsairs were Muslim pirates and privateers operating off the coast of North Africa who became infamous throughout Europe. Ranging throughout the Mediterranean and as far as Iceland, the Corsairs slaughtered livestock and captured Christians for sale in the slave markets of the Islamic world. The frequency and ferocity of these raids, or "Razzia" was such that long stretches of Italian and Spanish coast was abandoned for fear of abduction. It is estimated that some 1.25 million people were enslaved by Barbary corsairs between 1530 and 1780 A.D.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				The scope of Corsair activity began to diminish in the latter part of the 17th century, as the more powerful European navies started to pose a real threat to the Barbary States. However, Christian shipping and coastline continued to suffer until the early 19th century. Following the Napoleonic Wars and the Congress of Vienna in 1814, European powers agreed upon the need to suppress the Barbary corsairs for good. The razzias finally ceased after the Second Barbary War between the Barbary pirates and the United States, the impetus for the creation of the US Navy.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				"It is written in our Koran, that all nations which do not acknowledge the Prophet are sinners, whom it is the right and duty of the faithful to plunder and enslave; and that every mu'min (believer) who is slain in this warfare is sure to go to paradise."[NEWLINE]
				-Sidi Haji Abdrahaman, to Thomas Jefferson in reply to his demand for the protection of American merchant ships
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MOROCCO_CORSAIR_STRATEGY">
			<Text>
				The Corsair is the unique Moroccan replacement for the Corvette. It specializes in raiding and pillaging maritime trade routes, earning Food and Production for each enemy unit killed and trade route plundered. The unit can enter other Civilization's borders, even without an open borders agreement, which can be exploited to disrupt better protected trade routes.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MOROCCO_CORSAIR_HELP">
			<Text>
				Naval Unit specializing in disrupting maritime trade. Only Morocco may build it. Can enter Rival Territory. Gain [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production whenever a Corsair Kills a Units, Pillages a Resource, or Plunders a [ICON_INTERNATIONAL_TRADE] Trade Route.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MOROCCO_RAZZIA">
			<Text>Razzia</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MOROCCO_RAZZIA_HELP">
			<Text>
				Nearest Coastal Friendly City gains [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Kill, Pillage or Trade Route Plunder[ENDCOLOR]. Unit [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]can Enter Enemy Territory[ENDCOLOR] without Open Borders Agreement.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Dhanurgraha -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 4/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_INDIA_EPIC">
			<Text>Epic</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_INDIA_EPIC_HELP">
			<Text>Unit gains [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and additional XP [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Kill[ENDCOLOR]. [ICON_CULTURE] Culture doubled [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Barbarian Kills[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_INDIA_DHANURVIDYA">
			<Text>Dhanurvidya</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_INDIA_DHANURVIDYA_HELP">
			<Text>Unit gains [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and [ICON_PEACE] Faith [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Promotion[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDIA_DHANURAASHI">
			<Text>Dhanurgraha</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDIA_DHANURAASHI_HELP">
			<Text>
				Potent early Archery Unit. Only India may build it. Slightly stronger than Archer which it replaces. Gains [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and bonus XP for every kill, and gains [ICON_PEACE] Faith and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture when levelling up. [ICON_CULTURE] Culture from kills is doubled against Barbarians.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDIA_DHANURAASHI_STRATEGY">
			<Text>
				The Dhanurgraha is a powerful defense against early barbarians which helps India maintain its cultural and religious dominance in the early game. Seek out barbarians to kill for culture and faith, then turn on your neighbours if it suits you.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDIA_DHANURAASHI_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Archery was the most highly revered martial art of ancient India. Many of the culture heroes and gods of the Vedic texts describe archers of unparalleled skill, including Arjuna, Rama, Karna, and even Shiva himself. Traditional Indian bows are described as long, matching the height of their users, but without the tremendous strength of the Welsh longbow.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Dromon -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 30/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BYZANTIUM_GREEK_FIRE_0">
			<Text>Greek Fire</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BYZANTIUM_GREEK_FIRE_0_HELP">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]After Attack[ENDCOLOR] Defending Enemy Unit is marked. [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]At the beginning of its turn[ENDCOLOR] it takes an additional 10 "fire" damage for every mark. Effect can stack up to [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]3[ENDCOLOR] times after battles with 3 different units.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BYZANTIUM_GREEK_FIRE_1">
			<Text>Fire</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BYZANTIUM_GREEK_FIRE_1_HELP">
			<Text>Unit takes an additional 10 "fire" damage [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]at the start of its turn[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BYZANTIUM_GREEK_FIRE_2">
			<Text>Huge Fire</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BYZANTIUM_GREEK_FIRE_2_HELP">
			<Text>Unit takes an additional 20 "fire" damage [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]at the start of its turn[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BYZANTIUM_GREEK_FIRE_3">
			<Text>Raging Fire</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BYZANTIUM_GREEK_FIRE_3_HELP">
			<Text>Unit takes an additional 30 "fire" damage [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]at the start of its turn[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_BYZANTIUM_DROMON">
			<Text>Dromon</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_BYZANTIUM_DROMON_HELP">
			<Text>A powerful early Naval Ranged Unit. Only the Byzantines may build it. Each attack by a Dromon inflicts an additional 10 damage at the beginning of the enemy unit''s turn, up to 3 attacks. Starts with [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Splash Damage I[ENDCOLOR] Promotion.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_BYZANTIUM_DROMON_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Bring flaming death to your enemies. Stronger than the Penteconter it replaces, and deals additional burning damage to both the target unit and any enemies near the Dromon. It cannot end its turn in Deep Ocean tiles outside of the city borders.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_BYZANTIUM_DROMON_TEXT">
			<Text>
				A modified form of the traditional galley, the Dromon was an integral part of the Byzantine navy throughout the empire's reign. Featuring both oar and sail power, the Dromon was highly maneuverable and agile, but also dangerously equipped for battle. Through the use of Greek Fire, a precursor to modern Napalm, the Byzantines used an early form of the flamethrower to strike fear in the hearts of any who opposed them on the sea.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Dummies -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 29/08/2018 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_BARBICAN">
			<Text>DF Barbican</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_OPPIDUM">
			<Text>DF Oppidum</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_PROXENOS">
			<Text>DF Proxenos</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_HUEY">
			<Text>+3 [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_PEACE] Faith and Unit XP</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_GUMEY">
			<Text>DF Gumey</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_BUFFALO">
			<Text>DF Buffalo</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_FLAX">
			<Text>DF Flax</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_GUMEY_LUX">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold for all Nearby Luxuries</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_DRUIDIC">
			<Text>DF Druidic Lore</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_SACHEM_1">
			<Text>DF Sachem 1</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_SACHEM_2">
			<Text>DF Sachem 2</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_SACHEM_3">
			<Text>DF Sachem 3</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_SACHEM_4">
			<Text>DF Sachem 4</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_SACHEM_5">
			<Text>DF Sachem 5</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_SACHEM_6">
			<Text>DF Sachem 6</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_SACHEM_7">
			<Text>DF Sachem 7</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_QILA_1">
			<Text>DF Qila 1</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_QILA_2">
			<Text>DF Qila 2</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_TEUTONIC">
			<Text>DF Teutonic</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_D_FOR_BARBICAN">
			<Text>Fortifications</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_D_FOR_GUMEY">
			<Text>Suguba</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_WAAG">
			<Text>DF Waag</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_RIAD">
			<Text>DF Riad</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_EXAM">
			<Text>DF Exam Hall</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_CHAEBOL">
			<Text>DF Chaebol</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_HIPPODROME">
			<Text>+15% [ICON_GOLD] Gold [ICON_CULTURE] Culture during [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] WLTKD</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_BAAN">
			<Text>DF Baan Chang</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_FEITORIA">
			<Text>DF Feitoria</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_TRADITION">
			<Text>Dummy Tradition Finisher Building</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_LIBERTY">
			<Text>Dummy Liberty Finisher Building</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_HONOR">
			<Text>Dummy Honor Finisher Building</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_PIETY">
			<Text>Dummy Piety Finisher Building</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_PATRONAGE">
			<Text>Dummy Patronage Finisher Building</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_AESTHETICS">
			<Text>Dummy Aesthetics Finisher Building</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_RATIONALISM">
			<Text>Dummy Rationalism Finisher Building</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_EXPLORATION">
			<Text>Dummy Exploration Finisher Building</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_COMMERCE">
			<Text>Dummy Commerce Finisher Building</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_IDEOLOGY">
			<Text>Dummy Ideology Building</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_PANTHEON">
			<Text>Dummy Pantheon Building</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_FOUNDER">
			<Text>Dummy Founder Building</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_ENHANCER">
			<Text>Dummy Enhancer Building</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_REFORMATION">
			<Text>Dummy Reformation Building</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SHOPHET_DUMMY">
			<Text>DF Shofet</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- E-temenanki -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 28/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BABYLON_ETEMENANKI">
			<Text>E-temenanki</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BABYLON_ETEMENANKI_HELP">
			<Text>+25% [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] GPP in the City. +25 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture in the City as an instant boost whenever a [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen is born and +50 [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age Points whenever a Policy is unlocked, scaling with Era. Gain 15% of the City's [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_RESEARCH] Science output whenever you invest in a Building on Empire.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science to all Monuments and +2 [ICON_FOOD] Food to all Shrines.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Requires Monument in City. Can only be built in the [ICON_CAPITAL] Capital. The [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production Cost and [ICON_CITIZEN] Population Requirements increase based on the number of Cities you own.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BABYLON_ETEMENANKI_STRATEGY">
			<Text>E-temenanki is the Babylonian Unique Wonder, replacing the National Monument. In addition to the normal bonuses of a National Monument, E-temenanki awards Food and Science whenever a building is invested on empire, so invest in buildings early and often.  All monuments in empire gain +1 Science and all Shrines gain +2 Food. Available earlier than the National Monument</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BABYLON_ETEMENANKI_TEXT">
			<Text>E-temenanki was the Ziggurat of Marduk, god of storms and head of the Babylonian pantheon. Ziggurats were religious temples erected in Mesopotamian cities as the literal dwelling places of each city's patron god. The Ziggurats were constructed to replicate the high mountains, where it believed the gods originally lived, in order to make the gods feel more at home.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Eagle -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_AZTEC_EAGLE">
			<Text>Eagle</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_AZTEC_EAGLE_TEXT">
			<Text>One of the two elite class of infantry (the other being the Jaguar Warriors) in the Aztec army, the Eagle Warriors were the bravest young men of noble birth and/or those who had taken the most prisoners in battle. Like the Jaguars, the Eagles used the atlatl, bow, spear and macuahuitl (wooden swords set with obsidian shards); unlike the Jaguars, the Eagles decorated their armor with eagle feathers and wore a headdress shaped like the head of an eagle with the beak wide open. Upon taking 20 prisoners – intact enough to serve as human sacrifice – a young warrior was eligible to become an Eagle Warrior, no doubt making his family very proud. Until the Spanish arrived with their cannons, muskets, and horses, the Eagle and Jaguar warriors were the toughest bullies on the Mesoamerican block.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_AZTEC_EAGLE_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Eagle is the unique Aztec replacement for the Swordsman. It does not require Iron to build. It has increased vision, and has a chance of capturing defeated enemy units as Workers.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_AZTEC_EAGLE_HELP">
			<Text>Strong, front-line Unit of the Classical Era. Only the Aztecs may build it. Does not require [ICON_RES_IRON] Iron. 25% chance of converting any unit killed into a [ICON_WORKER] Worker. Starts with the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Sentry[ENDCOLOR] and [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Cover I[ENDCOLOR] Promotions.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_AZTEC_CUAUHOCELOTL_1">
			<Text>Cuauhocelotl</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_AZTEC_CUAUHOCELOTL_2">
			<Text>Cuauhocelotl (1 kill)</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_AZTEC_CUAUHOCELOTL_3">
			<Text>Cuauhocelotl (2 kills)</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_AZTEC_CUAUHOCELOTL_4">
			<Text>Cuauhocelotl (3 kills)</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_AZTEC_CUAUHOCELOTL_5">
			<Text>Cuauhocelotl (4 kills)</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_AZTEC_CUAUHOCELOTL_6">
			<Text>Cuauhocelotl (5 kills)</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_AZTEC_CUAUHOCELOTL_7">
			<Text>Cuauhocelotl (6 kills)</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_AZTEC_CUAUHOCELOTL_8">
			<Text>Cuauhocelotl (7 kills)</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_AZTEC_CUAUHOCELOTL_9">
			<Text>Cuauhocelotl (8 kills)</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_AZTEC_CUAUHOCELOTL_10">
			<Text>Cuauhocelotl (9 kills)</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_AZTEC_CUAUHOCELOTL_1_HELP">
			<Text>Unit will become an [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Eagle[ENDCOLOR] after killing 10 Units.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_AZTEC_CAPTIVES_OF_WAR">
			<Text>Captives of War</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_AZTEC_CAPTIVES_OF_WAR_HELP">
			<Text>Chance to [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]spawn a Worker on Kill[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Examination Hall -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CHINA_EXAMINATION_HALL">
			<Text>Examination Hall</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CHINA_EXAMINATION_HALL_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Perhaps the greatest legacy of Chinese culture is the Imperial Examination system with which the Son of Heaven's empire was staffed with civil servants for over two millennia. The Imperial examinations represented an attempt to create an aristocracy of learning, a remarkable advance over the warrior and hereditary aristocracies that dominated the rest of the world. Amounting to tests of rote memorization, the examinations required direct quotations of Confucian philosophy and ethics from the Five Confucian Classics. A scholar who obtained the highest degree, the jinshi, would have his memory trained to a tremendous degree.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				As Western universities began to move away from their own classical tradition to embrace economics, engineering and natural science, China's scholarly efforts languished in the ancient literary past. Under pressure to modernize, the examinations were abolished in 1890, leaving behind a legacy as the first system of intellectual meritocracy the world had ever seen.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				“We tried an experiment which is unique in the history of the world: We sought to rule this great country not by force, but by wisdom. And for centuries we succeeded.”[NEWLINE]
				-Anonymous Confucian Philosopher; excerpt from "On a Chinese Screen"
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CHINA_EXAMINATION_HALL_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Examination Hall is a Chinese unique building, replacing the Chancery. In addition to the normal bonuses of a Chancery, the Exam Hall boosts Great People generation in the city, adding Great Person Points to whichever great person currently has the most points in the city whenever a citizen is born.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CHINA_EXAMINATION_HALL_HELP">
			<Text>+10% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production of Diplomatic Units. Grants the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Royal Signet[ENDCOLOR] Promotion to all Diplomatic Units built in this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold in City for every City-State Friend, and +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for every Ally.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Whenever a [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen is born, gain +15 [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] points toward [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Great Person with the highest progress, scaling with Era.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold to [ICON_GREAT_WORK] Great Works in this City</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Fale Tel'e -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 5/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POLYNESIA_FALE_TELE">
			<Text>Fale Tele</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POLYNESIA_FALE_TELE_HELP">
			<Text>+5 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science whenever a [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen is born in this City, scaling with Era. +3 [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_GOLD] Gold, and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture whenever a Building is Constructed in this City, scaling with Era.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POLYNESIA_FALE_TELE_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique Council replacement for the Polynesians. In addition to the normal bonuses of a Council, the Fale Tele provides Gold, Food and Culture whenever a building is constructed in the city. Build the Fale tele as a first priority to maximize the bonuses for all later buildings.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POLYNESIA_FALE_TELE_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Literally meaning "Big Building", the Fale Tele is typical of Samoan architecture. By decree of Tagaloa-lagi, the Samoan creator god, all dwellings were to be of circular design, in imitation of the dome of the heavens and the horizon. Fale Tele were the largest of Samoan buildings, designed to act as meeting places for chief councils as well as family gatherings, celebrations and ceremonies. Regular dwellings were constructed behind the Fale Tele, while a carefully maintained lawn spread in front as a larger gathering and social space for all villagers.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Samoan culture’s emphasis on openness is reflected in their architecture, with its circular layouts and no walls. Fales have become emblematic of wider Polynesian architecture, with small fale, or faleo'o, becoming ubiquitous on beaches throughout the Pacific.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Figs -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 25/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_ROME_FIGS">
			<Text>Figs</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_ROME_FIGS_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_ROME_FIGS_TEXT">
			<Text>Native to the Middle East and western Asia, Figs have been cultivated since ancient times, being one of the oldest plants cultivated by humans. Figs were common in Ancient Greece and spread to Rome where they formed a staple fruit for the lower classes. Figs are easy to preserve and are well-suited to forming condiments due to their high sugar content. It is perhaps this very association with the simplicity and poverty of common folk which saw figs fall from fashion in later periods.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Flax -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 7/01/2018 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_EGYPT_FLAX">
			<Text>Flax</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_EGYPT_FLAX_HELP">
			<Text>Can be improved by Plantation. Spawns near a City on the construction of the Egyptian Nilometer</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_EGYPT_FLAX_TEXT">
			<Text>Flax is a food and fiber crop best known for its use in the production of linen. The crop was first domesticated in the Fertile Crescent and was cultivated extensively in Egypt, where the fabric became tightly bound to the local culture. Linen has a smooth texture, high lustre, and is cool to the touch. These characteristics linked it to religious and ceremonial purity within Egyptian rituals. Priests wore linen fabrics exclusively and mummies were wrapped in linen in preparation for the afterlife. Today, more durable textiles like cotton have largely replaced linen as a fabric, but the flax seed is still widely used for food and cooking oil.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Fusta -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_VENICE_FUSTA">
			<Text>Fusta</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_VENICE_FUSTA_HELP">
			<Text>A small and fast compliment to the Great Galleas, rather than a replacement. Weaker, but cheaper, and does not contribute to Unit [ICON_GOLD] Gold Maintenance. May withdraw before melee attacks.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_VENICE_FUSTA_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Fusta are quick, cheap, and do not cost any unit maintenance. Use these ships in combination with the bigger Galleass to monitor and protect your shipping lanes without causing an undue burden on your economy.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_VENICE_FUSTA_TEXT">
			<Text>Fusta, or galliots, were small galleys with no more than 35 sailors. Exceptionally light and fast, the Venetians originally used them to maintain a standing navy against pirates, but the ship quickly became a favorite of the pirates themselves. The shallow draft, maneuverability and speed of the Fusta made them a legend throughout the Mediterranean.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Grande École -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 10/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FRANCE_GRANDE_ECOLE">
			<Text>Grande École</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FRANCE_GRANDE_ECOLE_HELP">
			<Text>Requires University in the City. -1 [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Unhappiness from [ICON_RESEARCH] Illiteracy. +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and +1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science for every 2 [ICON_CITIZEN] Population in this City. +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production to [ICON_GREAT_SCIENTIST] Scientist Specialists and +2 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science to [ICON_GREAT_ENGINEER] Engineer Specialists in this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Allows Archaeologists to be built in this City.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FRANCE_GRANDE_ECOLE_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Grande École is the French unique building, replacing the Public School. In addition to the normal bonuses of a Public School, The Grande École increases production for every citizen in the City, has more Scientist Specialist slots, and helps to generate Great Engineers. In addition, all Scientists generate more Production, and all Engineers generate more Science, making any city with a Grande Ecole a powerhouse of scientific and technical achievement.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FRANCE_GRANDE_ECOLE_TEXT">
			<Text>The French Grande École are institutions of higher learning separate from the more conventional university system. These schools are highly selective, taking only the best and brightest French graduates, and barring entry by foreigners. Once accepted, students studying at a Grande École are considered public servants, paying little to no entrance fees and even receiving a monthly government stipend.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The origins of the Grande Écoles lie in the French Revolution, where several military and technical écoles normale supérieure were established by distinguished French mathematicians and intellectuals. The idea was to open education to individuals based strictly on merit. By the 19th century a number of schools had sprung up for a wide array of disciplines including natural sciences, business and the humanities. The Grande Écoles continue to have a deep impact on French society, with approximately 10% of all Native-born French citizens graduate from these schools, including many of France's most renowned politicians, philosophers, scientists, and executives.</Text>
		</Row>
				
		<!-- Hacienda -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 10/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_SPAIN_HACIENDA">
			<Text>Hacienda</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_SPAIN_HACIENDA_HELP">
			<Text>Available at Civil Service. Cannot be built next to another Hacienda. Provides [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_GOLD] Gold. Grants additional bonuses for every adjacent map component:[NEWLINE]
				+2 [ICON_FOOD] - Bonus Resource,[NEWLINE]
				+2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] - Strategic Resource,[NEWLINE]
				+2 [ICON_GOLD] - Luxury Resource,[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_CULTURE] - City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_PEACE] Faith if City has a Mission.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_SPAIN_HACIENDA_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Haciendas are colonial estates constructed by the Spanish for the administration and extraction of resources from their native subjects. Haciendas were based on grants of property and enterprise, rather than the strict grant of indigenous labor as described by the older Encomienda system. Haciendas were generally large estates, but the nature of the work varied from plantations, to mining, to factories.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				The owner of a Hacienda was called a Hacendado, but the wealthy landowners rarely visited their holdings and preferred to live in nearby cities. Day-to-day operations of a Hacienda were the responsibility of hired managers. Some unusually large and profitable Haciendas were the property of the Roman Catholic Church, exacerbating tension between native laborers and their Christian taskmasters.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				The Hacienda system was abolished in most countries after the dissolution of the Spanish Empire, but with mixed results. Efforts to break apart the large estates into individual holdings for subsistence farmers led to crushing poverty in some South American nations. In contrast, Latin American and Filipino Haciendas were mostly left intact, but without the same legal standing or permissions of their colonial past.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_SPAIN_HACIENDA">
			<Text>Build a [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_SPAIN_HACIENDA]Hacienda[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_SPAIN_HACIENDA_HELP">
			<Text>Constructs a Hacienda, which yields [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_GOLD] Gold and [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production. [NEWLINE]Gains [ICON_FOOD] Food for adjacent Bonus Resource, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for adjacent Strategic Resources, [ICON_GOLD] Gold for adjacent Luxury Resources, and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture from adjacent Cities. +1 [ICON_PEACE] Faith if the nearby City has built a Mission.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_SPAIN_HACIENDA_REC">
			<Text>It will increase [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_GOLD] Gold and [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production. [NEWLINE]Gains [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production from adjacent Cities and [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_GOLD] Gold and [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production from adjacent resources. +1 [ICON_PEACE] Faith if the nearby City has built a Mission.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Holkan -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 16/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MAYA_SCOUT_GOODY_BONUS_2">
			<Text>Lost Codices</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MAYA_SCOUT_GOODY_BONUS_2_HELP">
			<Text>Unit gains [ICON_RESEARCH] Science and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]from Ancient Ruins[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MAYA_HOLKAN">
			<Text>Holkan</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MAYA_HOLKAN_HELP">
			<Text>A dangerous scout with no penalty against Barbarians. Only the Maya may build it. Gains [ICON_RESEARCH] Science and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture with every Ancient Ruin explored. Starts with the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Trailblazer I[ENDCOLOR] Promotion.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MAYA_HOLKAN_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Holkan is a quick and independent scout for the Maya. Because of their free Trailblazer I promotion, the Holkan explores more quickly, and gains experience more easily than the Pathfinders. Their increased power against barbarians makes Holkans capable of ranging farther and taking more risks than a normal scout. Use these units to grab ruins quickly, and gain an early scientific edge and cultural edge.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MAYA_HOLKAN_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The Maya are often idealized as a peaceful civilization by western Mayanists, but the Maya were no strangers to war. Unlike the wars of Europe and Asia, however, the Maya engaged in a highly ritualized form of combat based on astrological and religious concerns as much as political ones. Squabbles over land, influence and resources were common, but the capture of human sacrifices was another factor leading to war.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The nobility and priesthood of Mayan cities kept a monopoly on violence, making all but the most desperate of wars strictly within the affairs of the upper class. Weapons made of obsidian and chert were stockpiled within the palaces of lords and kings, who would call upon their family to lead raids. The leaders of such expeditions were known as ‘Holkan’.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Great Turkish Bombard -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 1/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_OTTOMANS_SIEGE_INACCURACY_2">
			<Text>Siege Inaccuracy II</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_OTTOMANS_SIEGE_INACCURACY_2_HELP">
			<Text>-50% [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Ranged Combat Strength vs [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Land Units[ENDCOLOR]. Lost after unit upgrade.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_OTTOMANS_SAHI_TOPU">
			<Text>Sahi Topu</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_OTTOMANS_SAHI_TOPU_HELP">
			<Text>Unit deals 20 damage to itself [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Attack[ENDCOLOR]. +10 HP [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Heal inside Friendly Territory[ENDCOLOR]. Lost after unit upgrade.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_OTTOMANS_GREAT_TURKISH_BOMBARD_1">
			<Text>Basilica</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_OTTOMANS_GREAT_TURKISH_BOMBARD_2">
			<Text>Dardanelles Gun</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_OTTOMANS_GREAT_TURKISH_BOMBARD_3">
			<Text>Mohammed's Great Gun</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_OTTOMANS_GREAT_TURKISH_BOMBARD_4">
			<Text>Orban's Cannon</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_OTTOMANS_GREAT_TURKISH_BOMBARD">
			<Text>Great Bombard</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_OTTOMANS_GREAT_TURKISH_BOMBARD_HELP">
			<Text>An Incredibly powerful Unit capable of smashing Cities to pieces. Only the Ottomans may build it. Does very high damage to Cities and Naval Units, but is less useful against Land Units compared to other Siege Weapons.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Deals 20 damage to itself on attack, but heals an additional 10 HP when in Friendly Territory.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Player may have only [COLOR_GREEN]2[ENDCOLOR] Great Bombards at one time.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_OTTOMANS_GREAT_TURKISH_BOMBARD_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Great Bombard is a powerful Siege Weapon well after it is researched. It is the most powerful seige unit in its era; so dangerous it even hurts itself! Devastating against cities and naval units.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_OTTOMANS_GREAT_TURKISH_BOMBARD_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Bigger is better, and biggest is best. The super-sized bombards of the late medieval were first used in Western European warfare at the beginning of the 15th century, but it was the Ottomans that would realize the bombard's full potential at the Siege of Constantinople in 1453. Unable to find patronage with the Byzantine emperor, a Hungarian gunfounder named Orban sold his services to Mehmed II of the Ottoman Empire, and began crafting bronze cannons capable of lobbing 1.6 tons of shaped stone more than a mile.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Transporting such massive weapons took as many as 60 oxen, and required construction of entire road networks before the cannons could be brought to bear against the impregnable Theodosian Walls. Within a day of the opening bombardment, massive stones smashed the outer defenses to rubble and the city which had stood as a fortress of Christendom for a millennium fell. The sack of Constantinople raged for three days following, and triggered a mass exodus of Greeks into Europe proper. The influx of Byzantine refugees brought a rediscovery of the philosophical and intellectual achievements of Greek culture into Western Europe, planting the seeds of the Renaissance.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Stone bombards were supplanted by iron-ball cannons by the end of the 16th century, and few bombards are left intact. None of the bombard’s descendants, however, can claim to have single-handedly ended an era.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Goedendag -->
		<!-- Created by De_Genius on 28/10/2017, modified and incorporated by adan_eslavo on 12/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_NETHERLANDS_GOEDENDAG">
			<Text>Goedendag</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_NETHERLANDS_GOEDENDAG_HELP">
			<Text>A cheap, versatile Defensive unit with supporting abilities. Only the Dutch may build it. Provides a combat boost to all Units adjacent to it and has increased [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength if Garrisoned in a City.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_NETHERLANDS_GOEDENDAG_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Goedendag is an odd unit, but effective in groups. While effective on their own against cavalry, the Goedendag provides increased attack against all units adjacent to it, and has additional combat strength if Garrisoned in a City at the beginning of your turn. Goedendag's do not boost their own combat strength, so Goedendags must be adjacent to each other to receive the benefit of their own promotion. These units can be built very quickly, so an army can be raised in the event of a surprise war.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_NETHERLANDS_GOEDENDAG_TEXT">
			<Text>
				A Goedendag is a four-foot long club with a spearhead at its tip that was used by the militias of Medieval Flanders during the Franco-Flemish War. The weapon was christened "goedendag" by the French, a cognate with the Dutch greeting "good day". This name may be a reference to the Bruges Matins massacre of 1302, in which the guildsmen of Bruges took over the city by greeting people in the streets and murdering anyone who answered with a French accent.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Goedendags were used to great effect by the guildsmen of Flanders against the French knights, but exactly how the weapon was used is a source of debate. Contemporary illustrations show it being used as a club, written accounts describe its first use as a spear to meet a charge, then a club as the enemy was halted. However they worked, men armed with Goedendags marked the beginning of the end for heavy cavalry in Western Europe, and the dawn of an "Infantry Revolution" where peasant militia were now a credible threat to professional soldiers. The stunning victory of common men over foreign tyrants became a wellspring of romantic nationalism for the Low Countries.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				"each held his godendart (sic) raised against the French, the iron as one meets a wild boar"[NEWLINE]- Guillaume Guiart, a contemporary account describing the battle of Courtrai, 1302 A.D.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_NETHERLANDS_GOEDENDAG">
			<Text>Goedendag!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_NETHERLANDS_GOEDENDAG_HELP">
			<Text>+10% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]to adjacent Friendly Land Units[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_NETHERLANDS_BURGEMEESTE">
			<Text>Burgemeeste</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_NETHERLANDS_BURGEMEESTE_HELP">
			<Text>+33% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength if [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]within 2 tiles of a Friendly City[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Hashemite Raider -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ARABIA_HASHEMITE_RAIDER">
			<Text>Hashemite Raider</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ARABIA_HASHEMITE_RAIDER_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Long considered the "Sick Man of Europe", Ottoman power was in decline well before nationalist sentiment took root in the Arab population. When WWI broke out among the European powers the Ottomans set about crushing Arab dissent. Arab citizens responded in a popular revolt, declaring a new Islamic empire.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Hussein bin Ali, Sharif of Mecca, began the rebellion in hopes of re-establishing a Hashemite dynasty in Arabia, and led his fellow Arabs in armed rebellion against their Turkish masters in Hejaz. Seeing an opportunity to tie down Ottoman forces in a new front, the British promised to recognize Arab hegemony and heavily subsidize the revolt, sending the now famous T.E. Lawrence as a liaison. With this new infusion of funds and equipment, the Arabs waged a guerilla war through the desert, crippling Ottoman supply lines. With the help of French and English navy, they were able to take several ports along the Mediterranean coast, emboldening even more to join their cause.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				With the end of WWI in 1918 and the Ottomans’ defeat, the Arabs expected the full cooperation of their European allies as they established their new kingdom. However, the English and French had other plans. Behind closed doors, the French and English secretly formed the Sykes-Picot Agreement which divided the Middle-East amongst their own respective spheres of influence. This gross betrayal of a trusted ally has soured relations between the Arab states and the West ever since.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ARABIA_HASHEMITE_RAIDER_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Hashemite Raider the Arab replacement for the Light Tank. It is adept at hit-and-run tactics and disrupting enemy supply lines. Whenever it pillages an improvement, adjacent enemy units take 10 damage. Moves quickly through desert.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ARABIA_HASHEMITE_RAIDER_HELP">
			<Text>Fast and dangerous Modern Era Cavalry Unit. Only Arabia may build it. Available earlier, and does not require [ICON_RES_ALUMINUM] Aluminum. Moves faster and is stronger in Desert. Does not require [ICON_MOVES] Movement to pillage Tile Improvements, and deals damage to adjacent Enemy Units whenever it Pillages a tile.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ARABIA_GARLAND_MINE">
			<Text>Garland Mine</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ARABIA_GARLAND_MINE_HELP">
			<Text>Unit uses [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]no[ENDCOLOR] [ICON_ARROW_RIGHT] Movement Points [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Pillage[ENDCOLOR]. All [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]adjacent Enemy Units[ENDCOLOR] take 10 damage [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Pillage[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ARABIA_DESERT_RAIDER">
			<Text>Desert Raider</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ARABIA_DESERT_RAIDER_HELP">
			<Text>Double [ICON_ARROW_RIGHT] Movement and +25% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Desert[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Hippodrome -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 2/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BYZANTIUM_HIPPODROME">
			<Text>Hippodrome</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BYZANTIUM_HIPPODROME_HELP">
			<Text>Does not require an Arena in the City. [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Free[ENDCOLOR] Arena in the City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]-1 [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Unhappiness from [ICON_CULTURE] Boredom. +15% [ICON_GOLD] Gold and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture on Empire during [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] 'We Love the King' Day and a [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] 'We Love the King' Day begins immediately on Completion.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]At the beginning of every new Era, 1 turn of [ICON_RESISTANCE] Resistance occurs in this City, after which a [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] 'We Love the King' Day is triggered across the Empire.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]All Arenas gain +3 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and all Circuses gain +3 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture. +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture on all sources of [ICON_RES_HORSE] Horses on Empire.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production Cost and [ICON_CITIZEN] Population Requirements increase based on the number of Cities you own.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BYZANTIUM_HIPPODROME_STRATEGY">
			<Text>
				The Hippodrome is the Byzantine Unique Wonder, replacing the Circus Maximus. In comparison to the Circus Maximus, The Hippodrome greatly increases Gold and Culture yields during "We Love the King Days" and begins a "We Love the King Day" on completion. All Arenas in the empire receive gold, while circuses receive Culture, and Horses get both.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Be careful to time when your transition into a new era comes. A turn of resistance could is a small price to pay for a free "We Love the King Day", but it could slow down a crucial wonder or come during a war.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BYZANTIUM_HIPPODROME_TEXT">
			<Text>Hippodromes were a chariot racing tracks and the beating heart of Byzantine social and political life. Though slightly smaller in footprint than the Circus Maximus in Rome, there was no equal to the Hippodrome of Constantinople's grandeur, adorned with art and treasures from all corners of the empire. The Constantinople Hippodrome was built by Constantine himself shortly after he moved his capital to the city. The track was placed adjacent to the palace, taking the shape of a massive 'U', with ten monuments lining its center.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
			Not just a pastime of the rich, the chariot races became the one place where the common people could see and interact with the emperor in a single venue. Commoners took the opportunity to begin chants for political or religious reforms during sporting events. Four political parties, or demes, existed within Constantinople which each sponsored a different racing team: The Blues, the Whites, the Greens and the Reds. Enormous sums of money were wagered on the outcomes of these races, which became further heated by the religious, societal, and political leanings which each team came to represent. One such feud in particular would come to overshadow them all: the Nika riots.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] 
			During the reign of Justinian I (an ardent supporter of the Blues), a dispute arose concerning the conviction of two hooligans, arrested for murder from a prior riot. The sentencing of these men unified the Blues and the Greens against Justinian in a terrible mob, and disgruntled nobles seized the opportunity to try to depose him as revenge for Justinian’s new taxes. Though at first he considered fleeing, Justinian rallied his loyal generals to corral the rioters into the Hippodrome, where they were butchered by royal guardsmen and Gothic mercenaries. By the time the Nika riots had ended, half of Constantinople had been burned down and 30,000 people were killed -- the deadliest riot in world history.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Huey Teocalli -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AZTEC_HUEY_TEOCALLI">
			<Text>Huey Teocalli</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AZTEC_HUEY_TEOCALLI_TEXT">
			<Text>In the Aztec Empire, a teocalli was a terraced pyramid surmounted by a roofed temple, and acted as the site of all the important religious rituals in the town. The greatest of these teocalli was located in the heart of Tenochtitlan, the Huey Teocalli (or, according to the Spanish, the Templo Mayor) dedicated to a pair of gods: Huitzilopochtli, the god of war, and Tlaloc, the god of agriculture (an indication of what was important in Aztec culture). Each god had a separate temple, reached by separate staircases.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AZTEC_HUEY_TEOCALLI_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Huey Teocalli is the unique Aztec replacement for the Grand Temple. It does not require a Temple, and immediately triggers a Golden Age on completion. Every time you enter a Golden Age the Huey Teocalli permanently gains Food, Faith, and additional XP to units built in the city.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AZTEC_HUEY_TEOCALLI_HELP">
			<Text>Does not require a Temple. Triggers a [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age on Completion.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+2 [ICON_PEACE] Faith and +2 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture to all Temples, and +2 [ICON_FOOD] Food to all Barracks on Empire. Contains 1 slot for [ICON_GREAT_WORK] Great Work of Music. -1 [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Unhappiness from [ICON_PEACE] Religious Unrest. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Whenever you enter a [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age, permanently gain +3 [ICON_FOOD] Food, +3 [ICON_PEACE] Faith and +3 XP for Units trained in the City (max +30).[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production Cost and [ICON_CITIZEN] Population Requirements increase based on the number of Cities you own.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Iron Chariot -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ASSYRIA_IRON_CHARIOT">
			<Text>Iron Chariot</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ASSYRIA_IRON_CHARIOT_TEXT">
			<Text>Before horses were bred to be big enough to carry men on their backs, Assyrian chariots were used to smash into and disperse enemy formations. These sturdy chariots were both a platform for archers and javelins throwers and weapons themselves, forming the first shock tactics of history. Recognizing the great value of horses as weapons of war, Assyria was known for choosing lands to conquer specifically for their esteemed horse lineages.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ASSYRIA_IRON_CHARIOT_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Assyria's Iron Chariots act as shock troops to control the battlefield. They excel at breaking enemy ranks. The Iron Chariot gains a combat bonus for every adjacent enemy unit, neutralizing the enemy's flanking bonuses and allowing your chariots to take greater risks on the battlefield. Iron and Horse resources in excess of the number of Iron Chariots you own increase the combat effectivness of your chariots.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ASSYRIA_IRON_CHARIOT_HELP">
			<Text>Durable shock cavalry of the Ancient Era. Only Assyria may build it. Gains [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength for each adjacent Enemy Unit.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Does not require [ICON_RES_HORSE] Horses, but gains +2 [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength if Player has sufficient [ICON_RES_HORSE] Horses for all Iron Chariots, and again for [ICON_RES_IRON] Iron. Ends turn if entering Rough Terrain.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ASSYRIA_FURY_OF_NERGAL">
			<Text>Fury of Nergal</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ASSYRIA_FURY_OF_NERGAL_HELP">
			<Text>+10% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]for each adjacent Enemy Land Unit[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ASSYRIA_IRON_AND_HORSE">
			<Text>Hard and Fast</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ASSYRIA_IRON_AND_HORSE_HELP">
			<Text>+2 [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Power if [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Player has more Horses or Iron than Iron Chariot Units[ENDCOLOR]. Bonuses can stack. Lost after unit upgrade.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- InDuna -->	
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ZULU_IBUTHO">
			<Text>Ibutho</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ZULU_IBUTHO_HELP">
			<Text>Friendly Units stacked with this unit gain +50% Experience.</Text>
		</Row>	
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ZULU_IQAWE">
			<Text>Iqawe</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ZULU_IQAWE_HELP">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]On Expending[ENDCOLOR], [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]grants XP[ENDCOLOR] to a stacked Friendly Unit and [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]inflicts flat damage to every adjacent Enemy Unit[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>		
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA">
			<Text>InDuna</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The InDuna is a Zulu unique unit. May construct a Citadel. +15% Combat bonus to all Land units within 2 tiles.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]A unit stacked with an InDuna receives +50% Experience.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Expending an InDuna gives 30XP to the unit that was stacked with it, and deals 30 damage adjacent enemy units.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA_HELP">
			<Text>This Zulu Unique Great Person replaces the Great General. Aside from the ability to boost nearby troops and construct Citadels, Units stacked with an InDuna gain bonus Experience more quickly. Expending an InDuna gives bonus XP to a Stacked Unit, and immediately deals 30 damage to adjacent Enemy Units.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA_TEXT">
			<Text>Leadership was not a complicated affair for the Zulu military. An inDuna guided each regiment, or 'ibutho', and he in turn answered to senior izinDuna who controlled the corps. One or more of these elder chiefs might accompany a big force on an important mission, but there was no single "field marshal" in command of all Zulu forces. Regimental izinDuna, like the non-commissioned officers of today's army, were important for morale and discipline. This was demonstrated during the battle of Isandlwana, where the army led by Ntshingwayo kaMahole outmaneuvered and destroyed a British column. Ntshingwayo kaMahole and his fellow izinDuna snuck a Zulu force of 20 000 men behind the British, hiding them in a valley only 7 miles from the British camp. When discovered sitting in complete silence by scouts, the izinDuna spurred their men into action and closed the remaining distance with lightning speed.</Text>
		</Row>		
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA_1">
			<Text>Mzilikazi</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA_2">
			<Text>Mbopa</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA_3">
			<Text>Ntshingwayo kaMahole</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA_4">
			<Text>Nathaniel Isaacs</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA_5">
			<Text>Ndlela kaSompisi</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA_6">
			<Text>Umgobhozi Ovela Entabeni</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA_7">
			<Text>Nongalaza KaNondela</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA_8">
			<Text>Dabulamanzi kaMpande</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA_9">
			<Text>Dambuza Nzobo</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA_10">
			<Text>Nqoboka Mthiyane</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA_11">
			<Text>Mabhodla Mbuyazi</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA_12">
			<Text>Menziwa Biyela</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA_13">
			<Text>Gala ka Nodade</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA_14">
			<Text>Vumindaba kaNthati</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA_15">
			<Text>Mavumengwana kaNdlela</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA_16">
			<Text>Zibhebhu kaMaphitha</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA_17">
			<Text>Manyosi</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Iziko -->		
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ZULU_IZIKO">
			<Text>Iziko</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ZULU_IZIKO_TEXT">
			<Text>
				An Iziko is a simple hearth used as a gathering place for Zulu communities. The fireplace was revered as a source for food, warmth, dreams, and ancestral ties. It is from these gatherings that a sense of community and identity was formed, and young Zulus could perform and bond.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				The fireplace is used metaphorically for the "cooking of songs" in isicathamiya stage performances, a modern offshoot of traditional Zulu music. Dreams were an essential part of communicating with ancestors and formed part of a deeply rooted Zulu religion. Some isicathamiya musicians claim some of their songs were created in the spiritual realm or given to them by their ancestors.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				"A person is a person because of other people"[NEWLINE]-Zulu proverb
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ZULU_IZIKO_HELP">
			<Text>+33% [ICON_GREAT_WRITER] Great Writer Rate in the City, and all Writers' Guilds produce +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Whenever a unit gains a level, receive [ICON_CULTURE] Culture in the City, scaling with Unit level.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_DYE] Dye: +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_SILK] Silk: +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Contains 2 slots for Great Works of Writing[NEWLINE]+2 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture when Themed</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ZULU_IZIKO_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Iziko is the unique Zulu replacement for the Amphitheater. In addition to the bonuses of an Amphitheater, the Iziko provides Culture in the City whenever a military unit gains a level, with higher levels granting more culture. Make war an essential part of your empire's cultural development.</Text>
		</Row>	
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_THEMING_BONUS_ZULU_IZIKO">
			<Text>Collection of {2_CivAdjective} Folktales</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ZULU_IZIKO_THEMING_BONUS_HELP">
			<Text>To maximize your bonus, make sure the Great Work Slots are all filled with Writings either from your own Civilization, or from Civilizations other than your own.</Text>
		</Row>	
		<!-- Kabuki & the Japanese Guilds-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JAPAN_KABUKI">
			<Text>Kabuki Theater</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JAPAN_KABUKI_TEXT">
			<Text>Kabuki is a classical Japanese dance-drama known for the stylization of its drama and for the elaborate make-up worn by some of its performers. The art form was created in 1603 when Izumo no Okuni, a miko of Izumo-taisha, began performing a new style of dance drama in the dry riverbeds of Kyoto. Despite many the upheaval of Japans modernization, Kabuki remains the most popular of the traditional styles of Japanese drama, and has helped renew interest in other forms of traditional Japanese art.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JAPAN_KABUKI_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Kabuki is the unique Japanese replacement for the Opera House. On construction, Any guilds in the city are replaced with unique Japanese guilds.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JAPAN_KABUKI_HELP">
			<Text>Does not require an Amphitheater in the City. +33% [ICON_GREAT_MUSICIAN] Great Musician Rate. All Musicians' Guilds produce +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold. Internal [ICON_INTERNATIONAL_TRADE] Trade Routes to or from this City generate 50 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture when completed, scaling with Era.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Writers', Artists' and Musicians' Guilds in this City are replaced with unique Guilds of the same type.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JAPAN_MONOGATARI">
			<Text>Monogatari Guild</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JAPAN_MONOGATARI_TEXT">
			<Text>Monogatari are a classical form of Japanses literature which gained popularity during the 10th century Heian period. Monogatari were traditionally epics and semi-religious tales, but later works included secular stories of courtly life, including Genji Monogatari, widely regarded as the first novel. Many of the most prolific and successful writers of Monogatari were noble women.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JAPAN_MONOGATARI_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Monogatari Guild is the unique Japanese replacement for the Writers' Guild. It generates Great Writers more quickly than the Writers' Guild, gives Gold for Writer specialists in the City, and provides Culture and Gold whenever a Great Artist is born on Empire.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JAPAN_MONOGATARI_HELP">
			<Text>Generates [ICON_GREAT_WRITER] Great Writers, and contains slots for Writer Specialists. 1 Specialist in this City no longer produces [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Unhappiness from Urbanization.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold to Writer specialists in this city. When a [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Great Musician[ENDCOLOR] is born, Gain [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and [ICON_GOLD] Gold equal to 3% of the writer's potential [ICON_CULTURE] Culture from a [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Political Treatise[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JAPAN_UKIYOE">
			<Text>Ukiyo-e Guild</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JAPAN_UKIYOE_TEXT">
			<Text>Ukiyo-e is a style of Japanese painting on woodblocks which flourished in the 17th century. The production of ukiyo-e was a collaborative affair, often with a separate painter who crafted the designs, a woodcarver who crafted the woodblock, and a printer who inked and reproduced the artwork. The striking angles, shapes and colours of Ukiyo-e would leave a lasting impression on Western art, informing the impressionist and modernist movements.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JAPAN_UKIYOE_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Ukiyo-e Guild is the unique Japanese replacement for the Artists' Guild. It generates Great Artists more quickly than the Artists' Guild, gives Science for Artist specialists in the City, and provides Science and Golden Age Points whenever a Great Artist is born on Empire.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JAPAN_UKIYOE_HELP">
			<Text>Generates [ICON_GREAT_ARTIST] Great Artists, and contains slots for Artist Specialists. 1 Specialist in this City no longer produces [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Unhappiness from Urbanization.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+2 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science to Artist specialists in this city. When a [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Great Artist[ENDCOLOR] is born, gain [ICON_RESEARCH] Science and [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age Points equal to 3% of the artist's potential [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age Points from [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Starting a Golden Age[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JAPAN_GAGAKU">
			<Text>Gagaku Guild</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JAPAN_GAGAKU_TEXT">
			<Text>Gagaku is the oldest existing form of orchestral music in the world. The style was brought in from mainland China in the 6th century, and reached its peak in the 10th century's imperial court. Modern ensembles consist of three wind instruments, three percussion instruments, and a supporting string instrument.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JAPAN_GAGAKU_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Gagaku Guild is the unique Japanese replacement for the Musicians' Guild. It generates Great Musicians more quickly than the Musicians' Guild, gives Faith for Musician and Civil Servant specialists in the City, and provides Tourism and Faith whenever a Great Artist is born on Empire.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JAPAN_GAGAKU_HELP">
			<Text>Generates [ICON_GREAT_MUSICIAN] Great Musicians, and contains slots for Musician Specialists. 1 Specialist in this City no longer produces [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Unhappiness from Urbanization.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+2 [ICON_PEACE] Faith to Musician specialists in this city. When a [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Great Musician[ENDCOLOR] is born, Gain 200 [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism and [ICON_PEACE] Faith equal to 3% of the musician's potential [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism from a [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Concert Tour[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Kampong -->
		<!-- Created by pineappledan; incorporated by adan_eslavo on 24/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_INDONESIA_KAMPONG">
			<Text>Kampong</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_INDONESIA_KAMPONG_TEXT">
			<Text>The term ‘Sama-Bajau’ refers to a single ethnic group scattered between the modern day Philippines, Indonesia, and Malaysia. The Sama people live a semi-sedentary life in stilt villages or “kampongs” in coastal shallows, while Bajau refers to nomadic groups living in house boats. The Sama-Bajau defy national and ethnic borders, travelling and fishing between islands on the open ocean. In addition to their cultural and ethnic distinctiveness, the Bajau-Laut boast physical adaptations to their semi-aquatic way of life. Bajau-Laut possess unique abilities which allow them to see better underwater, and dive longer and deeper than any other group of humans.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]In recent years, the Bajau-Laut have been forced into sedentary lifestyles by various governments, and face discrimination as pagans, outsiders and squatters. A combination of overfishing and modernization threatens the Bajau’s nomadic traditions, as they have been forcibly resettled on land. Still, a few communities of Bajau-Laut ride their lepa lepa across the blue water of Southeast Asia, only traveling to shore a few times each year.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_INDONESIA_KAMPONG_HELP">
			<Text>The Kampong can be built by [ICON_WORKER] Embarked Workers on Coastal and Lake Tiles, and not next to another Kampong.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Each Kampong yields [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, and adjacent Fishing Boats receive +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_INDONESIA_KAMPONG">
			<Text>Build a [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_INDONESIA_KAMPONG]Kampong[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_INDONESIA_KAMPONG_HELP">
			<Text>Constructs a Kampong, which increases [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and adjacent Sea Resources receive +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_INDONESIA_KAMPONG_REC">
			<Text>It will increase [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and adjacent Sea Resources receive +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Khopesh -->
		<!-- Created by BlueGhost, incorporated and modified by adan_eslavo on 7/01/2018 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_EGYPT_KHOPESH">
			<Text>Khopesh</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_EGYPT_KHOPESH_TEXT">
			<Text>Khopesh is the Egyptian name of the Canaanite "sickle-sword", designed for hooking an opponent's shield or disarming them. The weapon evolved from the epsilon axes that were common in warfare at the time. Note, however, that the khopesh is not an axe, but rather a slashing weapon like a sabre. Its origins can be traced back to Sumer of the third millennium BC, where the Stele of Vultures depicts Eannatum of Lagash, the world's first emperor, wielding a khopesh. Many of the histories of Egyptian Pharaohs depict them holding the weapon. Indeed, most examples of khopesh recovered from tombs do not show signs of ever having been sharpened, indicating their use as ceremonial, or status symbols.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_EGYPT_KHOPESH_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Khopesh is the unique Egyptian replacement for the Spearman. It's a strong early unit that has an edge in direct combat. However, unlike the Spearman it replaces, it does not have a combat bonus against mounted units.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_EGYPT_KHOPESH_HELP">
			<Text>Strong, front-line Unit of the Ancient Era. Only Egypt may build it. Deals increased damage against heavily damaged Units. Does not have a bonus against Mounted Units.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_EGYPT_MERCY">
			<Text>Mercy</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_EGYPT_MERCY_HELP">
			<Text>+30% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength vs [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Units at or below 50 HP[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Kibitum -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 27/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_0">
			<Text>Legacy</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_0_HELP">
			<Text>+10% [ICON_STRENGTH] Defense against [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Ranged[ENDCOLOR] attacks.[NEWLINE]Unit gets +8% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]every 2 levels gained[ENDCOLOR] until level [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]12[ENDCOLOR], and level [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]15[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_1">
			<Text>Legacy I</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_1_HELP">
			<Text>+8% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_2">
			<Text>Legacy II</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_2_HELP">
			<Text>+16% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_3">
			<Text>Legacy III</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_3_HELP">
			<Text>+24% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_4">
			<Text>Legacy IV</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_4_HELP">
			<Text>+32% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_5">
			<Text>Legacy V</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_5_HELP">
			<Text>+40% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_6">
			<Text>Legacy VI</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_6_HELP">
			<Text>+50% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_7">
			<Text>A Winner is You</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_7_HELP">
			<Text>+75% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_BABYLON_KIBITUM">
			<Text>Sabum Kibitum</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_BABYLON_KIBITUM_HELP">
			<Text>Front-line Unit which grows more powerful with experience. Only Babylon may build it. This unit is stronger than the Spearman it replaces. Receives additional [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength for every few levels and gains more XP from fights.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_BABYLON_KIBITUM_STRATEGY">
			<Text>A soldier to stand the test of time. The Kibitum is not the strongest unit in its era, but its true strength lies in how it gains more power from experience than normal units. Keep these soldiers alive, and they will form an indispensable core for your army.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_BABYLON_KIBITUM_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The Babylonians were descended from semi-nomadic Amorite and Akkadian tribes from upper Mesopotamia. With the collapse of the Sumerian and Akkadian kingdoms, these Amorite tribes poured into Mesopotamia unopposed and established new dynasties. While in many respects these conquerors assimilated into Sumerian culture, their armies retained the toughness of their nomadic roots.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				The Sabum Kibitum were the heavy troops of the Babylonians and one of the earliest examples of career soldiers in history. Assembled from the royal guard and city residents, Sabum Kibitum were armed with long and short spears, javelins and bows to form a disciplined and flexible fighting force.
			</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Klepht -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 5/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_GREECE_PHILHELLENISM">
			<Text>Philhellenism</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_GREECE_PHILHELLENISM_HELP">
			<Text>Unit gains [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production in the [ICON_CAPITAL] Capital and [ICON_GOLD] Gold for every City-State Ally or Friend on [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Ranged Attack[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREECE_KLEPHT">
			<Text>Klepht</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREECE_KLEPHT_HELP">
			<Text>A quick and elusive guerilla fighter. Only Greece may build it. Slightly weaker than the Gatling Gun it replaces and does not have the [COLOR_RED]Covering Fire I[ENDCOLOR] Promotion. Starts with the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Philhellenism[ENDCOLOR] and [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Altitude Training[ENDCOLOR] Promotions, and can move after attacking.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREECE_KLEPHT_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Klepht is not as powerful as the Gatling Gun it replaces, but can move quickly through hills, even after attacking. This unit also gains gold and production for every city-state ally every time it attacks a unit.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREECE_KLEPHT_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Bandits and mountainfolk, turned anti-Ottoman insurgents and freedom fighters, The Klephts were the bedrock upon which the modern Greek army was formed. Together with the men originally hired to capture them, the Armatoloi, the Klephts formed the "yeast of liberty", and the first hope for Greek independence after more than four centuries of Ottoman rule.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Undisciplined and flighty as one would expect of brigands, Klephts waged an effective guerilla campaign against the much larger Ottoman armies sent to subdue them.  Massacres on both sides of the conflict were inflicted, but European sympathies fell heavily in favor of the Greeks. The unbridled cruelty of the Muslim Ottomans outraged Europe’s citizenry, who raised supplies, food and even soldiers to fight for a Hellenic independence.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				After 8 years Ottoman forces had finally managed to crush the revolt, but where Greek soldiers had failed poets and propaganda had succeeded. French, British and Russian governments each sent a fleet in defense of the Greek islands, in response to popular demand for intervention. In the face of such overwhelming force, the Ottomans sued for peace and liberated Greece. After more than 2,000 years under the boots of Macedonian, Roman and Ottoman conquerors, The Greek homeland was at last free -- unified as one people for the first time in history.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Koa -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 3/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_POLYNESIA_KAPU_KUIALUA_0">
			<Text>Kapu Ku'ialua</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_POLYNESIA_KAPU_KUIALUA_0_HELP">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]After Attack[ENDCOLOR] Defending Enemy Unit is marked, reducing its Max HP by [COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]20[ENDCOLOR] and Healing by [COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]10[ENDCOLOR] for [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]2[ENDCOLOR] turns.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_POLYNESIA_KAPU_KUIALUA_1">
			<Text>Leiomano</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_POLYNESIA_KAPU_KUIALUA_1_HELP">
			<Text>-20 Maximum HP and -10 HP [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Heal[ENDCOLOR]. Both effects last [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]2[ENDCOLOR] turns.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_POLYNESIA_KOA">
			<Text>Koa</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_POLYNESIA_KOA_HELP">
			<Text>Both a strong scout and front-line Unit. Only Polynesia may build it. Slightly stronger than the Scout it replaces, and starts with the [COLOR_GREEN]Amphibious[ENDCOLOR] Promotion.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Inflicts Leiomano status on enemies during melee combat, reducing Max HP by 20 and reducing Healing by 10 for 2 turns.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_POLYNESIA_KOA_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Koa is an effective early scout, able to hold its own against barbarians. It is stronger than the Scout, and can fight equally well across rivers and while embarked. This unit also inflicts Max HP and healing reduction to enemies it attacks for 2 turns, making them effective at clearing barbarians and preventing healing.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_POLYNESIA_KOA_TEXT">
			<Text>Deadly warriors from the islands of Hawai'i, Koa are named after the koa tree from which most of their weapons were fashioned. These warriors were trained extensively in Kapu Ku'ialua, a traditional Hawai'ian martial art specializing in weaponry and the focusing of mana into bone-shattering attacks.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]In battle, Koa warriors were well-versed in many weapons, including the less conventional knuckle-dusters, slings, and garrotes, but were also capable hand-to-hand fighters. More conventional daggers and clubs would occasionally be fitted with shark teeth along their edges, creating devastating serrated weapons called 'Leiomano'. These weapons were used similarly to the obsidian-tipped Macuahuitl of Central America.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Kobukseon -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_KOREA_COAST_MOVE">
			<Text>Coastal Patrol</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_KOREA_COAST_MOVE_HELP">
			<Text>Half [ICON_ARROW_RIGHT] Movement [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]in Deep Ocean[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_KOREA_DECK_SPIKES">
			<Text>Deck Spikes</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_KOREA_DECK_SPIKES_HELP">
			<Text>+25% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength vs [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Naval Melee Units[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Laguna -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VENICE_LAGUNA">
			<Text>Laguna</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VENICE_LAGUNA_HELP">
			<Text>
				+15% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production of Naval units, and increases [ICON_WAR] Military Supply by 2. When a [ICON_INTERNATIONAL_TRADE] Sea Trade Route originating here and targeting another Civilization is completed, receive a [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism boost with the Civilization based on your recent [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism output.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_FOOD] Food from Coast and Ocean Tiles, +2 [ICON_FOOD] Food, +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production to nearby Atolls and +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production from Sea Resources worked by this City. Sea Trade Routes gain +75% Range and +4 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_GOLD] Gold to Rialto District.[NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and +1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science to Venetian Arsenale.[NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism to Murano Glassworks.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must be built on the Coast. Requires a Lighthouse in the City.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VENICE_LAGUNA_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Laguna is a Medieval-era building, replacing the Harbor. It improves the range and [ICON_GOLD] Gold yield of sea trade routes, and boosts the value of sea tiles and resources. The Laguna also increases the [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production of Naval units by 15%, and increases Military Units supplied by this City''s population by 10%. The Laguna additionally provide bonus yields to Murano Glassworks, Rialto District, and Arsenale di Venezia.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VENICE_LAGUNA_TEXT">
			<Text>Laguna (eng. Lagoons) are shallow bodies of salt water separated from a larger sea by barrier islands or reefs. Venice itself is situated on the bank of a large lagoon, artificially maintained and enlarged by the dredging of the Venetian canals. The Venice Lagoon is also the largest wetland in the Mediterranean, offering protection as well as a rich source of food to its inhabitants.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Lamassu Gate -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ASSYRIA_LAMASSU_GATE">
			<Text>Lamassu Gate</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ASSYRIA_LAMASSU_GATE_TEXT">
			<Text>Lamassu are Assyrian protective deities, often depicted as having a human head, the body of a bull or lion, and bird's wings. The Lamassu were household protective spirits of Babylonian and Assyrian commoners, and were later adopted as royal protectors. Depictions of Lamassu are found throughout Assyrian architecture, positioned as sentinels at the thresholds of buildings and as colossal statues on each side of the city and palace gates. Common folk, for their part, engraved Lamassi onto clay tablets and buried them under their door's threshold.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ASSYRIA_LAMASSU_GATE_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique Wall replacement. Military Units supplied by this City's population increases by 20% and Increases the City's [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Bombard Strength by 25%. Contains a Writer specialist slot and a Great Work of Writing slot to help your empire get an early start on great works.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ASSYRIA_LAMASSU_GATE_HELP">
			<Text>[ICON_WAR] Military Supplies by this City's population increased by 20%. Increases the City's [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Bombard Strength by 10% and Strike Range by 1. Contains a slot for a [ICON_GREAT_WORK] Great Work of Writing.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Empire [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Needs Modifier is reduced by 5% in this City.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Landwehr -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_AUSTRIA_LANDWEHR">
			<Text>Landwehr</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_AUSTRIA_LANDWEHR_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The Austro-Hungarian Dual Monarchy sponsored two separate land armies to defend its Austrian and Hungarian portions. The Kaiserlich-Königliche Landwehr were one of three (or maybe six?) components of the Austrian national defense force between 1868 and 1918, the Austrian counterpart to the Hungarian Honved. Ludwig van Beethoven himself was commissioned to write the marching song for the Bohemian division, now famously known as the Yorkscher Marsch.[NEWLINE[NEWLINE]
				While the Hungarian Honved was generously supported by their parliament in Budapest, legislators in Vienna generally failed to do the same for the Landwehr, leaving it a skeletal force with only the appearance of parity. Nationalist interests led to a gradual strengthening and improvement of the Landwehr leading up to the First World War, just in time to see the entire Austro-Hungarian Empire collapse for good.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_AUSTRIA_LANDWEHR_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Landwehr is the backbone of the Industrial-era Austrian army. It excels in defending in owned territory and the territory of allied city-states. Each Landwehr can in the empire can also act as a passive source of culture if garrisoned in a city, fort or citadel.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_AUSTRIA_LANDWEHR_HELP">
			<Text>Stalwart defensive Unit. Only Austria may build it. Has additional [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Bonus when fighting in Territory owned by you or Allied City-States. Generates [ICON_CULTURE] Culture every turn if stationed in a Friendly Fort, Citadel or City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Starts with [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Field Works[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_AUSTRIA_YORKSCHER_MARCHE">
			<Text>Regimentsmarsche</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_AUSTRIA_YORKSCHER_MARCHE_HELP">
			<Text>Unit gains [ICON_CULTURE] Culture if unit [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]is Garrisoned or is standing in a Fort or Citadel inside Owned Territory[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Langskib -->
		<!-- Created by De_Genius on 28/10/2017, incorporated and modified by adan_eslavo on 21/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_DENMARK_LANGSKIB">
			<Text>Longship</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_DENMARK_LANGSKIB_HELP">
			<Text>Early Naval Exploration Unit. Only Denmark may build it. Available earlier, can move after attacking, and has [COLOR_GREEN]Blockade[ENDCOLOR] Promotion. Embarked Civilian Units starting their turn on the same tile as a longship may enter deep Ocean.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_DENMARK_LANGSKIB_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Danish Longship is an early ship unit which allow Denmark to have early sea control. This allows Denmark to begin scouting the far seas earlier than the other players to prepare future waves of colonization, defend your colonies abroad and provides support to raids with its bonuses to city attack at sea and performing hit-and-run tactics.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_DENMARK_LANGSKIB_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Longships were a type of boat invented and used by the Norsemen for trade, exploration, and warfare during the Viking Age. The longship's design evolved over many centuries, beginning in the Stone Age with the invention of the umiak and continuing up until the 6th century with clinker-built ships like Nydam and Kvalsund, appearing in its complete form between the 9th and 13th centuries. They were all made out of wood, with woven wool sails, and had numerous details and carvings on the hull.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Longships were notable for their quick speed and light construction. The ships were sturdy and reliable at sea, yet light enough to be carried onto shore or even tipped over as a makeshift shelter. The ability to move quickly in and out of shore was invaluable during the Vikings’ infamous raids.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The character and appearance of these ships are still reflected in Scandinavian boat-building traditions. Skills and methods for making longships are still used worldwide, often with modern adaptations
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_DENMARK_VIKING_EXPLORATION">
			<Text>Viking Exploration</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_DENMARK_VIKING_EXPLORATION_HELP">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Embarked Units[ENDCOLOR] starting in the same tile as a unit with this promotion [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]can cross Ocean[ENDCOLOR]. Promotion stays until Embarked Unit leaves the Ocean.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_DENMARK_VIKING_EXPLORATION_CAN_CROSS_OCEAN">
			<Text>Free to Explore</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_DENMARK_VIKING_EXPLORATION_CAN_CROSS_OCEAN_HELP">
			<Text>Unit [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]can cross Ocean Tiles[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>		
		
		<!-- Latifundium -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 10/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_ROME_LATIFUNDIUM">
			<Text>Latifundium</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_ROME_LATIFUNDIUM_HELP">
			<Text>Can be built on [ICON_RES_WHEAT] Wheat or any Resource normally requiring a Plantation and not adjacent to another Latifundium. Cannot be removed once it is built.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]On construction, immediately spawns an Improved [ICON_RES_FIGS] Figs Resource on a tile adjacent to the Latifundium, and claims that tile if not already owned by Rome.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Provides additional [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and [ICON_FOOD] Food. +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture to adjacent Plantations.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_ROME_LATIFUNDIUM_TEXT">
			<Text>An ancient precursor to today’s agribusinesses, A Latifundium was an expansive privately owned farm specializing in intensive agriculture. The first latifundia were accumulated from the spoils of war, confiscated from conquered peoples beginning in the early 2nd century BC in Magna Graecia (Southern Italy). The Latifundia system later expanded with conquest, to the Roman provinces of the Maghreb and Hispania Baetica in southern Spain
			[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]These estates depended on forced labor for their productivity, often supplied by the enslavement of the very peoples whose land had been taken. The Latifundia consolidated into larger estates with greater economies of scale. Owners re-invested their profits by purchasing small neighbouring farms. Evicted from their farms and replaced by slave labour, the Roman peasantry were forced to find work in the cities of Rome, though often resorting to squatting and handouts.
			[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Latifundia became the template upon which later European nations would base their imperial experiments. The Spanish are especially noteworthy for patterning the Encomienda system after the late Roman Latifundia.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_ROME_LATIFUNDIUM">
			<Text>Build a [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_ROME_LATIFUNDIUM]Latifundium[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_ROME_LATIFUNDIUM_HELP">
			<Text>Constructs a Latifundium, which yields [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture.[NEWLINE]On construction, spawns an Improved [ICON_RES_FIGS] Figs Resource adjacent to the Latifundium, and the Figs tile is claimed by Rome.[NEWLINE]Adjacent Plantations Receive +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_ROME_LATIFUNDIUM_REC">
			<Text>It will increase [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture.[NEWLINE]Spawns an Improved [ICON_RES_FIGS] Figs Resource adjacent to the Latifundium on construction, and the Figs tile is claimed by Rome.[NEWLINE]Adjacent Plantations Receive +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Legion (lua code in Ballista.lua)-->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 30/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ROME_PRAEFECTUS_CASTRORUM_ON_LEGION">
			<Text>Praefectus Castrorum</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ROME_PRAEFECTUS_CASTRORUM_ON_LEGION_HELP">
			<Text>+60% [ICON_WORKER] Work Rate if unit [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]starts turn within 2 tiles from Great General[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ROME_PRAEFECTUS_CASTRORUM_EFFECT">
			<Text>Camp Management</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ROME_PRAEFECTUS_CASTRORUM_EFFECT_HELP">
			<Text>+60% [ICON_WORKER] Work Rate [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]from Great General[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Licorne -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 26/10/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_RUSSIA_GRAPESHOT">
			<Text>Grapeshot</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_RUSSIA_GRAPESHOT_HELP">
			<Text>+50% [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Ranged Combat Strength vs [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Melee and Gunpowder Units[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_RUSSIA_LICORNE">
			<Text>Licorne</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_RUSSIA_LICORNE_HELP">
			<Text>Highly mobile Siege Unit. Only Russia may build it. This Unit is available earlier, has better mobility in Enemy Territory, and can move after attacking. Very effective against enemy Melee and Gunpowder Units.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_RUSSIA_LICORNE_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Licorne is a siege unit that can change the course of battle. Innovative construction allows moving after attacks and no penalty while attacking melee units. Is available earlier than the Field Gun.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_RUSSIA_LICORNE_TEXT">
			<Text>Licorne is the French name given to the Russian 'unicorn' cannons, named for the distinctively shaped handles on the gun barrels. Devised in 1757, Licornes were a flexible design, easy to fire and transport and made in many differing weights and power. Lighter designs are best remembered from their use as mobile horse artillery, a Russian innovation that would change the European theory of combined arms for the next century.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Longbowman -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 6/01/2018 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ENGLAND_AGINCOURT">
			<Text>Agincourt</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ENGLAND_AGINCOURT_HELP">
			<Text>+20% [ICON_RANGED_STRENGTH] Attack Bonus and +20% [ICON_STRENGTH] Defense Bonus vs [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Armor and Mounted Units[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>


		<!-- Madrasah -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARABIA_MADRASAH">
			<Text>Madrasa</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARABIA_MADRASAH_TEXT">
			<Text>"Madrasa" is Arabic for any type of educational institution. Though often with a religious component, madrasas were primarily secular, and could cover anything from elementary to higher learning, including medicine, law, science, philosophy or the education of women. The first madrasa, the Gama'at al-Qarawiyyn, was established in 859 AD by Fatimah al-Fihri, the daughter of a wealthy merchant. During the rule of the Fatimid, Ayyubid and Mamluk dynasties, the practice of sponsoring madrasas by the ruling elite spread across Egypt and the Middle East. As Europe suffered through the Dark Ages, the madrasas of the Turks and Arabs would keep the best of Western knowledge alive, blending it with that of the East.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARABIA_MADRASAH_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique Arabian replacement for the University. In addition to the bonuses of a University, the Madrasa generates additional yields when you purchase anything with Faith or expend a Great Person.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARABIA_MADRASAH_HELP">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science from Jungle tiles worked by this City. Gain 25% of the [ICON_RESEARCH] Science output of the City as an instant boost to your current Research when a [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen is born in this City. -1 [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Unhappiness from [ICON_RESEARCH] Illiteracy.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Gain 15% of the Cost of any [ICON_PEACE] Faith Purchase as [ICON_RESEARCH] Science in this City. Gain 5 [ICON_PEACE] Faith and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture whenever you Expend a [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Great Person, scaling with Era.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Monitor -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_AMERICA_MONITOR">
			<Text>Harbor Defense</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_AMERICA_MONITOR_HELP">
			<Text>+5% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]to adjacent Friendly Cities[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_AMERICA_HARDENED">
			<Text>Hardened</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_AMERICA_HARDENED_HELP">
			<Text>All incoming damage is reduced by 3.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Monolithic Church -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 12/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH">
			<Text>Monolithic Church</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The term "Monolithic Church" (or "rock-hewn church") can be attributed to any church cut from a single stone formation, but is most often used to refer to the complex of 11 churches in Lalibela, Ethiopia. These churches were constructed in the 12th century by King Gebre Mesqel Lalibela, a devout Christian. This 'New Jerusalem' is situated in a mountainous region in the heart of Ethiopia, and is an important center of Christian pilgrimage to this day.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Monolithic Churches are found in places besides Lalibela, including many in Tigray. These churches were almost unknown to the outside world until Abba Tewelde Medhin Josief, a Catholic priest, announced the existence of over 120 rock-hewn churches, 90 of which were still in use. Over the next few years, the total of known churches was raised to 153.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_HELP">
			<Text>
				Can be built on [ICON_RES_STONE] Stone or on Unfeatured Hills if not next to another Monolithic Church. Improves [ICON_RES_STONE] Stone resources[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Provides [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_PEACE] Faith. Instead of Technologies, Monolithic Churches are improved by the completing [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Social Policy Trees[ENDCOLOR] and adopting an [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Ideology[ENDCOLOR] or [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Religious Beliefs[ENDCOLOR]:[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_CULTURE] for every Ancient Policy Tree,[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_PEACE] for every Medieval Policy Tree,[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_RESEARCH] for every Industrial Policy Tree,[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_PEACE] for adopting a Pantheon,[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] for founding a Religion,[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_CULTURE] and [ICON_PRODUCTION] for enhancing a Religion,[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_GOLD] and [ICON_PRODUCTION] for reforming a Religion,[NEWLINE]
				+2 [ICON_GOLD] for adopting an Ideology.[NEWLINE]
				[NEWLINE]Every Monolithic Church benefits from [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Ethiopia's[ENDCOLOR] Policies and Religious Beliefs, even if located outside Ethiopia's borders.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH">
			<Text>Construct a [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH]Monolithic Church[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_HELP">
			<Text>Constructs a Monolithic Church, which increases [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_PEACE] Faith. Monolithic Churches increase yields if [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Ethiopia Adopts[ENDCOLOR] more Policies and Beliefs.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_REC">
			<Text>It will increase [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_PEACE] Faith.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Nilometer -->
		<!-- Created by BlueGhost, incorporated and modified by adan_eslavo on 7/01/2018 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_EGYPT_NILOMETER">
			<Text>Nilometer</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_EGYPT_NILOMETER_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Nilometer is an Egyptian unique building, replacing the Water Mill. It greatly increases the city's [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production output. On construction, 2 Flax resources spawn near the city, which provide additional culture and Production. This building can be built anywhere.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Flax prefers to spawn on rivers and flood plains, and will not spawn on hills or snow.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_EGYPT_NILOMETER_HELP">
			<Text>+2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for every 5 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens in the City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]2 [ICON_RES_FLAX] Flax Resources spawn near the City.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Oppidum -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 30/10/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_CELTS_OPPIDUM">
			<Text>Oppidum</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_CELTS_OPPIDUM_HELP">
			<Text>
				Cannot be built next to another Oppidum.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Unique Celtic Great Tile Improvement. It will improve Strategic Resources. Provides various yields and +100% [ICON_STRENGTH] Defense Bonus to Units stationed on it, and HP to a nearby City. Improves Adjacent Tile Improvements:[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_FOOD] and +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] to Farms,[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_FOOD] and +1 [ICON_PEACE] to Camps,[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] and +1 [ICON_PEACE] to Pastures,[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] and +1 [ICON_GOLD] to Mines,[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] and +1 [ICON_RESEARCH] to Quarries,[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_GOLD] and +1 [ICON_CULTURE] to Plantations,[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_FOOD] and +1 [ICON_RESEARCH] to Lumbermills,[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_FOOD] and +1 [ICON_CULTURE] to Logging Camps,[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_GOLD] and +1 [ICON_PEACE] to Fishing Boats.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Each Oppidum on Empire increases the effectiveness of the Hurry Production action of [ICON_GREAT_ENGINEER] Great Engineers, the Discover Technology action of [ICON_GREAT_SCIENTIST] Great Scientists, and the length of [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] 'We Love the King' Days from Trade Missions conducted by [ICON_GREAT_MERCHANT] Great Merchants.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_CELTS_OPPIDUM_TEXT">
			<Text>
				An Oppidum is a large defended settlement associated with the late La Tene culture. These fortified villages were often built in naturally protected areas and full of circular constructions. In times of conflict, the people who lived in open fields moved to these strategically located compounds to ensure their safety. Oppida could also have other purposes such as control of territory or safeguarding of crops. The most famous oppidum was Alesia, the site of the battle between Julius Caesar and Vercingetorix and the final defeat of the Gauls, ending of Gallic independence in France and Belgium.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Oppidum improve the yields of adjacent improvements:[NEWLINE]
				[ICON_BULLET]+1 [ICON_FOOD] Food and +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production to Farms[NEWLINE]
				[ICON_BULLET]+1 [ICON_FOOD] Food and +1 [ICON_PEACE] Faith to Camps[NEWLINE]
				[ICON_BULLET]+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and +1 [ICON_PEACE] Faith  to Pastures[NEWLINE]
				[ICON_BULLET]+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold to Mines[NEWLINE]
				[ICON_BULLET]+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and +1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science to Quarries[NEWLINE]
				[ICON_BULLET]+1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture to Plantations[NEWLINE]
				[ICON_BULLET]+1 [ICON_FOOD] Food and +1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science to Lumbermills[NEWLINE]
				[ICON_BULLET]+1 [ICON_FOOD] Food and +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture to Logging Camps[NEWLINE]
				[ICON_BULLET]+1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and +1 [ICON_PEACE] Faith to Fishing Boats
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_CELTS_OPPIDUM">
			<Text>Construct an [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_CELTS_OPPIDUM]Oppidum[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_CELTS_OPPIDUM_HELP">
			<Text>Cannot be built next to another Oppidum.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]It will increase [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]All Yields[ENDCOLOR]. Gives +100% [ICON_STRENGTH] Defense Bonus to units stationed on it, and permanent +10 HP to a nearby city. Provides bonus yields to most non-road and non-great person Improvements.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_CELTS_OPPIDUM_REC">
			<Text>Unit will be consumed[NEWLINE]Unique Celtic Great Tile Improvement. Will connect Strategic Resources on this tile to the trade network. Gives a [ICON_STRENGTH] Defense Bonus to units stationed on it, and +10 HP to a nearby City. Adjacent Improvements gain additional bonus yields.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Pairidaeza -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 16/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PERSIA_PAIRIDAEZA">
			<Text>Pairidaeza</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PERSIA_PAIRIDAEZA_HELP">
			<Text>Available earlier. +25% [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Great People Points in the City. 1 Specialist in this City no longer produces [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Unhappiness from Urbanization.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+15% [ICON_GOLD] Gold in the City during a [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age, and +30 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture as an instant boost in the City when a [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age begins.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Nearby Oases: +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_CITRUS] Citrus: +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food, +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_COCOA] Cocoa: +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food, +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PERSIA_PAIRIDAEZA_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Pairidaeza is the Persian unique Garden replacement. In addition to the normal bonuses of a Garden, each the Pairidaeza increases Gold production during Golden Ages. The beginning of every Golden Age produces culture for each city with a Pairidaeza, so be sure to build them in every city.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PERSIA_PAIRIDAEZA_TEXT">
			<Text>A Pairidaeza is a walled garden popularized by the Achaemenid. As a tool of state, Pairidaeza were invaluable in flaunting a kingdom’s ability to bring life to an area that would otherwise have none; its rectangular, ordered construction serving as a contrast the chaos of nature. The Achaemenid dynasty melded the pairidaeza with their royal hunting parks, an unsubtle way to show their command over both their empire and the natural world within it. The Persian gardens form the root of the greek “paradise”, informing western notions of an earthly Eden in art and poetry.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Pitz -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 16/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MAYA_KATUN_AHAW_0">
			<Text>K'atun Ahaw</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MAYA_KATUN_AHAW_0_HELP">
			<Text>Unit gets unique ability [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]every 20 Game Turns[ENDCOLOR]. Effect can be extended [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]4[ENDCOLOR] times.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MAYA_KATUN_AHAW_1">
			<Text>Hun K'atun Ahaw</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MAYA_KATUN_AHAW_1_HELP">
			<Text>+5 XP. +5% [ICON_DEFENSE] Combat Strength.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MAYA_KATUN_AHAW_2">
			<Text>Ka'a K'atun Ahaw</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MAYA_KATUN_AHAW_2_HELP">
			<Text>+10 XP. +10% [ICON_DEFENSE] Combat Strength. +5% [ICON_DEFENSE] Combat Strength [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]in Forest and Jungle[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MAYA_KATUN_AHAW_3">
			<Text>Oox K'atun Ahaw</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MAYA_KATUN_AHAW_3_HELP">
			<Text>+10 XP. +10% [ICON_DEFENSE] Combat Strength. +15% [ICON_DEFENSE] Combat Strength [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]in Forest and Jungle[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MAYA_KATUN_AHAW_4">
			<Text>Kan K'atun Ahaw</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MAYA_KATUN_AHAW_4_HELP">
			<Text>+15 XP. +10% [ICON_DEFENSE] Combat Strength. +5% [ICON_DEFENSE] Combat Strength [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]in Forest and Jungle[ENDCOLOR]. +10 HP [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Heal inside Friendly Territory[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MAYA_PITZ">
			<Text>Pitz Court</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MAYA_PITZ_HELP">
			<Text>Barracks, Forge, and Armory in this City gain +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production. -1 [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Unhappiness from [ICON_CULTURE] Boredom.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Grants [ICON_RESEARCH] Science and [ICON_PEACE] Faith at the end of every Long Count. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Land Units trained in this City receive the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]K'atun Ahaw[ENDCOLOR] Promotion, which grants new abilities for every 20 turns the Unit has been alive.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_PERFUME] Perfume: +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_OLIVE] Olives: +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food, +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MAYA_PITZ_STRATEGY">
			<Text>
				The Pitz Court is the Mayan unique building, replacing the Arena. In addition to the normal bonuses of an Arena, the Pitz Court provides Science and Faith at the end of every long count. Land units trained in a City with a Pitz Court receive the 'K'atun Ahaw' promotion, which grants new abilities for every 20 turns the unit has been alive.
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Hun: 5XP, +5% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Ka'a: 10XP, +10% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength, +5% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength in Forest/Jungle
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Oox: 10XP, +10% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength, +15% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength in Forest/Jungle
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Kan: 15XP, +10% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength, +15% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength in Forest/Jungle, +10 HP on Heal in Friendly Territory.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MAYA_PITZ_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The Mesoamerican Ball Game, or 'Pitz', is a game of ritual and cultural significance among the Mayan people. The object of the game is to keep the ball in play for as long as possible by striking back and forth within a sloped arena using the hips, though some variations allowed for elbows, shoulders and even rackets. The earliest archaeological evidence of the game come from a court estimated to be 3400 years old.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Over 1300 different ballcourts have been found within Mayan ruins, with relatively little variation in size or layout over thousands of years. Every court is shaped as a narrow alley with gently sloping walls on either side and enclosed endzones. This gave the court a roughly H-shaped layout. Later versions of the ballcourts would include hoops at the midpoint, suspended on the walls. Actually sending a ball through the ring must have been a rare occurrence, since the players could not use their hands or feet to guide the ball. Moreover, the rings were only slightly larger than the ball itself and were a long way from the playing alley.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				The game was more than a mere sporting event to the Mayan people, serving as a substitute for war in the case of a dispute between cities. Later Classical Mayan art suggests a link between the ball game and ritual sacrifice, with winners being decapitated as an offering to the gods. The Maya Twin Myth of the Popol Vuh describes the game between the Hero Twins, Hunahpu and Xbalanque, and lords of the underworld, One Death and Seven Death. The game was played so the Hero Twins might recover Hunahpu's head, which was being used as a ball by the Lords (Hunahpu had been using a squash for his head until his real one could be recovered).
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Pancerny -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 16/10/2017 modified 30/10/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_POLAND_BOGURODZICA">
			<Text>Bogurodzica</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_POLAND_BOGURODZICA_HELP">
			<Text>Unit gains [ICON_PEACE] Faith [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Kill[ENDCOLOR]. Bonus doubled [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Barbarian Kills[ENDCOLOR]. +25% [ICON_STRENGTH] Defense Bonus.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_POLAND_PANCERNY">
			<Text>Pancerny</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_POLAND_PANCERNY_HELP">
			<Text>A sturdy Mounted Skirmisher. Only Poland may build it. Earns [ICON_PEACE] Faith from each Enemy killed and double the amount from Barbarians. This Unit is stronger in both defense and offense than the Heavy Skirmisher, and has additional protection against Ranged Units.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_POLAND_PANCERNY_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Pancerny is the Polish replacement for the Heavy Skirmisher. It has stronger attack and defense than the Heavy Skirmisher, and takes reduced damage from Ranged attacks. The Pancerny also earns Faith for each enemy killed. As mounted unit, the Pancerny is vulnerable to Pikemen.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_POLAND_PANCERNY_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Towarzysz Pancerny (Mailed Companion) was a rank of Polish cavalryman from the 10th to 18th century, named for their chainmail armor. Pancerni were organized into companies, with each company consisting of 60 to 200 horsemen. Exceptionally well-armored, they used chainmail or platemail armor, vambraces, helmets, and buckler shields. The most common armaments were sabres, reflex bows and, with the arrival of gunpowder, flintlock pistols and carbines.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				After the rise of heavy cavalry the Pancerni often worked in concert with the newer and more heavily armed husaria, augmenting a cavalry charge and chasing down routing enemy soldiers. By the second half of the 17th century, they represented approximately 70% of all soldiers in the Polish military, fighting against Cossacks, Tatars, and the Swedish. The Husaria and Pancerni were eventually combined to form the ‘Kawaleria Narodowa’, the Polish-Lithuanian National Cavalry.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Pogost -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 14/10/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RUSSIA_POGOST_1">
			<Text>Pogost - Stage 1: Market</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RUSSIA_POGOST_2">
			<Text>Pogost - Stage 2: Intendant's Residention</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RUSSIA_POGOST_3">
			<Text>Pogost - Stage 3: Eastern Orthodox Church</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RUSSIA_POGOST_1_HELP">
			<Text>+10% [ICON_GOLD] Gold from [ICON_CONNECTED] City Connection in this City. +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold to Villages and Towns.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Incoming [ICON_INTERNATIONAL_TRADE] Trade Routes grants additional [ICON_GOLD] Gold for both City Owner and Trade Route Owner.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]-1 [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Unhappiness from [ICON_GOLD] Poverty. Gains additional traits, and a new look, at Banking and Architecture Technologies.[NEWLINE] Nearby [ICON_RES_BANANA] Bananas: +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RUSSIA_POGOST_2_HELP">
			<Text>+5% [ICON_GOLD] Gold from [ICON_CONNECTED] City Connection in this City. +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production to Villages and Towns.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RUSSIA_POGOST_3_HELP">
			<Text>+5% [ICON_GOLD] Gold from [ICON_CONNECTED] City Connection in this City. +2 [ICON_PEACE] Faith to Shrines, Temples and Monasteries.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RUSSIA_POGOST_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique Russian replacement for the Customs House. Initially, Pogosts are comparatively lackluster, but they develop new traits as the game progresses. Each stage increases Gold generated from City Connections, and The Pogost provides modest increases in gold from trade and culture, then gains modest boosts to gold and science at its second stage, and provides boosts to faith generation in its final stage.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RUSSIA_POGOST_TEXT">
			<Text>In many medieval Russian states, Pogosts began as inns and lodging for the nobility and priesthood, but may have doubled as community centers and trading hubs. By the end of the 10th century, however, Pogosts had evolved into administrative and legislative hubs throughout the Slavic states. By 1775 the last Pogost-led administrative district was abolished, and the buildings were repurposed as parishes of the Eastern Orthodox Church.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Prau -->
		<!-- Created by pineappledan; incorporated by adan_eslavo on 23/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_INDONESIA_FLYING_THE_AMA">
			<Text>Flying the Ama</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_INDONESIA_FLYING_THE_AMA_HELP">
			<Text>+2 [ICON_ARROW_RIGHT] Movement Points. Lost after unit upgrade.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDONESIA_PRAU">
			<Text>Prau</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDONESIA_PRAU_TEXT">
			<Text>One of the most ancient of seaworthy boat designs, the prau, also known as proa or perahu, are wooden sailing vessels consisting of a large hull (vaka) and a small hull (ama) set in parallel by a crossbeam (akas). Prau are believed to have been developed in Micronesia in the first century AD, spreading quickly throughout southeast Asia. Western accounts of prau first appear in the 16th century, when Magellan made note of their agility in his fateful trip to the Philippines.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]When sailing in strong winds, the crew walk between the hulls along the akas to counterbalance the force of the sail. A skilled prau crew can balance so as to lift the ama out of the water, called "flying the ama", and skim the ocean's surface to reach incredible speeds. Prau continue to be used worldwide, and modern designs can exceed 95km/h in favourable winds. This makes prau some of the fastest ships in the world; not bad for a 2,000 year old!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDONESIA_PRAU_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Prau is faster and cheaper than the Trireme it replaces and ignores zone of control. It is great for early game scouting and raiding.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDONESIA_PRAU_HELP">
			<Text>Effective early Naval Scout. Only Indonesia may build it. This unit is faster and available earlier than the Trireme it replaces. Starts with the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Pincer[ENDCOLOR] Promotion.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Penteconter -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 30/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PENTECONTER">
			<Text>Penteconter</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PENTECONTER_HELP">
			<Text>Dominant Classical Era Naval Unit used to own the seas well into the Medieval Era with its ranged attack.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PENTECONTER_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The first naval unit with a ranged attack. It cannot end its turn in Deep Ocean tiles outside of the city borders.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PENTECONTER_TEXT">
			<Text>The penteconter was an ancient Greek Galley, used for trade, piracy and warfare. The ship was rowed by 50 oarsmen arranged in 2 rows of 25, making the ship long, but relatively narrow. This design made the boat relatively quick, but difficult to turn during a naval engagement.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Pracinha -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BRAZIL_EXPEDITIONARY_FORCE">
			<Text>Expeditionary Force</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BRAZIL_EXPEDITIONARY_FORCE_HELP">
			<Text>+1% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]for every tile between unit and [ICON_CAPITAL] Capital[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BRAZIL_TOURISM">
			<Text>Glorious Banner</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BRAZIL_TOURISM_HELP">
			<Text>Unit gains [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]toward all Civilizations on Kill[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Prowler -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 20/10/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_IROQUOIS_PROWLER">
			<Text>Prowler</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_IROQUOIS_PROWLER_HELP">
			<Text>A nimble attacker excelling in Rough Terrain. Only the Iroquois may build it. Cheaper than the Musketman, this Unit can attack from behind obstacles and withdraw from enemy attacks.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_IROQUOIS_PROWLER_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Prowler is a cheap unit that makes perfect use of surrounding rough terrain. The Prowler's "Indirect Fire" promotion allows him to attack unseen from deep forests and hills, with the aid of reconnaissance or friendly borders. When attacked by an enemy unit, he can withdraw from combat. The prowler's evasiveness makes him an ideal guerilla Unit.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_IROQUOIS_PROWLER_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Unlike many other tribes, the Iroquois had easy access to trade goods at Dutch forts along the Hudson River, and traded for various goods and luxuries. Weapons of war such as the iron axe and musket were highly sought after, and by the 1640s the Iroquois were well-equipped to fight their traditional Huron and Algonquian enemies. Common muskets were given in exchange for pelts and food, but often of lighter and smaller caliber than military-grade muskets. The Dutch and British feared giving high-quality weapons to people who could turn against them, but the Iroquois often found the smaller weapons more suitable to rough terrain anyways.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				War tactics were changed after the Iroquois' acquisition of firearms. The lethality of their new weapons put the Iroquois, never a highly populous group, in a precarious position. The tribes' custom of absorbing refugees and prisoners of war changed as fewer and fewer warriors survived clashes with European arms. Great armies walking with prominent chiefs and shamans were replaced with guerilla tactics, small bands of troops guided by commanders.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Gumey -->
		<!-- Created by pineappledan on 29/08/2018 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SONGHAI_GUMEY">
			<Text>Gumey</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SONGHAI_GUMEY_HELP">
			<Text>When a [ICON_INTERNATIONAL_TRADE] Land Trade Route originating here and targeting another Civ is completed, receive a [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism boost with the Civ based on recent [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism output. +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_GOLD] Gold for every 3 Desert or 3 Tundra tiles worked by the City. [ICON_GREAT_MERCHANT] Merchant Specialists in this City gain +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][ICON_INTERNATIONAL_TRADE] Land Trade Routes gain +75% Range and +3 [ICON_GOLD] Gold. Incoming [ICON_INTERNATIONAL_TRADE] Trade Routes generate +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold for the City and the Trade Route Owner. +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture if a [ICON_INTERNATIONAL_TRADE] Trade Unit passes through the City.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_TRUFFLES] Truffles: +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_COTTON] Cotton: +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_FUR] Furs: +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold, +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_FLAX] Flax: +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold, +1 [ICON_PEACE] Faith.[NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold to all Nearby Luxuries.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SONGHAI_GUMEY_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Gumey is a Songhai unique building that replaces the Caravansary. The Gumey provides much larger bonuses to trade than the normal Caravansary, boosting International Trade Routes, and extra yields if a trade route passes through the city. Expand your empire's territory and reap the economic benefits of a vast trade empire.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SONGHAI_GUMEY_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Even before gaining their independence from the Mali Empire, the Songhai had become ludicrously wealthy off the trade of gold, salt and slaves from the Trans-Saharan trade routes. The Songhai's seat of power lay at the edge of the vast Saharan desert, forming an entrepot between the Taghazan salt mines to the north, the gold mines in the southwest, and the distant markets in Egypt and the Middle East. The Gumey were riverside ports and waystations, used to conduct goods and soldiers back and forth along the Niger river, before they were loaded onto camels for the arduous journey across the open desert.
			</Text>
		</Row>		
		
		<!-- Qizilbash -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 29/10/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_PERSIA_SAFAVI_AGITATOR">
			<Text>Safavi Agitator</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_PERSIA_SAFAVI_AGITATOR_HELP">
			<Text>Unit gains [ICON_PEACE] Faith, [ICON_GOLD] Gold and [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age Points when [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Pillaging Tiles[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PERSIA_QIZILBASH">
			<Text>Qizilbash</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PERSIA_QIZILBASH_HELP">
			<Text>Potent Mid-game cavalry focused on economic warfare. Only Persia may build it. Can always be purchased with [ICON_PEACE] Faith.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Generates [ICON_PEACE] Faith, [ICON_GOLD] Gold, and [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age Points when pillaging tiles.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PERSIA_QIZILBASH_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Qizilbash is the Unique Persian replacement for the Lancer. Stronger than the Lancer, the Qizilbash also generates Faith, Gold and Golden Age Points for every tile they pillage. This unit can also be purchased with Faith without needing a religious tenet. Maintaining a strong presence in enemy territory allows Persia to generate Faith for more Qizilbash, and trigger more Golden Ages to increase your army's power.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PERSIA_QIZILBASH_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Qizilbash (Tr: “red-heads”) was originally a pejorative for the followers of the Safawiyyah Sufi order. Named for their distinctive crimson headwear, the Qizilbash organized into a Shi'ite society reminiscent of a European knightly order. Though primarily of Turkman origin, the Qizilbash proved instrumental in the establishment of the Iranian Safavid Dynasty.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				In a campaign to avenge the death of his father, Ismail I led 7000 Qizilbash warriors to victory over an Aq Qoyunlu force of 30 000, and established the Safavid State. Within eleven short years, Ismail brought all of Iran under his control, becoming the first ethnically Iranian monarch to unify Iran in over 850 years. Though they had made him a powerful king, Ismail feared the influence of the Qizilbash over the Iranian people. Ismail and his successors would spend the next 80 years diminishing the threat posed by the foreign Qizilbash, replacing them with slave soldiers from the Caucasus. Nevertheless, the Qizilbash maintained a place of honor within the Safavid Empire, both on the battlefield and at court.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Qila -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 5/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INDIA_QILA">
			<Text>Qila</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INDIA_QILA_HELP">
			<Text>City must have Walls. +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for Quarries worked by this City. Slightly reduces [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Distress. Contains 1 slot for a [ICON_GREAT_WORK] Great Work of Art and generates +1 [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Great Artist Point per turn. +3 [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism at Flight.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+25 City HP for every National Wonder and World Wonder built in the City. 20% of [ICON_STRENGTH] City Defense is converted into [ICON_CULTURE] Culture every turn.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Empire [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Needs Modifier is reduced by 10% in this City.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INDIA_QILA_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Qila is the unique Indian replacement for the Castle. In addition to the normal bonuses of the Castle, the Qila generates Culture and Great Artist Points. 10% of City Defense is converted into Culture every turn and the city gains more defense for wonders built in the city. Your most magnificent cities also become more difficult to capture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INDIA_QILA_TEXT">
			<Text>The Mughals were an Islamic empire that invaded India in the 15th century, and ruled most of the sub-continent until the mid 19th. During their rule, they constructed elaborate forts called Qila across the countryside which served as administrative centers and living quarters for the occupiers. These forts were beautiful structures, fitting palaces for the rulers of a vast empire. Several--including the magnificent "Lahore Fort" and Red Fort of Agra--survive today and remain as some of the largest tourist attractions to India, monuments to the Mughals' power and style.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Ranch -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AMERICA_RANCH">
			<Text>Homestead</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AMERICA_RANCH_TEXT">
			<Text>A Homestead is a complex of buildings on a large landholding, typically a ranch, settled in accordance with the United States Homesteading Acts. The US Government implemented a policy of "free soil", allowing claimants, effectively squatters, ownership of land which they had converted into productive farms or ranches. Nearly 10% of the continental United States was settled in this way; 270 million acres of land claimed by approximately 1.6 million homesteaders between 1862 and 1930.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The colonization of vast swathes of the continental interior left an indelible mark on the American psyche. Legends of the frontier, the Old West, Cowboys and Indians still permeate American culture, informing their sense of independence, enterprising spirit and mastery over nature.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AMERICA_RANCH_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Homestead is the American replacement for the Stable. In addition to the regular abilities of the Stable, the Homestead immediately claims all Sheep, Horse, Cattle and Bison resources around the City. The production bonus for each claimed tile can help refund a bit of the cost of the Homestead immediately. The Homestead boosts Bison in addition to all the resources normally boosted by a Ranch, and all boosted resources gain additional food.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The Homestead boosts the production of workers and settler units, and allows America to train Pioneers a full era before they usually unlock. With the Homestead, America can settle new, powerful cities quickly.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AMERICA_RANCH_HELP">
			<Text>+33% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production when building Mounted Units and +25% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production when building Worker and Settler units. Pioneers can be built in this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Increases the [ICON_WAR] Military Supply Cap from [ICON_CITIZEN] Population in the City by 10%. Gain 15 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production whenever a [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen is born in the City, scaling with Era.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]On completion, the city immediately claims all [ICON_RES_HORSE] Horse, [ICON_RES_SHEEP] Sheep, [ICON_RES_COW] Cattle, and [ICON_RES_BISON] Bison within 3 tiles of the City. The City gains 20 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for each tile claimed, scaling with Era. Internal [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production [ICON_INTERNATIONAL_TRADE] Trade Routes from this City generate +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_HORSE] Horses: +2 [ICON_FOOD] Food, +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_SHEEP] Sheep: +2 [ICON_FOOD] Food, +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_COW] Cattle: +2 [ICON_FOOD] Food, +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_BISON] Bison: +2 [ICON_FOOD] Food, +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Riad -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MAROCCO_RIAD">
			<Text>Riad</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MAROCCO_RIAD_TEXT">
			<Text>
				A Riad is a traditional Moroccan house with an interior garden or courtyard. The riads were often plain on the exterior, but lavishly decorated inside, projecting humility and austerity while preserving a family’s privacy. The interior gardens often featured elaborate fountains and tiling, while the walls were adorned with quotes from the Quran in Arabic calligraphy.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				While architectural style has changed over the years, the riad’s basic form is still used in modern design. Riads have enjoyed a renaissance, with restoration efforts of old, often crumbling buildings in Marrakech and Essaouira. Many riads are now repurposed as hotels or restaurants.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MAROCCO_RIAD_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Riad is the Moroccan unique replacement for the Garden. Gold purchases in this city are slightly cheaper. Gold generation in the city is converted into [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Great Merchant Points. Oases are boosted by the Riad more than by a normal Garden. Unlike other buildings, the Riad's base yields increase with each Era.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MAROCCO_RIAD_HELP">
			<Text>+25% [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Great People Points in the City. 15% of [ICON_GOLD] Gold in the City is converted into [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Great Merchant Points.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]1 Specialist in this City no longer produces [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Unhappiness from Urbanization. Cost of [ICON_GOLD] Gold purchasing in this City reduced by 5%.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Gains +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism every Era[NEWLINE]Nearby Oases: +3 [ICON_GOLD] Gold, +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_CITRUS] Citrus: +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food, +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_COCOA] Cocoa: +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food, +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Sachem's Council -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 14/10/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_IROQUOIS_DIPLOMATIC_RECIPROCITY">
			<Text>Reciprocity</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_IROQUOIS_DIPLOMATIC_RECIPROCITY_HELP">
			<Text>After creating an [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Embassy[ENDCOLOR] its yields are permanently added to your [ICON_CAPITAL] Capital's revenue if target City-State [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]is an Ally[ENDCOLOR] or only half, if it [COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]is not[ENDCOLOR] one.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_IROQUOIS_SACHEMS_COUNCIL">
			<Text>Sachem's Council</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_IROQUOIS_SACHEMS_COUNCIL_HELP">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture for every 5 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens in this City. All Councils gain +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, and all Chanceries gain +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+10% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production of Diplomatic Units. A [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Free[ENDCOLOR] Emissary Unit appears on completion. All [ICON_DIPLOMAT] Great Diplomats gain the [COLOR_GREEN]Reciprocity[ENDCOLOR] Promotion.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_FOOD] Food in City for every City-State Friend, and +2 [ICON_PEACE] Faith for every Ally.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Global Happiness for every Defensive Pact or Ongoing War.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_IROQUOIS_SACHEMS_COUNCIL_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique Iroquoian replacement for the Scrivener's Office. In addition to the normal bonuses provided by the Scrivener's Office, the Sachem's Council  provides faster generation of Great Diplomat units. Great Diplomats also receive a unique promotion, providing Science, Culture and gold for every embassy founded. All Councils in your empire also gain +1 Culture, and all Chanceries gain +2 Gold. The Sachem's Council also provides Happiness for every Defensive Pact and Declared War involving the Iroquois.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_IROQUOIS_SACHEMS_COUNCIL_TEXT">
			<Text>
				According to oral tradition, the five tribes of the Iroquois devoted much energy toward fighting and killing each other until the 1500s. It was at this time that the five tribes united into a powerful confederation, forming an elaborate political system including a bicameral (two-house) legislature.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				In accordance with their unwritten constitution, the confederacy was represented by 50 delegates, or Sachems -- male representatives of the tribes, hand-picked by their respective clan mother. The 17 sachems from the Seneca and Mohawk tribes met in one house while the 19 Oneida and Cayuga met in the other. The 14 Onondaga sachems acted as tie-breakers and had the power to veto decisions made by the others. In addition to Sachem, who met on Onondaga land to cast their votes, an advisory council was formed, called the Pine Trees. Pine Trees could be men or women appointed for their heroic feats and accomplishments. In 1715 the Tuscarora joined the league, and it was renamed the League of Six Nations. Benjamin Franklin’s dealings with the Iroquois left an impression on him, and led him to model the United States’ government after theirs.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				“The soil of the earth from one end of the land to the other is the property of the people who inhabit it. By birthright the Ongwehonweh (original beings) are the owners of the soil which they own and occupy and none other may hold it. The same law has been held from the oldest times. The Great Creator has made us of the one blood and of the same soil he made us and as only different tongues constitute different nations he established different hunting grounds and territories and made boundary lines between them...” [NEWLINE]
				-Excerpt from the Iroquois Constitution
			</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Sambadrome -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BRAZIL_SAMBADROME">
			<Text>Sambadrome</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BRAZIL_SAMBADROME_TEXT">
			<Text>A Sambadrome is an exhibition place for the Samba schools parades during Carnaval in Brazil. A Sambadrome generally consists of tiered spectator viewing areas surrounding a long alley for the schools to parade down.  The parades attract many thousands of Brazilians and foreign tourists each year.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BRAZIL_SAMBADROME_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Sambadrome is the unique Brazilian replacement for the Opera House. In addition to the bonuses of an Opera House, the Sambadrome also generates Golden Age Points. The Sambadrome comes with a Musician specialist slot, and all Musicians in the city generate extra Gold and Golden Age Points.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BRAZIL_SAMBADROME_HELP">
			<Text>Unique replacement for the Opera House. +10% [ICON_CULTURE] Culture in the City. 10% of [ICON_CULTURE] Culture created by the City counts as [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age Points Per Turn. +33% [ICON_GREAT_MUSICIAN] Great Musician Points in the City. All Musicians' Guilds adds +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Contains 1 slot for [ICON_GREAT_WORK] Great Work of Music.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Starts 10 turns of 'Carnaval' when completed.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Scythed Chariot -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 26/10/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_CELTS_SCYTHE">
			<Text>Rend</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_CELTS_SCYTHE_HELP">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]On Move[ENDCOLOR] unit inflicts 10 [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]to all new adjacent Enemy Units[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_CELTS_CARNYX">
			<Text>Carnyx</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_CELTS_CARNYX_HELP">
			<Text>+10% [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Ranged Combat Strength vs [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Archer and Melee Units[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CELTS_SCYTHED_CHARIOT">
			<Text>Scythed Chariot</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CELTS_SCYTHED_CHARIOT_HELP">
			<Text>A dangerous Unit on Open Terrain. Only the Celts may build it. This unit is stronger against Archer and Melee Units.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]After moving, deals damage to all newly adjacent Enemy Units.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CELTS_SCYTHED_CHARIOT_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Scythed Chariot is a Celtic unique unit made for destroying enemy lines. Enemies take damage whenever the Scythed Chariot moves adjacent to them, making this unit deadly in open terrain. Make every move count to maximize damage, but be careful not to leave your Chariots exposed to enemies on their turn. A mounted unit, the Scythed Chariot is vulnerable to Spearmen.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CELTS_SCYTHED_CHARIOT_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Scythed chariots are modified war chariots with long blades extending from the wheel axels. Though often dismissed as fanciful storytelling, the use of scythed chariots has been ascribed to Pictish, Irish and Iceni armies. The only report of a scythed chariot in Britain outside of Roman propaganda comes from the Irish Ulster Cycle, during the adventures of Chu Chulainn.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Although chariots had fallen out of use in continental Europe from the end of the 3rd century BC, Caesar found that they remained significant in British warfare. Caesar encountered both Celtic cavalry and chariots and described how these warriors would throw javelins from their vehicles before dismounting to fight on foot. Celtic soldiers could return to their chariots to quickly retreat or redeploy.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				“They make war not only on horseback but also from two horse chariots and cars armed in the Gallic fashion – they call them Covinni - on which they use axles equipped with scythes.” [NEWLINE]
				- Pomponius Mela
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Seir Morb -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 9/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SIAM_COASTAL_CANNON">
			<Text>Coastal Cannon</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SIAM_COASTAL_CANNON_HELP">
			<Text>+25% [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Ranged Combat Strength vs [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Naval Units[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SIAM_CROACHING_TIGER">
			<Text>Crouching Tiger</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SIAM_CROACHING_TIGER_HELP">
			<Text>15 Bonus Damage [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]for every Remaining Movement Point[ENDCOLOR] on Attack.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SIAM_SEIR_MORB">
			<Text>Seir Morb</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SIAM_SEIR_MORB_HELP">
			<Text>Industrial Era Unit specializing in coastal defense. Only Siam may build it. Has a bonus against Naval Units instead of a penalty. No bonuses against Cities.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Deals more damage on attack the less the Unit has moved. Starts with the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Cover I[ENDCOLOR] and [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Cover II[ENDCOLOR] Promotions.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SIAM_SEIR_MORB_STRATEGY">
			<Text>A powerful coastal defense cannon, the Seir Morb is more powerful than the Field Gun it replaces, especially against naval targets, but deals less damage to cities. The Seir Morb receives a combat boost for every remaining movement point when attacking, so pick a good spot and keep it steady.  Location, Location, Location.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SIAM_SEIR_MORB_TEXT">
			<Text>Despite Siam's remarkable diplomacy, they did occasionally come into conflict with the great imperial powers which threated their independence. When the French set their sights on Laos, the Siamese mistakenly believed the English would support them against France, and prepared for war. The Seir Morb ("Crouching Tiger") were the most technologically advanced cannons in the Siamese arsenal at the time; coastal artillery which could destroy any French boats foolish enough to enter their harbours. No amount of raw power, however, can account for corruption and disorganization; the French managed to establish their beachheads, and the coastal artillery of Thailand remained unused. It turns out that the finest artillery money can buy still needs to be fired.</Text>
		</Row>


		<!-- Suffet -->
		<!-- Created by pineappledan -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET">
			<Text>Suffet</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_HELP">
			<Text>This Carthaginian unique Great Person replaces the Great General. Aside from the ability to boost nearby troops and construct citadels, this unit disembarks onto water tiles as a [ICON_GREAT_ADMIRAL] Great Admiral. Causes Friendly Units beginning in the same or adjacent tile to ignore Enemy Zone of Control for that turn.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Suffet is the unique Great General and Great Admiral replacement for Carthage. This unit causes all friendly units beginning in the same or an adjacent tile to ignore an enemy's Zone of Control for that turn. In addition, whenever this unit embarks into a water tile, it becomes a Great Admiral. It returns to Great General status upon disembarking into a city. Use a Suffet to enhance your military's power and mobility in pitched battles.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_TEXT">
			<Text>In the various independent city-states and colonies of Phoenicia a Suffet (or Shophet) was a non-royal magistrate granted control over a city-state, sometimes functioning much in the same way as a Roman consul. Following the overthrow of its monarchy in the 5th century BC, Carthage was ruled by a number of aristocratic councils presided over by two suffets. The exceptional leadership of suffet generals like Hannibal Barca have become legendary, handing Rome the greatest defeats it had ever suffered.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_CARTHAGE_GENERAL">
			<Text>Punic Commander</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_CARTHAGE_GENERAL_HELP">
			<Text>Unit turns into Great Admiral [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Embark[ENDCOLOR]. [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]From the beginning of the turn to its end[ENDCOLOR], Friendly Units stacked or adjacent to the Suffet gain [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Plague Immunity[ENDCOLOR] and [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]ignore Zone of Control[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_CARTHAGE_ADMIRAL">
			<Text>Punic Commander</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_CARTHAGE_ADMIRAL_HELP">
			<Text>Unit turns into Great General if it [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]is standing in City[ENDCOLOR]. [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]From the beginning of the turn to its end[ENDCOLOR], Friendly Units stacked or adjacent to the Suffet gain [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Plague Immunity[ENDCOLOR] and [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]ignore Zone of Control[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_CARTHAGE_ZOC">
			<Text>Cannae and Drepana</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_CARTHAGE_ZOC_HELP">
			<Text>Unit has [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Plague Immunity[ENDCOLOR] and [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]ignores Zone of Control[ENDCOLOR] for 1 turn.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Unique Names-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_1">
			<Text>Bomilcar</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_2">
			<Text>Hamilcar Barca</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_3">
			<Text>Hannibal</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_4">
			<Text>Hannibal Barca</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_5">
			<Text>Hasdrubal II</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_6">
			<Text>Hasdrubal Gisco</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_7">
			<Text>Hasdrubal the Boetharch</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_8">
			<Text>Mago I Justin</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_9">
			<Text>Mago II</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_10">
			<Text>Mago III</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_11">
			<Text>Himilco I</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_12">
			<Text>Himilco II</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_13">
			<Text>Hasdrubal the Fair</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_14">
			<Text>Ad Herbal</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_15">
			<Text>Carthalo</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_16">
			<Text>Hannibal Monomachus</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_17">
			<Text>Maharbal</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_18">
			<Text>Sophonisba</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_19">
			<Text>Hannibal the Rhodian</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_20">
			<Text>Hanno the Elder</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_21">
			<Text>Hanno the Great</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_22">
			<Text>Aderbaal</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_23">
			<Text>Bodashtart</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_24">
			<Text>Philosir</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_25">
			<Text>Abdmelqart</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Suffet -->
		<!-- Created by pineappledan -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET">
			<Text>Shofet</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_HELP">
			<Text>This Israelite unique Great Person replaces the Great General. Aside from the ability to boost nearby troops and construct citadels, this unit generates +2 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and [ICON_PEACE] Faith every turn.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Deals damage every turn to enemy cities the Shofet is adjacent to. Damage is doubled if the city is [ICON_BLOCKADED] Blockaded</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Shofet is the unique Great General replacement for Israel. The Shofet is very effective at shortening sieges, dealing consistent damage each turn if adjacent to an enemy city. Shoftim also act as a steady supply of Faith and Culture for your Empire, so don't feel the need to build citadels with them right away.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_TEXT">
			<Text>The Judges of Israel, or Shoftim, were Israelite military leaders in times of crisis, before Israel established their monarchy. The Book of Judges in the Hebrew Bible describes the Shofet as part of a cyclical pattern: The Israelite people fall away from their god, hardship is brought on as punishment from God, the Israelites cry out to the Lord for rescue, God sends a Shofet to lead the Israelites to overthrow their persecutors, and the cycle repeats. The cycle of Judges is thought to have gone on for between 300 and 500 years.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The first judge of Israel named by the Bible was Moses, who is said to have led the Israelites out of bondage in Egypt and established the Jewish law. After Moses, Joshua led the Israelites in the conquest of Canaan. The final judge named in the Bible was Samuel, who anointed both the first and second kings of the new Kingdom of Israel.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_SHOPHET">
			<Text>Judge of Israel</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_SHOPHET_HELP">
			<Text>+2 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and +2 [ICON_PEACE] Faith every turn.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_SHOFAR">
			<Text>Shofar</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_SHOFAR_HELP">
			<Text>Deals 20 Damage to adjacent enemy City every turn. Effect is doubled if enemy City is [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Blockaded[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Unique Names-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_1">
			<Text>Joshua</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_2">
			<Text>Othniel</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_3">
			<Text>Ehud</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_4">
			<Text>Shamgar</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_5">
			<Text>Deborah</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_6">
			<Text>Gideon</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_7">
			<Text>Abimelech</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_8">
			<Text>Tola</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_9">
			<Text>Jair</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_10">
			<Text>Jephthah</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_11">
			<Text>Ibzan</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_12">
			<Text>Elon</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_13">
			<Text>Abdon</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_14">
			<Text>Samson</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_15">
			<Text>Eli</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_16">
			<Text>Samuel</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_17">
			<Text>Moses</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_18">
			<Text>Joel</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_19">
			<Text>Abadiah</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_20">
			<Text>Amariah</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_21">
			<Text>Zebediah</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_22">
			<Text>Barak</Text>
		</Row>	
		<!-- Shotelai -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 12/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ETHIOPIA_MAIM_0">
			<Text>Maim</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ETHIOPIA_MAIM_0_HELP">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]After Attack[ENDCOLOR] Defending Enemy Unit is marked. Marked unit has reduced [ICON_ARROW_RIGHT] Movement [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]next turn[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ETHIOPIA_MAIM_1">
			<Text>Maimed</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ETHIOPIA_MAIM_1_HELP">
			<Text>-2 [ICON_ARROW_RIGHT] Movement.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ETHIOPIA_HOOKED_WEAPON">
			<Text>Hooked Weapon</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ETHIOPIA_HOOKED_WEAPON_HELP">
			<Text>+25% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength vs [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Mounted Units[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ETHIOPIA_SHOTELAI">
			<Text>Shotelai</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ETHIOPIA_SHOTELAI_HELP">
			<Text>Front-line Medieval Era land Unit. Only Ethiopia may build it. It is stronger against Mounted Units, unlike the Longswordsman it replaces. Enemies attacked by this Unit have -2 [ICON_MOVES] Movement Points on their next turn.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ETHIOPIA_SHOTELAI_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique replacement for the Longswordsman. This unit specializes in combating Mounted opponents and hobbling retreating units. Only Ethiopia may build it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ETHIOPIA_SHOTELAI_TEXT">
			<Text>Shotel are dramatically curved double-edged swords used exclusively by the ancient Ethiopian Empire’s Shotelai warriors. Almost semicircular, the shotel could be used to hook shields, or even reach around them to strike an opponent. The sword could also be used to hook and unhorse a mounted soldier, bringing them to the ground. Elite corps of Shotelai were employed by the armies of Amda Seyon I, comprising an elite force within his mighty host.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Slaganz -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GERMANY_SLAGANZ">
			<Text>Ulfhedinn</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GERMANY_SLAGANZ_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The strength and ferocity of the tribal Germanic warriors was legendary among Roman writers and soldiers alike. Of particular note were the Ulfhedinn, Odin's sacred warriors who clothed themselves in wolf pelts and imitated wolves while fighting. Germanic tribesmen stood an average of 6 inches taller than a Latini, but were often overmatched by the Legions' superior equipment, organization, and training. German fortunes would change, however, under the leadership of Arminius.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] 
				A Cherusci commander who had spent time training under the Romans, Arminius organized a coalition of five German tribes to strike back at the Roman invaders under Publius Varus. The Germans falsified reports of a northern Germanic uprising and laid an ambush for Varus deep in the Teutoburg Forest. Using their superior numbers, heavy rain, and Arminius' knowledge of Roman tactics, the Roman’s defeat at Teutoburg Forest was thorough, with 20 000 dead or enslaved after the German onslaught. Rome's total defeat at Teutoberg halted their expansion permanently, and would be remembered as Rome’s greatest humiliation.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GERMANY_SLAGANZ_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Ulfhedinn is the unique Warrior replacement which only the Germans can train. It is much cheaper than the Warrior and gains an attack bonus against Barbarian Units. When a barbarian unit is defeated, the Ulfhedinn has a chance to convert the unit to your side. Converting barbarian units also increases your influence with the nearest city-state. Use Slaganz to hunt down barbarians and form a strong coalition of early city-state allies.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GERMANY_SLAGANZ_HELP">
			<Text>Cheap early-game warrior. Only Germany may build it. Much stronger against Barbarians, and has a chance of converting defeated Barbarian Units. Starts with [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Barbarian Alliance[ENDCOLOR] Promotion, allowing him to create faster Alliances with City-States.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_GERMANY_FUROR_TEUTONICUS">
			<Text>Furor Teutonicus</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_GERMANY_FUROR_TEUTONICUS_HELP">
			<Text>+50% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength vs [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Barbarians[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_GERMANY_BARBARIAN_ALLIANCE">
			<Text>Druhtiz</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_GERMANY_BARBARIAN_ALLIANCE_HELP">
			<Text>Unit [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]can convert Barbarian Unit[ENDCOLOR] to your side [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Kill[ENDCOLOR]. +5 [ICON_INFLUENCE] Influence to the nearest City-State [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Conversion[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Sofa -->		
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SONGHAI_HORSE_FATHER">
			<Text>Father of the Horse</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SONGHAI_HORSE_FATHER_HELP">
			<Text>+15% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]to all Friendly Mounted Units within 2 tiles[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SONGHAI_HORSE_FATHER_EFFECT">
			<Text>Nearby Sofa</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SONGHAI_HORSE_FATHER_EFFECT_HELP">
			<Text>+15% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]from Sofa[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SONGHAI_SOFA">
			<Text>Sofa</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SONGHAI_SOFA_HELP">
			<Text>Ranged Unit excelling at supporting your cavalry. Only the Songhai may build it. Cheaper and available earlier than the Crossbowman, and all mounted units within two tiles receive a [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat boost. Starts with the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Medic I[ENDCOLOR] Promotion.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SONGHAI_SOFA_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Sofa is a Songhai unique unit, replacing the Crossbowman. It serves as an excellent support unit starting with the Medic I promotion and a 15% Damage increase to all Mounted units within 2 tiles. The Sofa has lower offensive strength, but is relatively cheap to train and available earlier.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SONGHAI_SOFA_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Sofa is a Mandinka term for slave soldiers who served in the army of the various Empires of West Africa. Originally, the Sofas were horse grooms of the soldier-nobility, the Farari, but their role slowly changed to become skirmishers and soldiers in their own right. Sofas were recruited from "jonow" (slaves) captured in battle or bought from afar. The institution of slavery in the Mali and Songhai Empires heavily rewarded loyalty, and jonow could rise to civil or military positions of prominence. Jonow became part of their master's clan, and were often freed after a certain amount of years.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Sofas were equipped with two quivers, and their bow was small by European standards, so sofas employed deadly poisons and fired in arcs to give their arrows strength.
			</Text>
		</Row>		
		
		<!-- SPAD -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 11/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_FRANCE_SPAD">
			<Text>SPAD S.VII</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_FRANCE_SPAD_HELP">
			<Text>Potent Modern Era flying Unit. Only France may build it. Has a longer range and is slightly weaker than the Triplane it replaces. Starts with the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Air Logistics[ENDCOLOR] Promotion. Requires [ICON_RES_OIL] Oil.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_FRANCE_SPAD_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The SPAD S.VII is France's early air superiority fighter. These fighters will help create a strong French presence in the air with their ability to attack twice in a turn.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_FRANCE_SPAD_TEXT">
			<Text>
				World War I saw rapid technological and tactical changes in how wars were fought, including the adoption of aircraft for scouting and bombing. These machines opened an entirely new theatre of war. Despite their promise, the first aircrafts were slow, clumsy, and unreliable due to their underpowered combustion engines. This all changed in 1915 when Marc Birgikt invented a new V8 engine boasting 150 horsepower and weighing only 330 pounds. The French high command saw the new motor's value as an aircraft engine and commissioned a new fighter aircraft: The Société Pour L'Aviation et ses Dérivés, or "SPAD" S. VII.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				By late 1916, SPAD VIIs were beginning to see action, and were widely adopted by allied pilots for the rest of the war. Though lacking the maneuverability of older Nieuport fighters, the SPAD VII was unmatched in sheer speed, travelling in excess of 127mph and capable of diving at more than 249mph. Pilots created entirely new tactics to leverage this speed, which gave the SPAD the ability to safely avoid pitched battles. The added stability in diving was especially appreciated over the old Nieuports, which had a bad habit of shedding their wings during maneuvers.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Air superiority became a constant arms race against newer and better German designs and engines. By the end of the war, the SPAD VII's single .303 Vickers machine gun was outmatched by German fighters, which carried at least two machine guns. The heavier and faster SPAD XIII eventually replaced the SPAD VII by late 1917, and saw France through the remainder of the War. Despite its shortcomings, the SPAD series is remembered as one of the fastest and most powerful of WWI fighters.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Standschützen -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AUSTRIA_STANDSCHUTZEN">
			<Text>Schützenstand</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AUSTRIA_STANDSCHUTZEN_TEXT">
			<Text>The Schützenstand were originally rifle guilds and rifle companies that had been formed in the 15th and 16th centuries and were regularly involved in military operations within the borders of the Austrian county of Tyrol. A Standschütze was a member of a Schützenstand ("shooting club"), into which he was enrolled, which automatically committed him to the voluntary military protection of the state of Tyrol (and Vorarlberg). In effect this made Standschützen a Tyrolean local militia and home guard.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AUSTRIA_STANDSCHUTZEN_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Schützenstand is an Austrian unique building, replacing the Arsenal. It is cheaper than the Arsenal and provides more defense. Increases the City's [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Ranged Strike Range by 1, and also allows the City to Ranged Strike indirectly, ignoring Line of Sight. It allows for faster construction of land military units in the city. It also provides +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture per city-state ally.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AUSTRIA_STANDSCHUTZEN_HELP">
			<Text>City must have a Castle. Military Units supplied by this City's population increased by 25%. Increases the City's [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Ranged Strike Range by 1, and allows Indirect Fire.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Garrisoned units receive an additional 10 Health when healing in this city. Foreign Spies cannot steal [ICON_RESEARCH] Science from this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture for each City-State Ally. +30% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and 15 XP for Gunpowder Units, and +15% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production to all other Land Military Units.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Empire [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Needs Modifier is reduced by 5% in this City.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Steam Mill -->
		<!-- Created by Gazebo -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_STEAM_MILL">
			<Text>Steam Mill</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_STEAM_MILL_TEXT">
			<Text>Stationary steam engines are fixed steam engines used for pumping or driving mills and factories, and for power generation. They are distinct from locomotive engines used on railways, traction engines for heavy steam haulage on roads, steam cars (and other motor vehicles), agricultural engines used for ploughing or threshing, marine engines, and the steam turbines used as the mechanism of power generation for most nuclear power plants. They were introduced during the 18th century and widely made for the whole of the 19th century and most of the first half of the 20th century, only declining as electricity supply and the internal combustion engine became more widespread.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_STEAM_MILL_HELP">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for every 2 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens in the City. +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for every Steam Mill on Empire. Manufactories worked by the City gain +4 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]2 Specialists in this City no longer produce [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Unhappiness from Urbanization.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]When you complete a building from the Industrial Era or later, gain 10% of its construction cost as Points towards a [ICON_GREAT_ENGINEER] Great Engineer.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production to Engineer Specialists.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_COAL] Coal: +3 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_STEAM_MILL_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique English replacement for the Factory. The Steam Mill is cheaper, requires no [ICON_RES_COAL] Coal, is available earlier than the Factory, and provides additional Production to [ICON_RES_COAL] Coal worked by the City. The Steam Mill also provides [ICON_GREAT_ENGINEER] Great Engineer points when constructing buildings, while increasing the [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production of engineer specialists. Since Steam Mills do not require Coal, you can use your Coal surplus to build Seaports and ironclads, or you can trade it away for a large amount of gold.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Qullqa & Coca -->	
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INCA_QULLQA">
			<Text>Qullqa</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INCA_QULLQA_HELP">
			<Text>Units stationed in this city heal [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]5 HP[ENDCOLOR] every turn, regardless of any actions taken. City Receives a [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Free[ENDCOLOR] [ICON_RES_COCA] Coca Luxury Resource and 25 [ICON_FOOD] Food on Construction.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]15% of [ICON_FOOD] Food is carried over after a new [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen is born.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Allows [ICON_FOOD] Food to be moved from this city along trade routes inside your civilization.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_WHEAT] Wheat: +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_BANANA] Bananas: +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_DEER] Deer: +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_BISON] Bison: +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INCA_QULLQA_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Qullqa is the unique Granary replacement for the Inca. In addition to the normal bonuses of a Granary, the Qullqa heals your garrisoned units every turn. On construction, a [ICON_RES_COCA] Coca Luxury Resource appears beneath the city. [ICON_RES_COCA] Coca replaces any existing resource that was below the city previously.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Coca increases the speed of constructing improvements, but also makes mountains passable to any civilization which controls it. Guard your Qullqa, so that other civilizations cannot follow your troops into the mountains.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INCA_QULLQA_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Qullqa were storage silos located along roadsides near cities and political centers across the Tawantinsuyu. The vast network of Qullqa stored food and supplies for the military. Maintaining and stocking the Qullqa system fell to local lords who resided in military resupplying stations called Tambo, each located within a day's march of the next. This system relieved soldiers from the need to forage, but required constant maintenance from the local populace.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Royal Qullqa stored the luxury and ceremonial goods of the Incan nobility, including feathers, precious stones, and Coca leaves. Coca production was jealously guarded as an imperial monopoly; cultivation and distribution of coca was strictly under the control of the nobles and a few favored classes.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_COCA">
			<Text>Coca</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_COCA_TEXT">
			<Text>Coca is the leaf of any of four cultivated species of the family Erythroxylaceae native to western South America. The plant is famous for its various medicinal and nutritional uses, increasing alertness, dulling pain, supressing appetite, and treating altitude sickness. The leaves are traditionally chewed or brewed into a tea. Coca made an impression on the Spanish conquerors for its ability to help people work harder, even through exhaustion or hunger.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Today, coca is best known for its psychoactive alkaloid, cocaine. The alkaloid content of coca leaves is relatively low, requiring a large number of leaves for a single batch of cocaine. Coca leaf extract began being used in Coca-Cola products in 1885, but cocaine was completely eliminated from the products around 1903.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_MONOPOLY_COCA">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Monopoly Bonus: [ENDCOLOR]Grants [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Coca Leaves[ENDCOLOR] Promotion to all Units.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_INCA_COCA">
			<Text>Coca Leaves</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_INCA_COCA_HELP">
			<Text>Unit [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]can cross Mountains[ENDCOLOR]. +15% [ICON_WORKER] Work Rate.</Text>
		</Row>
			
		<!-- Tarkhan -->		
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_HUNS_HORSE_ARCHER">
			<Text>Last Chance</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_HUNS_HORSE_ARCHER_HELP">
			<Text>Unit Attacks a valid target automatically [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]if spent all [ICON_ARROW_RIGHT] Movement Points without Attacking[ENDCOlOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_HUNS_MIGRATION">
			<Text>Migration</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_HUNS_MIGRATION_HELP">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_ARROW_RIGHT] Movement Point to Workers and Settlers [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]that begin the turn stacked with this unit[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_HUNS_SACKER">
			<Text>Bellum Alet</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_HUNS_SACKER_HELP">
			<Text>20 HP to all adjacent Friendly Units [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Pillage[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HUNS_TARKHAN">
			<Text>Tarkhan</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HUNS_TARKHAN_HELP">
			<Text>Mounted warrior who supports Civilian and other Land Military Units with its unique abilities. Only the Huns may build it. Slightly cheaper than the Horseman it replaces. +1 Movement to [ICON_TEAM_1] Settlers and [ICON_WORKER] Workers that begin the turn stacked with this Unit and +20 HP to all adjacent friendly units whenever this unit pillages a tile.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HUNS_TARKHAN_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Tarkhan is the Hunnic unique replacement for the Horseman. Slightly cheaper than the Horseman, the Tarkhan can help to quickly spread your empire by increasing the movement of Settlers and Workers. Pillaging tiles with a Tarkhan heals all your adjacent units, which can be handy for healing a recently captured unit.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HUNS_TARKHAN_TEXT">
			<Text>Tarkhan were nobles and high-ranking commanders within the armies of the Xiongnu and Hunnic empires. The term spread throughout the languages and peoples of the steppes, appearing as a title within Turkic, Mongol and Iranian cultures, even becoming a common boys name. Analogous to modern day generals, the Tarkhan were the protectors and conquerors of the Hunnic empire, spurring their civilization forward to greatness.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Tersane -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 1/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_OTTOMANS_TERSANE">
			<Text>Tersane</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_OTTOMANS_TERSANE_HELP">
			<Text>When a Sea Trade Route originating here and targeting another Civilization is completed, receive a [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism boost with the Civilization based on your recent [ICON_CULTURE] Culture output.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+50% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production towards Cargo Ships and +30% [ICON_PRODUCTION] towards Naval Melee Units. Naval Melee Units trained in this City receive the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Prize Ships[ENDCOLOR] Promotion.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_FOOD] Food from Coast and Ocean Tiles, +2 [ICON_FOOD] Food and +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production from Sea Resources worked by this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must be on the coast.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_OTTOMANS_TERSANE_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Tersane is the unique Harbor replacement of the Ottomans. In addition to the bonuses of a Harbor, the Tersane increases the yields of work boats. The building also greatly improves production towards trade and military vessels, greatly improving the Ottoman's naval capabilities. All Melee Ships built in this city also receive the Prize Ships promotion, allowing them to capture defeated enemy units.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_OTTOMANS_TERSANE_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The Turkish word 'Tersane' is derived from the Venetian 'darsane', from which the English word 'arsenal' is also derived. Though never at the forefront of shipbuilding technology, the Ottomans enjoyed over a century of naval dominance in the Mediterranean following their conquest of Constantinople in 1453. The largest Tersane, constructed at the Golden Horn across from Constantinople, housed over 160 docks, drydocks, storehouses and supply depots, making it one of the largest centers of commerce and industry in the Mediterranean[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Ottoman naval power was maintained through its tremendous shipbuilding capacity and its allegiances to the Barbary corsairs of North Africa. This pre-eminence was finally ended at the battle of Lepanto, where a combined Spanish and Venetian armada delivered a crushing defeat to the Ottomans, capturing or destroying more than two thirds of the Ottoman navy. In response, the Ottomans built 250 new vessels within six months.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				"You come to see how we bear our misfortune. But I would have you know the difference between your loss and ours. In wresting Cyprus from you, we deprived you of an arm; in defeating our fleet, you have only shaved our beard."[NEWLINE] Grand Vizier Mehmed Sokullu, on the defeat at Lepanto, and the capture of Cyprus, which the Ottomans had taken earlier the same year
			</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Teutonic Order -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GERMANY_TEUTONIC_ORDER">
			<Text>Teutonic Order</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GERMANY_TEUTONIC_ORDER_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The Order of Brothers of the German House of Saint Mary in Jerusalem, more commonly known as the Teutonic Order, is a Catholic knightly order christened in 1190 in Acre, Jerusalem. Originally founded as an adjunct of the Knights Hospitaller, the Order was tasked with establishing hospitals and helping Germanic pilgrims on their way to the Holy Land. Within 50 years, the German Catholic order became a state unto itself, prosecuting a holy crusade against Baltic pagans from their capital in present day Malbork, Poland.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] 
				After Christian forces were expelled from Jerusalem, the Teutonic knights found work as mercenaries and guardsmen in Transylvania, Hungary, and then Poland, before becoming the largest player in a new Prussian Crusade against the pagan inhabitants of the Eastern Baltics. The Teutonic Order carried out a bloody, centuries-long campaign of forced conversions and ethnic replacement that brought them into conflict with Estonians, Lithuanians, Old Prussians and their former Polish allies. Resistance to forced Christianization by Catholic knights would shape the national identities of all these neighboring peoples.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				The adoption of Christianity in Lithuania along with Poland's attempts to politically isolate the Teutonic Order from the rest of Catholicism left the Order without a purpose (and a shortage of friends) by 1520. In response, the Grand Master of the Order, Albert of Brandenburg, resigned from the Order, converted to Lutheranism, and styled himself Duke of Prussia. With the consent of the Order, Albert converted their land holdings into a secularized fiefdom, making Prussia the first Protestant state. Though declining in political force, the Teutonic Order continued to exist as a Catholic state through its holdings in Germania until forcibly dissolved by Napoleon Bonaparte in 1809. The Teutonic Order eventually reformed and still exists today as a ceremonial and charitable organization.  
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GERMANY_TEUTONIC_ORDER_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Teutonic Order is Germany's unique wonder, replacing the Heroic Epic. This wonder provides strong bonuses to all cities in your empire with a Barracks comparable to that of a full Order. All new units trained in any city with a Barracks receive the Morale promotion for free.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]With this wonder, Germany is able to found and reform much more easilly and quickly than other civilizations.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GERMANY_TEUTONIC_ORDER_HELP">
			<Text>
				Does not require a Barracks. Grants a [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Free[ENDCOLOR] Barracks in the City. A [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Free[ENDCOLOR] Great Writer appears near the city. Contains 1 slot for a [ICON_GREAT_WORK] Great Work of Writing.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]All Castles gain +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and all Barracks in the Empire gain +2 [ICON_PEACE] Faith, +3 [ICON_STRENGTH] Defense, and +50 HP. Units trained in a City with a Barracks gain the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Morale[ENDCOLOR] Promotion.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]15 [ICON_PEACE] Faith whenever you kill an enemy Unit, scaling with Era. Enables you to select a Reformation Belief at 5% below its normal Global [ICON_RELIGION] Follower requirement (20% on Standard).
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production Cost and [ICON_CITIZEN] Population Requirements increase based on the number of Cities you own.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Tophet -->
		<!-- Created by pineappledan -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CARTHAGE_TOPHET">
			<Text>Tophet</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CARTHAGE_TOPHET_HELP">
			<Text>Gain +20 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture in the City whenever a Unit is purchased, scaling with Era. Units purchased in this City receive additional experience.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CARTHAGE_TOPHET_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Tophet is the unique Shrine replacement for Carthage. In addition to the normal bonuses of a Shrine, the Tophet provides Culture whenever a unit is purchased in the City. Military Units purchased in a City with a Tophet gain +5XP at normal speed, giving them a small boost before barracks, and mitigating the experience penalty on purchased units slightly.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CARTHAGE_TOPHET_TEXT">
			<Text>"Tophet" is a Hebrew term for a place of worship and human sacrifice to the Canaanite gods, and has become a colorful synonym for hell within Judeo-Christian theology. Usually located outside cities, Tophets were holy places where sacrifices to the gods could be presented to the heads of the Phoenician pantheon, Ba'al Hammon and his consort, Tanit.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Regular sacrifices were made to ensure the prosperity of Carthage and the ashes of burnt offerings were sealed within the Tophet. Child sacrifice, once prevalent throughout the Near-East, was a persistent hallmark of Carthaginian religious life long after contemporary cultures had shunned the practice. Modern archaeological evidence suggests children were sacrificed in times of great stress such as wars, plagues, and natural disasters as an act of divine supplication.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- University of Coimbra -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PORTUGAL_UNIVERSITY_OF_COIMBRA">
			<Text>University of Coimbra</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PORTUGAL_UNIVERSITY_OF_COIMBRA_TEXT">
			<Text>Opened in 1290, the University of Coimbra is one of the oldest centers of higher learning in the world, and the oldest in Portugal. The university was founded by King Dinis as the Lisbon Estudo Geral, originally with faculties of Arts, Law, Canon Law and Medicine. As the only university in Portugal for 350 years, the University of Coimbra became a focus of educational, political, and social influence in Portugal.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PORTUGAL_UNIVERSITY_OF_COIMBRA_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Universiy of Coimbra is the unique Portuguese replacement for the Oxford University. It does not require a University, and provides a free University in the city. In addition to the normal bonuses of the Oxford University, it gives all naval units the ability to gain gold from exploration, and generates Gold and Production in the city for every Feitoria built in foreign lands.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PORTUGAL_UNIVERSITY_OF_COIMBRA_HELP">
			<Text>Does not require a University in the City. Provides a [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Free[ENDCOLOR] [ICON_GREAT_SCIENTIST] Great Scientist and a University on Completion. All Universities gain +3 [ICON_GOLD] Gold. +50 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture every time you research a Technology, scaling with Era. -1 [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Unhappiness from [ICON_RESEARCH] Illiteracy.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]All Naval Units gain the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Age of Discovery[ENDCOLOR] Promotion. Whenever a Feitoria is built in City-State Territory, permanently gain +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold in the City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Contains 2 slots for [ICON_GREAT_WORK] Great Works of Writing. +3 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science when themed.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production Cost and [ICON_CITIZEN] Population Requirements increase based on the number of Cities you own.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_PORTUGAL_AGE_OF_DISCOVERY">
			<Text>Age of Discovery</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_PORTUGAL_AGE_OF_DISCOVERY_HELP">
			<Text>Gain [ICON_GOLD] Gold [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]for revealing new areas[ENDCOLOR] on the map.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Waag -->
		<!-- Created by De_Genius on 17/11/2017, incorporated and modified by adan_eslavo 13/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NETHERLANDS_WAAG">
			<Text>Waag</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NETHERLANDS_WAAG_HELP">
			<Text>Available earlier. Requires a Market in City.[NEWLINE]Reduces Enemy [ICON_SPY] Spy Stealing Rate by 20%. -1 [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Unhappiness from [ICON_GOLD] Poverty. When you spend [ICON_GOLD] Gold to purchase Units or invest in Buildings in this City, 15% of the cost is converted into [ICON_RESEARCH] Science.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Caravansaries and Customs Houses in the City gain +3 [ICON_GOLD] Gold. +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold, [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, and [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production in this City for every Global Monopoly on Empire.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_GOLD] Gold: +3 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_SILVER] Silver: +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold, +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_GEMS] Gems: +2 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NETHERLANDS_WAAG_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Waag is the Netherlands' unique replacement for the Bank. In addition to the normal bonuses of a Bank, the Waag comes earlier and provides bonuses to Defense and Production. The Waag's bonuses scale with the total number of global monopolies, both luxury and strategic that the Dutch control. Trade and conquer vigorously to leverage your Waag's potential strengths.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NETHERLANDS_WAAG_TEXT">
			<Text>A Waag ("weigh house") was a public building in which goods were weighed for market. Prior to international standards of weights and measures, the Waags performed an indispensable service in preventing the fraudulent sale of goods. Waags were operated by local authorities who would also use them for the levying of taxes on goods transported through or sold within the city. This necessitated weigh houses be near a market square or town centre.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Of particular note is the Amsterdam Waag, built in the 15th-century on Nieuwmarkt square in Amsterdam. A number of guilds were housed on the top floors of the building: the blacksmiths' guild, the painter's guild, the masons' guild and the surgeons' guild, each with its own entrance gate. In 1632 Rembrandt van Rijn was commissioned to paint the surgeons at work; the resulting painting, ‘The Anatomy Lesson of Dr. Nicolaes Tulp’, made his reputation.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Wat -->		
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_THEMING_BONUS_WAT">
			<Text>Collection of {2_CivAdjective} Suttas</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WAT_THEMING_BONUS_HELP">
			<Text>To maximize your bonus, make sure all slots are filled with Writing from the Same Era and Civilization.</Text>
		</Row>		

		<!-- Xiafan Guanjun -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CHINA_XIAFAN_GUANJUN">
			<Text>Xiafan Guanjun</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CHINA_XIAFAN_GUANJUN_HELP">
			<Text>Sturdy Renaissance Era Naval Ranged Unit. Only China may build it. Generates [ICON_INFLUENCE] Influence every turn when stationed in a City-State's borders. Has the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Broadside[ENDCOLOR] Promotion for free.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CHINA_XIAFAN_GUANJUN_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Xiafan Guanjun is a Chinese unique unit. It is much sturdier than the Frigate it replaces, and is available earlier. You can use your Xiafan Guanjun to passively bring city-states under your sway, or take advantage of its bonus against cities and dominate coastal empires.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CHINA_XIAFAN_GUANJUN_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The Xiafan Guanjun (lit. "The Foreign Expeditionary Armada") was the great treasure fleet of the Ming Dynasty. At the behest of Emperor Zhu Di, the legendary admiral Zheng He headed seven voyages between 1405 and 1433 AD. The Xiafan Guanjun ranged as far as the Arabian Peninsula in their task of projecting Chinese influence abroad, bringing many smaller nations under the suzerainty of China.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				The Xiafan Guanjun had some of the largest wooden ships ever constructed, some measuring up to 416 feet in length. It would be another century before European ships could match the size and power of China’s fleet, making them the undisputed naval superpower of the 15th century. Despite their superiority, Zheng He’s voyages were primarily diplomatic, bringing envoys and even kings before the emperor to present tribute and perform the 'kowtow', a ritual act of reverence and subservience.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				"As an engine for carrying man and his commerce upon the high and stormy seas as well as on the vast inland waterways, it is doubtful if any class of vessel… is more suited or better adapted to its purpose than the Chinese or Indian junk, and it is certain that for flatness of sail and handiness, the Chinese rig is unsurpassed."[NEWLINE]-H. Warington Smyth
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_CHINA_KOWTOW">
			<Text>Kowtow</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_CHINA_KOWTOW_HELP">
			<Text>+2 [ICON_INFLUENCE] Influence per turn [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]inside City-State Territory[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost-->

		<!-- Yamato -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_JAPAN_YAMATO">
			<Text>Yamato</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_JAPAN_YAMATO_HELP">
		<Text>Powerful Naval Ranged Unit. Only Japan may build it. Has more range, power and higher defense than the Battleship it replaces. Earns [ICON_GREAT_ADMIRAL] Great Admiral Points on kills.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Receive +600 [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age Points whenever a Yamato is constructed.[NEWLINE]Enemies receive +400 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and +400 [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age Points whenever they destroy a Yamato.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_JAPAN_YAMATO_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Yamato is the unique Battleship replacement for Japan which is significantly more powerful. It has increased range, attack, strength, defense against attack and earns Great Admiral Points on kills. Use them to dominate the seas in the end game, giving you the edge for a Domination Victory.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
			Each Yamato gives points towards a Golden Age when constructed, but sinking a Yamato rewards enemies with Golden Age points and Culture, so don't leave your Yamatos without an escort.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_JAPAN_YAMATO_TEXT">
			<Text>The Yamato-class battleships were the crown jewel of the Imperial Japanese Navy during World War II. Displacing 73,000 tonnes at full load, the vessels were the heaviest and most powerfully armed battleships ever constructed. Each Yamato carried nine 18.1 inch guns, the largest naval artillery ever fitted to a warship, each capable of firing 3,000 lb. shells over 26 miles. Two battleships of the class, Yamato and Musashi, were completed while a third, Shinano, was converted to an aircraft carrier during construction. All were sunk by American forces during WWII.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Due to their size, speed, and power, The Yamato-class visibly embodied Japan's determination and readiness to defend its interests against the western powers, especially the United States. One of the reasons that the warship may have such significance in Japanese culture is that the word "Yamato" was often used as a poetic name for Japan itself. Thus, the construction and destruction of the Yamato battleships became symbolic for the rise and fall of Japanese imperial aspirations.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_JAPAN_YAMATO">
			<Text>Taikan Kyohosyugi</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_JAPAN_YAMATO_HELP">
			<Text>Unit gains [ICON_GREAT_ADMIRAL] Great Admiral Points [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Kill[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Yassa Court -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 29/10/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MONGOLIA_YASSA_COURT">
			<Text>Yassa Court</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MONGOLIA_YASSA_COURT_HELP">
			<Text>Automatically constructed in all [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Unoccupied Cities[ENDCOLOR] after discovering Philosophy.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Eliminates [ICON_OCCUPIED] Extra Unhappiness from an Occupied City. +20% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production towards Ranged, Siege, Mounted and Armor Military Units. +10 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science, [ICON_CULTURE]Culture, and [ICON_GOLD] Gold for every Yassa Court on Empire whenever you Conquer a City, scaling with Era.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Illiteracy, Boredom, and Empire [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Needs Modifier is reduced by 1% in all Cities. Building cost is slightly increased with number of Cities.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MONGOLIA_YASSA_COURT_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique Mongolian replacement for the Courthouse. Is automatically built in non-occupied Cities. In addition to eliminating Unhappiness in Occupied Cities, this building reduces global unhappiness from Illiteracy and Boredom, and increases production of all Land-based military units, except Unmounted Melee. Conquering Cities triggers a small amount of Gold, Science and Culture in every city. It is also slightly cheaper than the Courthouse.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MONGOLIA_YASSA_COURT_TEXT">
			<Text>Yassa was a secret written code of law created by Genghis Khan. The word Yassa translates into "order" or "decree". It was the de facto law of the Mongol Empire even though the "law" was never actually made public. The Yassa seems to have originated from decrees issued in war time, and was later codified and expanded to include cultural and life-style conventions. By keeping the Yassa secret, the decrees could be modified and used selectively. It is believed that the Yassa was supervised by Genghis Khan himself with the help of the high judge of the Mongol Empire: His stepbrother, Shihihutag. Genghis Khan appointed his second son Chagatai (a.k.a. Chagatai Khan) to oversee the execution of the laws.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Yellow Brow -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 3/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SHOSHONE_BIG_HORSE_DANCE">
			<Text>Big Horse Dance</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SHOSHONE_BIG_HORSE_DANCE_HELP">
			<Text>Adds [ICON_STRENGTH] Defense Bonus [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Fortifying[ENDCOLOR]. Fights at full strength when damaged.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SHOSHONE_BIG_HORSE_DANCE_PERFORMED">
			<Text>Big Horse Dance Performed</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SHOSHONE_BIG_HORSE_DANCE_PERFORMED_HELP">
			<Text>Unit [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]is Fortified[ENDCOLOR]. [ICON_STRENGTH] Defense Bonus added.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SHOSHONE_YELLOW_BROW">
			<Text>Yellow Brow</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SHOSHONE_YELLOW_BROW_HELP">
			<Text>Tenacious Renaissance Era Unit. Only the Shoshone may build it. Has the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Anti-cavalry[ENDCOLOR] Promotion, fights at full strength when damaged, and has double combat bonus from fortifying.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SHOSHONE_YELLOW_BROW_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Yellow Brow is unmatched for its ability to hold ground. Never one to retreat, the Yellow brow fights at full strength regardless of health, and has double the normal bonus from fortifying. This unit is very effective against enemy cavalry</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SHOSHONE_YELLOW_BROW_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Yellow Brows (Sh. Ohamupe) were one of two military societies within the Shoshone, playing an integral role in hunting, scouting, and policing within their bands. Yellow Brow braves shaved their heads into a cockscomb 'mohawk', and painted their exposed heads yellow, hence their common English name.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				The Yellow Brows were composed of only the bravest and most daring of the young men, tasked with keeping order on hunting expeditions, scouting, and soldiering. The Society never had more than a few hundred members at a time; members elected their replacement upon graduation. A young Yellow Brow was expected to act and speak in a contrarian way as a sign of membership.  For instance, when asked if he would like to join the Yellow Brows, it was expected that the young man would say 'No' as a sign of willingness to join, or 'Yes' if he wished to decline.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				In battle, Yellow Brows were led by a war chief who carried a long cane tipped with a stone or metal dagger.  The cane was used to grab and unhorse opponents, or as a No-Retreat signal. If the enemy was gaining the upper hand, the chief would drive his staff into the ground and the braves would defend him to the last. Yellow Brows were banned from leaving their chief's side until another member of the tribe came and released the braves from their charge. Deserting the chief was met with abject mockery, and often resulted in banishment from the tribe.
			</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>
</GameData>
