<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 7/01/2018 -->
<GameData>
	<Language_en_US>
		<!-- Andelsbevægelse -->
		<!-- Created by De_Genius, modified and incorporated by adan_eslavo 10/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DENMARK_ANDELSBEVAEGELSE">
			<Text>Andelsbevægelse</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DENMARK_ANDELSBEVAEGELSE_HELP">
			<Text>+5% [ICON_FOOD] Food and +10% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production when constructing buildings in City. Unlike the Agribusiness which it replaces, it does not require horses.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_FOOD] Food on Plains tiles, and +2 [ICON_FOOD] Food, +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, and +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold from Pastures. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Only Denmark can build it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DENMARK_ANDELSBEVAEGELSE_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Andelsbevægelse is a Danish unique building which can speed up building production and can help your City grow quickly, especially when surrounded by plains and pastures.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DENMARK_ANDELSBEVAEGELSE_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The Andelsbevægelse (Danish Cooperative Movement) was a means of economical organization under leadership of consumer- or producer-controlled corporations, where each individual member owned a part of the corporation. The type of organization was popular in the farming industry and in consumer organizations in Denmark from the 1790s to the 1960s. The members of the corporations sought to share the economic stress of producing or buying goods, and divided the eventual end-year financial surplus amongst themselves. The type of ownership rules varied greatly between individual corporations, as some divided the financial risk equally, while others gave more power to the most financially involved individuals.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]After the Second War of Schleswig in 1864, two new movements hit Denmark. One was a successful attempt to reclaim moors in central and western Jutland for farming, which was mostly sandy land abandoned in the 14th century as a result of the Black Plague, but in many cases good for potatoes. This movement was initiated by Hedeselskabet (the Heath Association). Equally important was an influx of agricultural imports to Great Britain, Denmark's primary market for grains, from a rapidly industrializing United States, which caused not only a sharp drop in prices, but an agriculture crisis throughout Europe in the final decade of the 19th century. This affected the income of many Danish farmers and the result was a change in production from grain to dairy products and meat. When a farmer couldn't sell his grain, he fed it to his cows and pigs.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The change in production resulted in a need for dairies and slaughterhouses. A Danish minister visited England and studied the Rochdale system of co-operatives, which he then brought back to Denmark. The only way to pay for such massive investments was for a large group of farmers to share the cost and risk between them, thus creating the cooperative dairies and slaughterhouses. The new situation implied that farmers would buy cheap grain from Russia and feed it to their livestock, selling milk, butter, eggs and meat for a much higher price. This movement also resulted in the creation of both the Danish Bacon and Danish Lurpak Butter brands. The cooperative movement also resulted in a series of co-op stores known as Brugsen, which were under the administration of The Danish Consumers Co-operative Society. The stores kept a large share of the Danish consumer goods market. It merged with the similar retail chains in Norway and Sweden in January 2002, to form Coop Norden.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Agora -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 3/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GREECE_AGORA">
			<Text>Agora</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GREECE_AGORA_HELP">
			<Text>Unique Ancient Era building. Only the Greeks may build it. Increases [ICON_GOLD] Gold in this city for every Allied City-State. +20% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production towards Diplomatic Units in City. [ICON_INTERNATIONAL_TRADE] Trade Routes other Players make to this City will generate +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold for both the City owner and the Trade Route owner.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GREECE_AGORA_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique Market replacement for the Greeks. In addition to the normal bonuses of a Market, the Agora generates Gold for every City-State ally, and boosts the production Diplomatic Units. In addition to the normal bonuses to Spices and Sugar, the Agora also provides bonuses to Wine and Olives.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GREECE_AGORA_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The Agora was the marketplace and beating heart of the ancient Greek city-states. Originally used as meeting places for announcements and a muster point for soldiers, Agoras gradually became centers of commerce and trade. Artisans and merchants could sell their wares either in the open, or along the covered walkways which surrounded the field, known as the stoa. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Often the site of intense philosophical and political discussion, the Agora have been immortalized as the proving ground of renowned philosophers, writers, storytellers, and orators. Disciplines such as Sophism, Skepticism, Cynicism and Stoicism can trace their roots back to the politicking and squabbles of the Grecian Agora.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Armada -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 8/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SPAIN_SANTA_MARIA">
			<Text>Santa María</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SPAIN_SANTA_MARIA_HELP">
			<Text>Unit gains [ICON_CAPITAL] Great Admiral Points [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Kills[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SPAIN_INVINCIBLE">
			<Text>Invincible</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SPAIN_INVINCIBLE_HELP">
			<Text>+2 XP if unit[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]is inside Enemy Territory at full Health[ENDCOLOR]. +10% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength if [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]at full Health[ENDCOLOR]. Lost after unit upgrade.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SPAIN_INVINCIBLE_AT_FULL">
			<Text>Appearances</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SPAIN_INVINCIBLE_AT_FULL_HELP">
			<Text>+10% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength if [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]at full Health[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SPAIN_ARMADA">
			<Text>Armada</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SPAIN_ARMADA_HELP">
			<Text>Unique Renaissance Era Naval Unit. A Slow, but incredibly dangerous ship. Adept at extended sieges and engaging other ships[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Generates Great Admirals more quickly[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Only the Spanish may build it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SPAIN_ARMADA_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Armada is a powerful ship in its era. You are unlikely to chase down an enemy, but these ships can blockade cities and force an engagement. Maneuver your Armada into the borders of cities and settle in for a long siege. Your units will amass more and more experience, becoming more dangerous while they wait for a proper fight.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SPAIN_ARMADA_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The "Great and Most Fortunate Navy", the Spanish Armada, was a fleet of 130 ships constructed expressly for the invasion of England to overthrow the Reformist tyrant, Elizabeth I. The fleet was one of the largest ever seen in Europe, raised at great expense by Philip II in retribution for England's break from the Catholic Church, the perceived illegitimacy of Elizabeth I (born from Henry VIII's second marriage), Elizabeth's execution of Mary, Queen of Scots, and English support for the Dutch revolt against Spain. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Spanish ships were outnumbered, but they easily outgunned their smaller English counterparts. In the end, however, it was not firepower, but speed and maneuverability which won the day, allowing the small English vessels to harry the lumbering Spanish Juggernaut, sinking 10 ships. When finally forced to retire to Spain, a navigational error blew the Armada off-course and onto the Irish coast, where fierce storms dashed the ships against the rocks. When the Armada at last reached Spain only 67 of the original 130 ships remained, full of sickly, starving, and demoralized sailors. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				The lessons of the Spanish Armada informed naval strategy and design for the next two centuries. Cannons and ranged action had now overtaken boarding and ramming as the primary methods of attack; sinking, rather than capturing, was now the priority. With this stunning victory, England had wrested naval dominance from Spain, a lead they would maintain until the rise of the United States in WWII. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				"I sent the Armada against men, not God's winds and waves".[NEWLINE]
				-Philip II
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Baan Chang -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 6/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SIAM_BAAN_CHANG">
			<Text>Elephant Camp</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SIAM_BAAN_CHANG_HELP">
			<Text>Unique Siamese replacement for the Workshop.[NEWLINE]
				+1[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][ICON_GOLD] Gold and +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production on all Forest and +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture for all Lumber Mills and Logging Camps
				+1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production in City for every 2 Strategic Resource received as City-State gifts.  Receive 10 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture in Capital for every Baan Chang in the Empire every time a city state gifts a unit, scales with Era.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Allows [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production to be moved from this city along Trade Routes inside your civilization.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SIAM_BAAN_CHANG_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Baan Chang is the Siamese unique replacement for the Workshop. In addition to the normal bonuses of a Workshop, The Baan Chang increases Culture from lumber mills, and gives Production and Faith from Ivory. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City state gifts, both Strategic Resources and units, provide additional benefits in cities with a Baan Chang, so be sure to make strong alliances to get the most from this building.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SIAM_BAAN_CHANG_TEXT">
			<Text>Often thought of as ceremonial and military implements first, perhaps the greatest contribution of elephants to human society has been as beasts of burden. Elephants are prized as a labour force even within today's lumber camps for their ability to haul the dense teak lumber found only within Burma and Thailand. The power of a fully grown elephant is matched only by its grace, as the animals can navigate difficult and uneven terrain impassable by carts and tractors, while carrying loads far in excess of other animals. The use of elephants in logging also has had unintentional benefits to the health of forests, with their delicate command of the forest trails reducing the potential damage of logging roads.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
			The jobs of Southeast Asia's working elephants have come under threat within the past few decades with the mechanization of logging. Elephants and their mahouts have been forced to look for work in tourism and religious festivals, jobs which elephants find terribly stressful. </Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Bastu -->
		<!-- Created by pineppledan 25/11/2017, modified and incorporated by adan_eslavo 17/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SWEDEN_BASTU">
			<Text>Sauna</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SWEDEN_BASTU_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The Swedish Bad Stuga (bath cabin), or Bastu, is a small cabin designed as a bathing and dry heat spa. A stove or furnace heats the room to 75-100°C (167–212 °F) before patrons enter, where they will recline and sweat. Bastus are a social affair; places for discussion and relaxation with family and friends, but in ancient times were also places for food curing and childbirth.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Many cultures around the world have independently created their own 'sweat bath' cultures, including Aztec temazcalli, Roman thermae, Korean jjimjilbang, and the sweat lodges of many North American tribes. It is not known where or when Scandinavian sweat baths were first created, but it was well before the Christianization of Scandinavia, as evidenced by their ubiquity throughout medieval Europe. By the time written descriptions of Scandinavian sweat baths were being made, Nordic countries had created varied and distinct cultures surrounding these baths.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				The health benefits of heat baths are many and varied. Sessions have been shown to relieve cold symptoms and increase pain thresholds. They also help with rheumatic pain and fatigue, and may even reduce the risk of dementia. Prolonged use of a sauna has been linked to reduced male fertility, however, and heat baths should never be enjoyed while under the effects of alcohol.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SWEDEN_BASTU_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique Swedish replacement for the Baths. In addition to the bonuses of the Baths, the Bastu provides bonuses for lakes and tundra. Science and Culture is generated whenever a citizen is born, and extra Food is generated during Golden Ages. Unlike the Baths, the Bastu does not require a river,</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SWEDEN_BASTU_HELP">
			<Text>Golden Ages increase [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and [ICON_FOOD] Food by 10%. Gain 15% of the [ICON_RESEARCH] Science and 15% of the [ICON_CULTURE] Culture output of the City as an instant boost when a [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen is born in this City. +1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science from Lake and Tundra Tiles.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Black Tug -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 29/10/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MONGOLIA_MINGGHAN">
			<Text>Mingghan</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MONGOLIA_MINGGHAN_HELP">
			<Text>+5 XP [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Pillage[ENDCOLOR]. +20% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength if unit is standing [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Pillaged Tile[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MONGOLIA_MASSACRE">
			<Text>Massacre</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MONGOLIA_MASSACRE_HELP">
			<Text>+20% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]from Pillaged Tile[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MONGOLIA_BLACK_TUG">
			<Text>Black Tug</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MONGOLIA_BLACK_TUG_HELP">
			<Text>Aggressive and menacing Medieval Era Mounted Unit. Only the Mongols may build it. It is stronger against wounded units or while standing on pillaged tiles. Gains additional XP for pillaging.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MONGOLIA_BLACK_TUG_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Black Tug is a Mongolian unique unit, replacing the Knight. It is stronger and deals more damage to wounded units, and while standing on pillaged tiles. As mounted unit, the Black Tug is vulnerable to Pikemen.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MONGOLIA_BLACK_TUG_TEXT">
			<Text>
				A tug is a pole with circularly arranged horse or yak tail-hairs of varying colors arranged at the top. Originally a symbol of the Mongol Empire, it was later adopted in by the Turkic khanates, as well as the Ottoman Empire. It was also adopted by Slavic cavalry in the 18th century, who called the banners 'Bunchuk', and is still used by some units of the Polish military. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]

				Usage of the horse tail is symbolic because of the central importance of horses in Mongol life. A white-haired banner is used as a peacetime symbol, while the black banner was for wartime. The original white banner disappeared early in history, but the black banner survived as the repository of Genghis Khan's soul. The Mongols continued to honor the banner, building a monastery with the special mission of flying and protecting the black tug banner. However, in 1937 the black banner disappeared amidst purges of Mongol nationalists, monks, and intellectuals. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]

				The Nine White banners came into renewed significance in Mongolia after democracy was adopted in the early 1990s as a symbol of the traditional Mongolian state, replacing the previous communist flags. The modern Mongolian nine white banners are kept in the Government Palace in Ulaanbaatar; the modern Mongolian black banners are kept in the Ministry of Defense.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Barbican -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 14/10/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_POLAND_BARBICAN">
			<Text>Barbican</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_POLAND_BARBICAN_HELP">
			<Text>+33% [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Range Combat Strength [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Garrison in the City[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POLAND_BARBICAN">
			<Text>Barbican</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POLAND_BARBICAN_HELP">
			<Text>+2 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, +2 [ICON_PEACE] Faith, +2 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science and +10 [ICON_STRENGTH] Defense to the City. Reduces [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Crime.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+25 XP for all new Units trained in this city, and ranged units in the city have increased attack.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Only Polish may build it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POLAND_BARBICAN_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique Polish replacement for the Armory. Must have built Walls in the city. In addition to the normal bonuses provided by the Armory, this building provides Culture, Faith, and increased city defense. Ranged and Siege garrisoned in the city have increased attack.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POLAND_BARBICAN_TEXT">
			<Text>	
				A Barbican is a fortified outpost or archery tower, forming part of a city’s outer defense. The towers were often situated outside the main line of defenses with a clear line of fire towards the city’s gates, and connected to the city walls via a walled road called the ‘neck’. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				
				The most well-known barbican was built in Kraków in 1498-1499 during the reign of Jan Olbracht. It was inspired by two other Barbicans in Torun (1429) and Chelm (1449), and motivated by the danger posed by Encroaching Ottoman and Wallachian forces. The Warsaw barbican was erected in 1540 in place of an older gate to protect Nowomiejska Street and almost immediately became an anachronism serving no practical purpose. With the improvement in siege tactics and artillery in the 15th century, barbicans had largely lost their significance. The Warsaw barbican was used in the defense of the city only once, during the Swedish invasion of Poland in 1656, when it had to be recaptured from the Swedes by the polish army.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Ballista -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 30/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ROME_LEGATUS_LEGIONIS">
			<Text>Legatus Legionis</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ROME_LEGATUS_LEGIONIS_HELP">
			<Text>Double [ICON_ARROW_RIGHT] Movement [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Flat, but not hindering Terrain to all Roman Siege Units within 2 tiles[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ROME_LEGATUS_LEGIONIS_ON_BALLISTA">
			<Text>Legatus Legionis</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ROME_LEGATUS_LEGIONIS_ON_BALLISTA_HELP">
			<Text>Double [ICON_ARROW_RIGHT] Movement [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Flat, but not hindering Terrain if Great General is within 2 tiles[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ROME_LEGATUS_LEGIONIS_EFFECT">
			<Text>Siege Mobility</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ROME_LEGATUS_LEGIONIS_EFFECT_HELP">
			<Text>Double [ICON_ARROW_RIGHT] Movement [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Open Terrain if within 2 tiles of a Great General[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Cacadores -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PORTUGUESE_CACADORES">
			<Text>
				Cacadores
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PORTUGUESE_CACADORES_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The Cacadores were the elite light infantry of the Portuguese army in the 18th and 19th centuries. The divisions were famed for their marksmanship and their brown coats, one of the first attempts at military camouflage. After a Portugal's sound defeat and occupation by Napoleon, the English intervened on behalf of their ally to rally and reorganize a joint war to retake the country. The British general William Beresford, as part of his reforms, formed the Cacadores to fill a role analogous to the German jaeger or American ranger divisions. Under this combined military, the Cacadores helped in reclaiming Portuguese independence and distinguished themselves as the "fighting cocks" of the Portuguese army until the units were eventually dissolved in the military reforms of 1911.  
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PORTUGUESE_CACADORES_STRATEGY">
			<Text>
				The Cacador is the unique Portuguese replacement for the Gatling Gun. It gains recon promotions by leveling up, allowing it to excel in hostile terrain.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PORTUGUESE_CACADORES_HELP">
			<Text>
				Ranged unit of the Industrial era. Only Portugal may build it. Whenever it levels up, it gains a random promotion from the Trailblazer or Survivalism lines.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_CACADOR">
			<Text>
				Cacador
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_CACADOR_HELP">
			<Text>
				When this unit levels up, it gains a Trailblazer or Survivalism promotion.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Dhanurgraha -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 4/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_INDIA_EPIC">
			<Text>Epic</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_INDIA_EPIC_HELP">
			<Text>Unit gains [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and additional XP [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Kill[ENDCOLOR]. [ICON_CULTURE] Culture doubled [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Barbarian Kills[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_INDIA_DHANURVIDYA">
			<Text>Dhanurvidya</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_INDIA_DHANURVIDYA_HELP">
			<Text>Unit gains [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and [ICON_PEACE] Faith [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Promotion[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDIA_DHANURAASHI">
			<Text>Dhanurgraha</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDIA_DHANURAASHI_HELP">
			<Text>Unique Ancient Era Unit.  Only the Indians may build it. Gains additional [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and experience for every kill, and gains [ICON_PEACE] Faith and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture when levelling up. [ICON_CULTURE] Culture from kills is doubled on barbarians.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDIA_DHANURAASHI_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Dhanurgraha is a powerful defense against early barbarians which helps India maintain its cultural and religious dominance in the early game. Seek out barbarians to kill for culture and faith, then turn on your neighbours if it suits you.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDIA_DHANURAASHI_TEXT">
			<Text>Archery was the most highly revered and prized martial art of ancient India. Many of the culture heroes and gods of the Vedic texts describe archers of unparalleled skill, including Arjuna, Rama, Karna, and even Shiva, the greatest of the Hindu gods. Traditional Indian bows are described as long, even reaching the height of their users, but without the tremendous strength of the Welsh longbow.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Buffalo Pound -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 4/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SHOSHONE_BUFFALO_POUND">
			<Text>Buffalo Pound</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SHOSHONE_BUFFALO_POUND_HELP">
			<Text>Unique Shoshone replacement for the Well. [NEWLINE]Increases [ICON_FOOD] Food from nearby [ICON_RES_HORSE] Horses, [ICON_RES_SHEEP] Sheep, [ICON_RES_COW] Cattle and [ICON_RES_BISON] Bison and a [ICON_RES_BISON] Bison resource appears near the City[NEWLINE]Additional [ICON_FOOD] Food for every 4 [ICON_CITIZEN] Population in City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Can be built anywhere, including cities with a Water Mill.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SHOSHONE_BUFFALO_POUND_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Buffalo Pound is the Shoshone unique building, replacing the Well.  In addition to the normal bonuses of the Well, the Buffalo Pound provides food from Horses, Cattle, Sheep and Bison.  It can also be constructed in cities with access to fresh water, even if a Water Mill has already been built there.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SHOSHONE_BUFFALO_POUND_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Buffalo Pounds were large constructions built by many Plains Tribes for the entrapment and killing of Buffalo. Large herds of bison were corralled and funneled into the pound, a sturdy circular ring of hides and wood, where tribesmen could throw spears and other missile weapons from the safety of the walls to take the powerful beasts down. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Buffalo were a staple food source on the North American Plains, but hunting such large animals was difficult without horses or sturdy weapons. With the arrival of Europeans and the introduction of the horse and musket, hunting on the Great Plains was changed forever. Widespread adoption of the horse meant Native American tribes could travel great distances and attack bison herds with impunity. The good times would not last, however, as Europeans encroached upon this way of life. Increasingly, the Great Plains were converted into farms and pastures for American homesteaders. The American bison was driven to the brink of extinction by a combination of habitat loss, industrial-scale hunting, and culling intended to starve the indigenous population. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Today, American buffalo have recovered, but their range has been greatly limited to a few national parks. Commercial farming and sport hunting continues, but the bison are unlikely to ever return to their historical numbers.
			</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Corsair -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MOROCCAN_CORSAIR">
			<Text>
				Corsair
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MOROCCAN_CORSAIR_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The Barbary Corsairs were pirates and privateers operating off the coast of North Africa. The corsairs became infamous throughout Europe, ranging throughout the Mediterranean, and as far as Iceland, slaughtering livestock and capturing Christians for sale in the slave markets of the Islamic world. The ferocity and frequency of such raids, or "Razzia" was such that much of the coast of Italy and Spain was abandoned for fear of abduction. It is estimated that some 1.25 million people were taken as slaves by barbary pirates between 1530 and 1780 A.D.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				
				The scope of Corsair activity began to diminish in the latter part of the 17th century, as the more powerful European navies started to compel the Barbary States to cease attacking their shipping. However, the ships and coasts of Christian states continued to suffer until the early 19th century. Following the Napoleonic Wars and the Congress of Vienna in 1814, European powers agreed upon the need to suppress the Barbary corsairs entirely. Occasional incidents continued to occur, including two Barbary wars between the United States and the Barbary States, creating the impetus for the creation of the US Navy.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				"It is written in our Koran, that all nations which do not acknowledge the Prophet are sinners, whom it is the right and duty of the faithful to plunder and enslave; and that every mu'min (believer) who is slain in this warfare is sure to go to paradise."[NEWLINE]
				-Sidi Haji Abdrahaman, to Thomas Jefferson in reply to his demand for the protection of American merchant ships
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MOROCCAN_CORSAIR_STRATEGY">
			<Text>
				The Corsair is the unique Moroccan replacement for the Corvette. It specializes in raiding and pillaging maritime trade routes, earning Food and Production for each enemy unit killed and trade route plundered.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MOROCCAN_CORSAIR_HELP">
			<Text>
				Naval unit that specializes in piracy and disrupting maritime trade. Only Morocco can build it. It gains [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production from killing units, pillaging resources, and plundering trade routes.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_RAZZIA">
			<Text>
				Razzia
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_RAZZIA_HELP">
			<Text>
				Gain Food and Production in the nearest coastal city whenever you kill an enemy unit, pillage an improvement, or plunder a trade route.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Dromon -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 30/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BYZANTIUM_GREEK_FIRE">
			<Text>Greek Fire</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BYZANTIUM_GREEK_FIRE_HELP">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]After Attack[ENDCOLOR] Defending Enemy Unit is marked. [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]At the beginning of its turn[ENDCOLOR] it takes an additional 10 "fire" damage for every mark. Effect can stack up to [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]3[ENDCOLOR] times after battles with 3 different units.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BYZANTIUM_GREEK_FIRE_ON_UNIT">
			<Text>Fire</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BYZANTIUM_GREEK_FIRE_ON_UNIT_HELP">
			<Text>Unit takes an additional 10 "fire" damage [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]at the start of its turn[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BYZANTIUM_GREEK_FIRE_2_ON_UNIT">
			<Text>Huge Fire</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BYZANTIUM_GREEK_FIRE_2_ON_UNIT_HELP">
			<Text>Unit takes an additional 20 "fire" damage [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]at the start of its turn[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BYZANTIUM_GREEK_FIRE_3_ON_UNIT">
			<Text>Raging Fire</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BYZANTIUM_GREEK_FIRE_3_ON_UNIT_HELP">
			<Text>Unit takes an additional 30 "fire" damage [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]at the start of its turn[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_BYZANTIUM_DROMON">
			<Text>Dromon</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_BYZANTIUM_DROMON_HELP">
			<Text>Unique Classical Era Unit. Only the Byzantines may build it. Tougher than the Penteconter it replaces. Receives the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Splash Damage I[ENDCOLOR] Promotion for free and units struck by the Dromon take an additional 10 damage on their turn.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_BYZANTIUM_DROMON_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Bring flaming death to your enemies. Stronger than the Penteconter it replaces, and deals additional burning damage to both the target unit and any enemies near the Dromon. It cannot end its turn in Deep Ocean tiles outside of the city borders.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_BYZANTIUM_DROMON_TEXT">
			<Text>A modified form of the traditional galley, the Dromon was an integral part of the Byzantine navy throughout the empire's reign. Featuring both oar and sail power, the Dromon was highly maneuverable and agile, but also dangerously equipped for battle. Through the use of Greek Fire, a precursor to modern Napalm, the Byzantines used an early form of the flamethrower to strike fear in the hearts of any who opposed them on the sea.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Dummy City HP Building -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 30/10/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DUMMYCITYHP">
			<Text>Dummy City HP Building</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Dummy Culture Building -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 5/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DUMMYCULTURE">
			<Text>Dummy Culture Building</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Dummy Gold Building -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 5/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DUMMYGOLD">
			<Text>Dummy Gold Building</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Dummy Science Building -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 5/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DUMMYSCIENCE">
			<Text>Dummy Science Building</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Dummy GMP Building -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 31/10/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DUMMYGMP">
			<Text>Dummy GMP Building</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Dummy Faith Building -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 5/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DUMMYFAITH">
			<Text>Dummy Faith Building</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Dummy Production Building -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 24/10/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DUMMYPRODUCTION">
			<Text>Dummy Production Building</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Dummy Defense Building -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 14/01/2018 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DUMMYDEFENSE">
			<Text>Dummy Defense Building</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Dummy City GPP And Defense Building -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 13/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DUMMYGPPANDDEFENSE">
			<Text>Dummy City GPP And Defense Building</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Dummy Food Building -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 24/10/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DUMMYFOOD">
			<Text>Dummy Food Building</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Dummy Happiness Building -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 24/10/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DUMMYHAPPINESS">
			<Text>Dummy Happiness Building</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- E-temenanki -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 28/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BABYLON_ETEMENANKI">
			<Text>E-temenanki</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BABYLON_ETEMENANKI_HELP">
			<Text>Requires Monument in City.[NEWLINE]+30% [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Great Person rate in City. Receive +15% of the City's [ICON_CULTURE] Culture output in in the city as [ICON_CULTURE] Culture whenever a citizen is born, and 50 [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age Points as an instant boost whenever a policy is unlocked, scaling with Era. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Receive 15% of the City's [ICON_RESEARCH] Science and [ICON_FOOD] Food output as an instant boost in the City whenever you invest in a building. All monuments gain +1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science and all Shrines gain +2 [ICON_FOOD] Food. The [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production Cost and [ICON_CITIZEN] Population Requirements increase based on the number of cities you own.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BABYLON_ETEMENANKI_STRATEGY">
			<Text>E-temenanki is the Babylonian Unique Wonder, replacing the National Monument. In addition to the normal bonuses of a National Monument, E-temenanki awards Food and Science whenever a building is invested on empire, so invest in buildings early and often.  All monuments in empire gain +1 Science and all Shrines gain +2 Food.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BABYLON_ETEMENANKI_TEXT">
			<Text>E-temenanki was the Ziggurat of Marduk, god of storms and head of the Babylonian pantheon. Ziggurats were religious temples erected in Mesopotamian cities as the literal dwelling places of each city's patron god. The Ziggurats were constructed to replicate the high mountains, where it believed the gods originally lived, in order to make the gods feel more at home.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
			
			E-temenanki was destroyed at least twice in history, once by Sennacherib, King of Assyria, and once by Alexander the Great. Alexander had intended to level the temple in order to rebuild it on fresh foundations, but the project only got as far as the demolition before Alexander's death, and the project was immediately abandoned in the ensuing chaos.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BABYLON_ETEMENANKI_THEME">
			<Text>Treasury of Babylon</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BABYLON_ETEMENANKI_THEME_HELP">
			<Text>To maximize your bonus, make sure the Great Work Slots are all filled with Art from different Eras and different Civilizations.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Eagle -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_AZTEC_EAGLE">
			<Text>
				Eagle
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_AZTEC_EAGLE_TEXT">
			<Text>
				One of the two elite class of infantry (the other being the Jaguar Warriors) in the Aztec army, the Eagle Warriors were the bravest young men of noble birth and/or those who had taken the most prisoners in battle. Like the Jaguars, the Eagles used the atlatl, bow, spear and macuahuitl (wooden swords set with obsidian shards); unlike the Jaguars, the Eagles decorated their armor with eagle feathers and wore a headdress shaped like the head of an eagle with the beak wide open. And they had a hilltop temple in Malinalco. Upon taking 20 prisoners – intact enough to serve as human sacrifice – a young warrior was eligible to become an Eagle Warrior, no doubt making his family very proud. Until the Spanish arrived with their cannons, muskets, and horses, the Eagle and Jaguar warriors were the toughest bullies on the Mesoamerican block.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_AZTEC_EAGLE_STRATEGY">
			<Text>
				The Eagle is the unique Aztec replacement for the Swordsman. It does not require Iron to build. It has increased vision, and has a chance of capturing defeated enemy units as Workers.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_AZTEC_EAGLE_HELP">
			<Text>
				Strong, front-line land Unit of the Classical Era. Only the Aztecs may build it. It gains the Sentry promotion for free. When it defeats an enemy unit, it has a 50% chance of capturing that unit as a Worker.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_CAPTIVES_OF_WAR">
			<Text>
				Captives of War
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_CAPTIVES_OF_WAR_HELP">
			<Text>
				May capture defeated units as Workers.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Examination Hall -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VP_EXAMINATION_HALL">
			<Text>
				Examination Hall
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VP_EXAMINATION_HALL_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Perhaps the most truly unique aspect of Chinese culture - and the one with the most powerful legacy - is the Confucian examination system with which the Son of Heaven's empire was staffed with civil servants over the best part of two millennia. The Imperial examinations represented an attempt to create an aristocracy of learning, which in itself represent a remarkable advance over the warrior and hereditary aristocracies that dominated in the rest of the world. The Chinese examination system, archaic, laborious and daunting as it may have been, was nevertheless, was a glorious attempt at intellectual meritocracy.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				The Imperial Exams, or Keju, were state organized examinations for candidacy into the Chinese civil service. The examinations amounted to tests of rote memorization of the Five Confucian Classics and required direct quotations on Confucian philosophy and ethics. There were several levels of exams, each conferring differing levels of honor and privelege. A scholar who obtained the highest degree, the jinshi, would have his memory trained to a tremendous degree.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				The Imperial examinations was abolished in 1890 under pressure by Chinese citizens to reform and modernize the state. As Western universities began to move away from their own classical tradition to embrace economics, engineering and natural science, China's scholarly efforts languished in the ancient literary past. It is unsurprising that the ingenuity that produced the “Four Great Inventions” could not flourish in such a backward-looking intellectual environment.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				 “Do you know that we tried an experiment which is unique in the history of the world? We sought to rule this great country not by force, but by wisdom. And for centuries we succeeded.”[NEWLINE]
				-Anonymous Confucian Philosopher; excerpt from "On a Chinese Screen"
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VP_EXAMINATION_HALL_STRATEGY">
			<Text>
				The Examination Hall is a Chinese unique building, replacing the Chancery. In addition to the normal bonuses of a Chancery, the Exam Hall boosts Great People generation in the city, and gives random Great Person Points whenever a citizen is born.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VP_EXAMINATION_HALL_HELP">
			<Text>
				+10% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production of Diplomatic Units. Grants Promotion [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Royal Signet[ENDCOLOR] for Diplomatic Units in the city in which it is built. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold in City for every City-State Friend, and +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for every Ally.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+5% Great People rate in the city, increased to +10% during We Love the King Day.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Whenever a citizen is born, gain 15 points toward a random Great Person, scaling with era.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_ALERT_EXAMINATIONS">
			<Text>
				The birth of a citizen has earned you {1_Num} points toward a {2_Str} in {3_Str}.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Fale Tel'e -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 5/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POLYNESIA_FALE_TELE">
			<Text>Fale</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POLYNESIA_FALE_TELE_HELP">
			<Text>Unique Ancient Era building. Only the Polynesians may build it. Increases [ICON_GOLD] Gold from Work Boats. Gain [ICON_RESEARCH] Science when a [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen is born in this City, scaling with era, and gain [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, [ICON_FAITH] Faith, [ICON_GOLD] Gold and [ICON_FOOD] Food when a building is constructed in this City, scaling with era.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POLYNESIA_FALE_TELE_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique Council replacement for the Polynesians. In addition to the normal bonuses of a Council, the Fale Tele provides Gold on Improved Sea Resources and a small amount of Culture, Faith, Gold and Food whenever a building is constructed in the city. Build the Fale tele as a first priority to maximize the bonuses for all later buildings.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POLYNESIA_FALE_TELE_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Literally meaning "Big Building", the Fale Tele is typical of Samoan architecture. By decree of Tagaloa-lagi, the Samoan creator god, all dwellings were to be of circular design, in imitation of the dome of the heavens and the horizon. Fale Tele were the largest of Samoan buildings, designed to act as meeting places for chief councils as well as family gatherings, celebrations and ceremonies. Regular dwellings were constructed behind the Fale Tele, while a carefully maintained lawn spread in front as a larger gathering and social space for all villagers.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Samoan culture’s emphasis on openness is reflected in their architecture, with its circular layouts and no walls. Fales have become emblematic of wider Polynesian architecture, with small fale, or faleo'o, becoming ubiquitous on beaches throughout the Pacific.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Figs -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 25/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_ROME_FIGS">
			<Text>Figs</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_ROME_FIGS_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_ROME_FIGS_TEXT">
			<Text>Native to the Middle East and western Asia, Figs have been cultivated since ancient times, being one of the oldest plants cultivated by humans. Figs were widespread in Ancient Greece, and spread to Rome where they formed a staple fruit for the lower classes. Figs are easy to preserve and are well-suited to forming condiments due to their high sugar content. It is perhaps this association with the common folk which saw figs fall from fashion in later periods, being associated with simplicity and poverty.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Flax -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 7/01/2018 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_EGYPT_FLAX">
			<Text>Flax</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_EGYPT_FLAX_HELP">
			<Text>Can be improved by Plantation. Spawns near a City on the construction of the Egyptian Nilometer</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_EGYPT_FLAX_TEXT">
			<Text>Flax is a food and fiber crop best known for its use in the production of linen. The crop was first domesticated in the Fertile Crescent and was cultivated extensively in Egypt, where the fabric became tightly bound to the local culture. Linen has a smooth texture, high lustre, and is cool to the touch. These characteristics linked it to religious and ceremonial purity within Egyptian rituals. Priests wore linen fabrics exclusively, and mummies were wrapped in linen in preparation for the afterlife. Today, more durable textiles like cotton have largely replaced linen as a fabric, but the flax seed is still widely used for food and cooking oil.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Fusta -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_JFD_LANTERNAS">
			<Text>Fusta</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HELP_JFD_LANTERNAS">
			<Text>A small and fast compliment to the Galleas, rather than a replacement. Weaker, but cheaper, and does not contribute to unit maintenance. May withdraw before melee attacks.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_JFD_LANTERNAS_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Fusta are quick, cheap, and do not cost any unit maintenance. Use these ships in combination with the bigger Galleass to monitor and protect your shipping lanes without causing an undue burden on your economy.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_JFD_LANTERNAS_TEXT">
			<Text>Fusta, or galliots, were small galleys with no more than 35 sailors. Exceptionally light and fast, the Venetians originally used them to maintain a standing navy against pirates, but the ship quickly became a favorite of the pirates themselves. The shallow draft, maneuverability and speed of the Fusta made them a legend throughout the Mediterranean.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Grande École -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 10/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FRANCE_GRANDE_ECOLE">
			<Text>Grande École</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FRANCE_GRANDE_ECOLE_HELP">
			<Text>Unique French replacement for the Public School.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science and +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for every 2 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens in the City. +3 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for Scientists and +3 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science for Engineers in this City. Greatly Reduces [ICON_HAPPINESS_4] Unhappiness generated by Illiteracy. Allows Archaeologists to be built in this city. +2 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science and +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production at Computers. [NEWLINE]Requires University in City.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FRANCE_GRANDE_ECOLE_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Grande Ecole is the French unique building, replacing the Public School. In addition to the normal bonuses of a Public School, The Grande Ecole increases production for every citizen in the City, has more Scientist Specialist slots, and helps to generate Great Engineers. In addition, all Scientists generate more Production, and all Engineers generate more Science, making any city with a Grande Ecole a powerhouse of scientific and technical achievement.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FRANCE_GRANDE_ECOLE_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The French Grande Ecole are institutions of higher learning separate from the more conventional university system. These schools are highly selective, taking only the best and brightest French graduates, and barring entry by foreigners. Once accepted, students studying at a Grande Ecole are considered public servants, paying little to no entrance fees and even receiving a monthly government stipend. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				The origins of the Grande Ecoles lie in the French Revolution, where several military and technical ecoles normale superieure were established by distinguished French mathematicians and intellectuals. The idea was to open education to individuals based strictly on merit. By the 19th century a number of ecoles had sprung up for a wide array of disciplines including natural sciences, business and the humanities. The Grande Ecoles continue to have a deep impact on French society. Approximately 10% of all Native-born French citizens graduate from these schools, including many of France's most renowned politicians, philosophers, scientists, and executives.
			</Text>
		</Row>
				
		<!-- Hacienda -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 10/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_SPAIN_HACIENDA">
			<Text>Hacienda</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_SPAIN_HACIENDA_HELP">
			<Text>Available at Civil Service, the Hacienda can be built next to Cities or Luxury Resources, but not next to each other. Yields [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_GOLD] Gold and [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Gains [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production from adjacent Cities and [ICON_GOLD] Gold from adjacent Luxury Resources. +1 [ICON_FAITH] Faith if the nearby City has built a Mission.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_SPAIN_HACIENDA_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Haciendas are colonial estates constructed by the Spanish for the administration and extraction of resources from their native subjects. Haciendas were based on grants of property and enterprise, rather than the strict grant of indigenous labor as described by the older Encomienda system. Haciendas were generally large estates, but the nature of the work varied from plantations, to mining, to factories. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				The owner of a Hacienda was called a Hacendado, but such wealthy landowners rarely visited or inspected their holdings and preferred to live in nearby cities. Day-to-day operations of a Hacienda were the responsibility of hired managers. Some unusually large and profitable Haciendas were the property of the Roman Catholic Church, causing no small amount of hostility between native laborers and their Christian taskmasters. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				The Hacienda system was abolished in most countries after the dissolution of the Spanish Empire, but with mixed results. Efforts to break apart the large estates into individual holdings for subsistence farmers led to crushing poverty in some South American nations. In contrast, Latin American and Filipino Haciendas were mostly left intact, though without the same legal standing or permissions of their colonial past.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_SPAIN_HACIENDA">
			<Text>Build a [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_SPAIN_HACIENDA]Hacienda[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_SPAIN_HACIENDA_HELP">
			<Text>Constructs a Hacienda, which yields [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_GOLD] Gold and [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production. [NEWLINE]Gains [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production from adjacent Cities and [ICON_GOLD] Gold from adjacent Luxury Resources. +1 [ICON_FAITH] Faith if the nearby City has built a Mission.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_SPAIN_HACIENDA_REC">
			<Text>It will increase [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_GOLD] Gold and [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production. [NEWLINE]Gains [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production from adjacent Cities and [ICON_GOLD] Gold from adjacent Luxury Resources. +1 [ICON_FAITH] Faith if the nearby City has built a Mission.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Holkan -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 16/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MAYA_RENEWAL_CYCLE">
			<Text>Renewal Cycle</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MAYA_RENEWAL_CYCLE_HELP">
			<Text>Unit is healed for 30 HP [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]in regular turn cycles[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MAYA_SCOUT_GOODY_BONUS_2">
			<Text>Treasure Hunter II</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MAYA_SCOUT_GOODY_BONUS_2_HELP">
			<Text>Unit gains [ICON_RESEARCH] Science [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]from Ancient Ruins[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MAYA_HOLKAN">
			<Text>Holkan</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MAYA_HOLKAN_HELP">
			<Text>Unique Ancient Era Unit, only the Maya may build it. This unit can move faster than the Pathfinder it replaces, and has no penalty against Barbarians. Heals 30HP every 20 turns, and gains [ICON_RESEARCH] science with every ruin.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MAYA_HOLKAN_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Holkan is a quick and independent scout for the Maya. Because of their increased speed, the Holkan explores more quickly, and gains experience more easily than the Pathfinders. Their increased power against barbarians and ability to heal makes Holkans capable of ranging farther and taking more risks than a normal scout. Use these units to grab ruins quickly, and gain an early scientific edge.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MAYA_HOLKAN_TEXT">
			<Text>The Maya were often idealized as a peaceful civilization by western Mayanist scholars, yet the Maya were no strangers to war. Unlike the wars of Europe and Asia, however, the Maya engaged in a highly ritualized form of combat, based on astrological and religious concerns as much as political ones. Squabbles over land, influence and resources were common, but the capture of human sacrifices was another factor leading to war. 
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The nobility and priesthood of Mayan cities kept a monopoly on violence, making all but the most desperate of wars strictly within the affairs of the upper class. Weapons made of obsidian and chert were stockpiled within the palaces of lords and kings, who would call upon their family to lead them. The leader of such raids were known as Holkan.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Great Turkish Bombard -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 1/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_OTTOMANS_SIEGE_INACCURACY_2">
			<Text>Siege Inaccuracy II</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_OTTOMANS_SIEGE_INACCURACY_2_HELP">
			<Text>-50% [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Ranged Combat Strength vs [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Land Units[ENDCOLOR]. Lost after unit upgrade.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_OTTOMANS_SAHI_TOPU">
			<Text>Sahi Topu</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_OTTOMANS_SAHI_TOPU_HELP">
			<Text>Unit deals 20 damage to itself [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Attack[ENDCOLOR]. +10 HP [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Heal inside Friendly Territory[ENDCOLOR]. Lost after unit upgrade.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_OTTOMANS_GREAT_TURKISH_BOMBARD_1">
			<Text>Basilica</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_OTTOMANS_GREAT_TURKISH_BOMBARD_2">
			<Text>Dardanelles Gun</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_OTTOMANS_GREAT_TURKISH_BOMBARD_3">
			<Text>Mohammed's Great Gun</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_OTTOMANS_GREAT_TURKISH_BOMBARD_4">
			<Text>Orban's Cannon</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_OTTOMANS_GREAT_TURKISH_BOMBARD">
			<Text>Great Bombard</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_OTTOMANS_GREAT_TURKISH_BOMBARD_HELP">
			<Text>Unique Medieval Era Siege Unit. An Incredibly powerful unit capable of smashing cities to pieces. Does very high damage to cities and naval units, but is less useful against land units compared to other siege weapons. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Player may have only [COLOR_GREEN]2[ENDCOLOR] Great Bombards at one time.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Only Ottomans may build it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_OTTOMANS_GREAT_TURKISH_BOMBARD_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Great Turkish Bombard is a powerful Siege Weapon well after it is researched. Devastating against cities and naval units. It is the most powerful siege weapon in its era, but be sure to protect them!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_OTTOMANS_GREAT_TURKISH_BOMBARD_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Bigger is better, and biggest is best. The super-sized bombards of the late medieval were first used in Western European warfare at the beginning of the 15th century, but it was the Ottomans that would realize the bombard's full potential at the Siege of Constantinople in 1453. Unable to find patronage with the Byzantine emperor, the Hungarian gunfounder Orban sold his services to Mehmed II of the Ottoman Empire, and began crafting bronze cannons capable of lobbing 1.6 tons of shaped stone more than 2 kilometers. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Transporting such massive weapons took as many as 60 oxen, and required construction or refurbishing of entire road networks before the cannons could be brought to bear against the impregnable Theodosian Walls. Within a day of the opening bombardment, the city which had stood as a fortress of Christendom for a millennium fell, as massive stones smashed the city's defenses to rubble. The sack of Constantinople raged for three days following, and triggered a mass exodus of Greeks into Europe proper. With these Byzantine refugees came a rediscovery of the philosophical and intellectual achievements of Greek culture in Western Europe, planting the seeds of the Renaissance. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Few examples of stone bombards can be found today. These weapons were largely supplanted by iron-ball cannons by the end of the 16th century, but none of those can claim to have single-handedly ended an era.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Goedendag -->
		<!-- Created by De_Genius on 28/10/2017, modified and incorporated by adan_eslavo on 12/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_NETHERLANDS_GOEDENDAG">
			<Text>Goedendag</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_NETHERLANDS_GOEDENDAG_HELP">
			<Text>Unique Medieval Era Melee Unit. A cheap and effective unit in groups, provides a combat boost to all units adjacent to it and has increased [ICON_STRENGTH] Strength when standing on a Luxury Resource tile. Stagnates growth in cities while built. Excess food contributes to production.[NEWLINE]Only the Dutch may build it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_NETHERLANDS_GOEDENDAG_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Goedendag is an odd unit, but effective in groups. While effective on their own against cavalry, the Goedendag provides increased attack against all units adjacent to it, and has additional combat strength if standing on a luxury resource. Goedendag's do not boost their own combat strength, however, so they must be adjacent to another Goedendag to receive the benefit of their own promotion. These units can be built very quickly, so an army can be raised in the event of a surprise war.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_NETHERLANDS_GOEDENDAG_TEXT">
			<Text>
				A goedendag is a four-foot long club with a spear at its tip, originally used by the militias of Medieval Flanders, notably during the Franco-Flemish War. The weapon was christened "goedendag" by the French, a cognate with the universal Dutch-language greeting "good day". The name is supposedly a reference to the Bruges Matins massacre in 1302, at which the guildsmen of Bruges purportedly took over the city by greeting people in the streets, and murdering anyone who answered with a French accent.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				The weapon was used to great effect by the guildsmen of Flanders' wealthy cities against the French knights, but exactly how the weapon was used is a source of debate. Contemporary illustrations show it being used as a club, but the contemporary sources describe its first use as a spear to meet a charge, then a club as the enemy was halted. Flemish Goedendags marked the beginning of the end for heavy cavalry in western Europe, and the dawn of an "Infantry Revolution" where common militia were now a credible threat. The stunning victory of common men over foreign tyrants became a wellspring of romantic nationalism for the Low Countries.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				"each held his godendart (sic) raised against the French, the iron as one meets a wild boar"[NEWLINE]- Guillaume Guiart, a contemporary account describing the battle of Courtrai, 1302 A.D.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_NETHERLANDS_GOEDENDAG">
			<Text>Goedendag!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_NETHERLANDS_GOEDENDAG_HELP">
			<Text>+10% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength vs [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Mounted Units[ENDCOLOR]. +10% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]to all adjacent Friendly Units[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_NETHERLANDS_GOEDENDAG_EFFECT">
			<Text>Golden Spurs</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_NETHERLANDS_GOEDENDAG_EFFECT_HELP">
			<Text>+10% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]from adjacent Friendly Unit[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_NETHERLANDS_BURGEMEESTE">
			<Text>Burgemeeste</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_NETHERLANDS_BURGEMEESTE_HELP">
			<Text>+25% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength if unit is standing [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on a Luxury Resource[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_NETHERLANDS_BURGEMEESTE_EFFECT">
			<Text>Luxuries!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_NETHERLANDS_BURGEMEESTE_EFFECT_HELP">
			<Text>+25% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]from Luxury Resource[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Hashemite Raider -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ARABIA_HASHEMITE_RAIDER">
			<Text>
				Hashemite Raider
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ARABIA_HASHEMITE_RAIDER_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Long considered the 'Sick Man of Europe', Ottoman power was in decline well before nationalist sentiment took root in the Arab population. When WWI broke out among the European powers and Ottomans set about to crush Arab dissent, the Arabs responded in a popular revolt, declaring a new Islamic empire.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Hussein bin Ali, Sharif of Mecca, began his rebellion in hopes of re-establishing a Hashemite dynasty in Arabia, and led his fellow Arabs in a popular revolt against their Turkish masters in Hejaz. Seeing an opportunity to tie down Ottoman forces in a new front, the British promised to recognize Arab hegemony and heavily subsidize the revolt, sending the now famous T.E. Lawrence as a liaison. The Arabs waged a guerilla war through the desert, crippling Ottoman supply lines and retreating back into the vast desert. With the help of French and English navy, they were able to take several ports along the Mediterranean coast, drawing even more to join their cause.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				With the end of WWI in 1918, and the Ottomans soundly defeated, the Arabs expected the full cooperation of their European allies as they established their new kingdom, but the English and French had other plans. Reneging on their agreement, the French and English secretly, formed the Sykes-Picot Agreement, in which Britain and France agreed to divide the Middle-East amongst themselves into their own respective spheres on influence. This gross betrayal of a trusted ally has soured relations between the Arab states and the West ever since.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ARABIA_HASHEMITE_RAIDER_STRATEGY">
			<Text>
				The Hashemite Raider the Arab replacement for the Light Tank. It is adept at hit-and-run tactics and disrupting enemy supply lines. Whenever it pillages an improvement, adjacent enemy units take 10 damage. Moves quickly through desert.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ARABIA_HASHEMITE_RAIDER_HELP">
			<Text>
				The Hashemite Raider is the Arabian replacement for the Light Tank. It is stronger than the unit it replaces, available earlier, and does not require Aluminum. Double Movement and +25% [ICON_STRENGTH] Strength in Desert. This unit requires no movement to pillage, and deals damage to adjacent enemy units when pillaging improvements.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_GARLAND_MINE">
			<Text>
				Garland Mine
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_GARLAND_MINE_HELP">
			<Text>
				Unit uses [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]no[ENDCOLOR] [ICON_ARROW_RIGHT] Movement Points [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Pillage[ENDCOLOR]. All [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]adjacent Enemy Units[ENDCOLOR] take flat damage [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Pillage[ENDCOLOR].
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_DESERT_RAIDER">
			<Text>
				Desert Raider
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_DESERT_RAIDER_HELP">
			<Text>
				Double [ICON_ARROW_RIGHT] Movement and +25% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Desert[ENDCOLOR].
			</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Hippodorme -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 2/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BYZANTIUM_HIPPODROME">
			<Text>Hippodrome</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BYZANTIUM_HIPPODROME_HELP">
			<Text>Requires Arena in City. +20% [ICON_GOLD] Gold and [ICON_CULTURE] in the City during 'We Love the King Day' and a 'We Love the King Day' begins immediately on Completion. +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture on the Palace, all Arenas gain +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and all Circuses gain +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture. +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture on all sources of [ICON_RES_HORSE] Horses. On completion, triggers an Event. The [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production Cost and [ICON_CITIZEN] Population Requirements increase based on the number of cities you own.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BYZANTIUM_HIPPODROME_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Hippodrome is the Byzantine Unique Wonder, replacing the Circus Maximus. In comparison to the Circus Maximus, The Hippodrome greatly increases Gold and Culture yields during 'We Love the King Days' and begins a 'We Love the King Day' on completion. The Palace gains Culture and Gold, and all Arenas in the empire receive gold, while circuses receive Culture, and Horses get both. In addition to the 'We Love the King Day', a unique event is triggered on completion, giving your choice of additional bonuses. Choose wisely!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BYZANTIUM_HIPPODROME_TEXT">
			<Text>The Hippodrome was a chariot racing track and the beating heart of Byzantine social and political life. Located immediately next to the palace, the track was built by Constantine shortly after moving his capital to the city. The track was U-shaped, with ten monuments lining the center. Though slightly smaller in footprint than the Circus Maximus in Rome, the Hippodrome was adorned with art and treasures from all corners of the empire.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
			Not just a pastime of the rich, the chariot races become the one place where the common people could see and interact with the emperor in a single venue. Commoners often took this opportunity to begin chants for political or religious reforms during sporting events. Four political parties, or demes, existed within Constantinople which each sponsored a different racing team.  These were the Blues, the Whites, the Greens and the Reds. Enormous sums of money were wagered on the rivalries between these teams, which became further heated by the religious, societal and political leanings which each team came to represent.	One such feud in particular would come to overshadow them all: the Nika riots.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] 
			During the reign of Justinian I (an ardent supporter of the Blues), a dispute arose concerning the sentencing of two hooligans who had been arrested for murder from a prior riot. The sentencing of these men unified the Blues and the Greens against Justinian in a terrible mob, and disgruntled nobles seized the opportunity to try to depose him in revenge for the recently levied taxes against the rich Though at first he considered fleeing Constantinople, Justinian rallied his loyal generals to corral the rioters into the Hippodrome, where they were butchered by royal guardsmen and Gothic mercenaries. By the time the Nika riots had ended, half of Constantinople had been burned down and 30,000 rioters and conspirators lay dead; the most violent riot in world history.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Huey Teocalli -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VP_HUEY_TEOCALLI">
			<Text>
				Huey Teocalli
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VP_HUEY_TEOCALLI_TEXT">
			<Text>
				In the Aztec Empire, a teocalli was a terraced pyramid, surmounted by a temple on top, site of all the important religious rituals in the town. The greatest was located in the heart of Tenochtitlan, the Huey Teocalli (or, according to the Spanish, the Templo Mayor) dedicated to a pair of gods: Huitzilopochtli, the god of war, and Tlaloc, the god of agriculture (an indication of what was important in Aztec culture). Each god had a separate temple, reached by separate staircases.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VP_HUEY_TEOCALLI_STRATEGY">
			<Text>
				The Huey Teocalli is the unique Aztec replacement for the Grand Temple. It does not require a Temple, and provides a free Temple in the city. It provides a global bonus to Barracks and Floating Gardens. Every time you enter a Golden Age, the Huey Teocalli permanently gains Food, Faith, and additional XP to units built in the city.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VP_HUEY_TEOCALLI_HELP">
			<Text>
				Unique replacement for the Grand Temple. Only the Aztec may build it.[NEWLINE]Comes with a free Temple. A [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age begins. Reduces [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Religious Unrest. All Temples gain +1 [ICON_PEACE] Faith and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, Barracks get +2 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, and Floating Gardens get +2 [ICON_FOOD] Food. Whenever you enter a Golden Age, permanently gain +3 [ICON_FOOD], +3 [ICON_PEACE] Faith, and +3 XP for units trained in the city (max +30 each).[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production Cost and [ICON_CITIZEN] Population Requirements increase based on the number of cities you own.
			</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Iron Chariot -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ASSYRIA_IRON_CHARIOT">
			<Text>
				Iron Chariot
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ASSYRIA_IRON_CHARIOT_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Before horses were bred to be big enough to carry men on their backs, Chariots formed the core of the Assyrian army. Assyrian chariots were drawn by four horses and used to smash into and disperse enemy formations.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ASSYRIA_IRON_CHARIOT_STRATEGY">
			<Text>
				Assyria's Iron Chariots act as shock troops to control the battlefield. They excel at breaking enemy ranks. The Iron Chariot gains a combat bonus for every adjacent enemy unit, neutralizing the enemy's flanking bonuses and allowing your chariots to take greater risks on the battlefield. Iron and Horse resources in excess of the number of Iron Chariots you own increase the combat effectivness of your chariots
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ASSYRIA_IRON_CHARIOT_HELP">
			<Text>
				The Iron Chariot is the Assyrian replacement for the Horseman. It does not require Horses, and gains +2 combat strength if you have sufficient Horses for all Iron Chariots, and likewise for Iron. Gains +10% combat strength for each adjacent enemy unit.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_FURY_OF_NERGAL">
			<Text>
				Fury of Nergal
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_FURY_OF_NERGAL_HELP">
			<Text>
				+10% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]for each adjacent Enemy Unit[ENDCOLOR].
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_FURY_OF_NERGAL_1">
			<Text>
				Fury of Nergal I
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_FURY_OF_NERGAL_1_HELP">
			<Text>
				+10% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_FURY_OF_NERGAL_2">
			<Text>
				Fury of Nergal II
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_FURY_OF_NERGAL_2_HELP">
			<Text>
				+20% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_FURY_OF_NERGAL_3">
			<Text>
				Fury of Nergal III
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_FURY_OF_NERGAL_3_HELP">
			<Text>
				+30% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_FURY_OF_NERGAL_4">
			<Text>
				Fury of Nergal IV
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_FURY_OF_NERGAL_4_HELP">
			<Text>
				+40% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_FURY_OF_NERGAL_5">
			<Text>
				Fury of Nergal V
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_FURY_OF_NERGAL_5_HELP">
			<Text>
				+50% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_FURY_OF_NERGAL_6">
			<Text>
				In a Pickle
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_FURY_OF_NERGAL_6_HELP">
			<Text>
				+60% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength.
			</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Kampong -->
		<!-- Created by pineappledan; incorporated by adan_eslavo on 24/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_INDONESIA_KAMPONG">
			<Text>Kampong</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_INDONESIA_KAMPONG_TEXT">
			<Text>The Bajau-Laut people are a living anomaly: nomads of the sea, they defy countries’ conventional borders. Sailing from place to place on the blue waters between the Philippines, Indonesia, and Malaysia, the Bajau-Laut people live on the bounty of the sea. Traveling in a loose “village” made up of a few families, the Bajau-Laut are almost as reliant on others as they are of their beloved sea. Bajau religion is also tied to the sea, being an unique mixture of animism and Islam. In recent years, the Bajau-Laut people have been forced by multiple governments to become sedentary, living in permanent buildings on land. A combination of overfishing and toxic fishing techniques have also turned Bajau-Laut lives over, as they have had to move onto land out of necessity. Still, a few communities of Bajau-Laut ride their lepa lepa across the blue water of Southeast Asia, only traveling to shore a few times each year.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_INDONESIA_KAMPONG_HELP">
			<Text>Available at Sailing, the Kampong can be built by embarked Workers on Coastal tiles. Each Kampong yields [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and adjacent Sea Resources receive +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production. Cannot be built adjacent to each other.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_INDONESIA_KAMPONG">
			<Text>Build a [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_INDONESIA_KAMPONG]Kampong[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_INDONESIA_KAMPONG_HELP">
			<Text>Constructs a Kampong, which increases [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and adjacent Sea Resources receive +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_INDONESIA_KAMPONG_REC">
			<Text>It will increase [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and adjacent Sea Resources receive +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Khopesh -->
		<!-- Created by BlueGhost, incorporated and modified by adan_eslavo on 7/01/2018 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_EGYPTIAN_KHOPESH">
			<Text>Khopesh</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_EGYPTIAN_KHOPESH_TEXT">
			<Text>Khopesh is the Egyptian name of the Canaanite "sickle-sword", in Assyrian known as sappara. Its origins can be traced back to Sumer of the third millennium BC, where the Stele of Vultures depicts Eannatum of Lagash, the world's first emperor, wielding a khopesh.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]A typical khopesh is 50–60 cm (20–24 inches) in length, designed for hooking an opponent's shield or disarming them. The blade is only sharpened on the outside portion of the curved end. The khopesh evolved from the epsilon or similar crescent shaped axes that were used in warfare. Note, however, that the khopesh is not an axe, but rather a slashing weapon like a sabre. Many examples of Khopesh can be found in tombs and many Pharaohs are depicted holding the weapon. Indeed, many examples of khopesh found do not show signs of ever having been sharpened, indicating they were ceremonial, or status symbols.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_EGYPTIAN_KHOPESH_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Khopesh is the unique Egyptian replacement for the Spearman. It's a strong early unit that has an edge in direct combat. However, unlike the Spearman it replaces, it does not have a combat bonus against mounted units.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_EGYPTIAN_KHOPESH_HELP">
			<Text>Strong, front-line land Unit of the Ancient Era. Only Egypt may build it. Deals increased damage vs heavily damaged units, and has the Skillful promotion, which temporarily reduces the combat power of a unit that it attacks.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_EGYPT_FATIGUE">
			<Text>Skillful</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_EGYPT_FATIGUE_HELP">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]After Attack[ENDCOLOR] Defending Enemy Unit gets -20% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]until it Fortifies[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_EGYPT_FATIGUE_1">
			<Text>Fatigue</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_EGYPT_FATIGUE_1_HELP">
			<Text>-20% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength. Penalty is removed [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]after Fortifying[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_EGYPT_MERCY">
			<Text>Mercy</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_EGYPT_MERCY_HELP">
			<Text>+30% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength vs [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Units at or below 50 HP[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Kibitum -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 27/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY">
			<Text>Legacy</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_HELP">
			<Text>Unit gets +8% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]every 2 levels gained[ENDCOLOR] until level [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]10[ENDCOLOR], then additional +10% on level [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]12[ENDCOLOR] and 25% on level [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]15[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_1">
			<Text>Legacy I</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_1_HELP">
			<Text>+8% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_2">
			<Text>Legacy II</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_2_HELP">
			<Text>+16% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_3">
			<Text>Legacy III</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_3_HELP">
			<Text>+24% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_4">
			<Text>Legacy IV</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_4_HELP">
			<Text>+32% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_5">
			<Text>Legacy V</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_5_HELP">
			<Text>+40% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_6">
			<Text>Legacy VI</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_6_HELP">
			<Text>+50% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_7">
			<Text>A Winner is You</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_7_HELP">
			<Text>+75% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_BABYLON_KIBITUM">
			<Text>Sabum Kibitum</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_BABYLON_KIBITUM_HELP">
			<Text>Unique Ancient Era Unit.  Only the Babylonians may build it. This unit is stronger than the spearman it replaces. Receives additional [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength for every 2 levels and has the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Quick Study[ENDCOLOR] Promotion for free.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_BABYLON_KIBITUM_STRATEGY">
			<Text>A soldier to stand the test of time. The Khibitum is not the strongest unit in its era, but its true strength lies in how it gains more power from experience than normal units. Keep these soldiers alive, and they will form an indispensable core for your army.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_BABYLON_KIBITUM_TEXT">
			<Text>The Babylonians were descended from semi-nomadic Amorite and Akkadian tribes from upper Mesopotamia. With the collapse of the Sumerian and Akkadian kingdoms, these Amorite tribes poured into Mesopotamia unopposed and established new dynasties. While in many respects these conquerors assimilated into Sumerian culture, their armies retained the toughness of nomadic peoples.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The Sabum Kibitum were the heavy troops of the Babylonians and one of the earliest examples of career soldiers in history. Assembled from the royal guard and city residents, Sabum Kibitum were armed with long and short spears, javelins and bows to form a disciplined and flexible fighting force.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Klepht -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 5/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_GREECE_PHILHELLENISM">
			<Text>Philhellenism</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_GREECE_PHILHELLENISM_HELP">
			<Text>Unit gains [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_GOLD] Gold [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]for every City-State Ally or Friend on Fight[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREECE_KLEPHT">
			<Text>Klepht</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREECE_KLEPHT_HELP">
			<Text>Unique Industrial Era Unit.  Only the Greeks may build it. This unit is slightly weaker than the Gatling Gun it replaces and does not have the [COLOR_RED]Covering Fire I[ENDCOLOR] Promotion, but can move quickly through hills and can move after attacking. Receives the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Philhellenism[ENDCOLOR] Promotion for free.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREECE_KLEPHT_STRATEGY">
			<Text>A quick and elusive guerilla fighter. The Klepht is not as powerful as the Gatling Gun it replaces, but can move quickly through hills, even after attacking. This unit also gains gold and production for every city-state ally every time it attacks a unit.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREECE_KLEPHT_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Bandits and mountainfolk, turned anti-Ottoman insurgents and freedom fighters, The Klephts were the bedrock upon which the modern Greek army was formed. Together with the men originally hired to capture them, the Armatoloi, the Klephts formed the "yeast of liberty", and the first hope for Greek independence after more than four centuries of Ottoman occupation. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Undisciplined and flighty as one would expect of brigands, Klephts waged an effective guerilla campaign against the much larger and well-armed Ottoman forces sent to subdue them.  Massacres on both sides of the conflict were carried out, but Western European sympathy fell heavily in favor of the Greeks. The unbridled cruelty of the Muslim Ottomans outraged Europe’s citizenry, who raised supplies, food and even soldiers to fight for a Hellenic independence. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				After 8 years Ottoman forces had mostly succeeded in crushing the revolt, but where Greek soldiers had failed poets and propaganda had succeeded brilliantly. French, British and Russian governments each sent a fleet in defense of the Greek islands, in response to popular demand for intervention. In the face of such overwhelming force, the Ottomans sued for peace and liberated Greece. After more than 2,000 years under the boots of Macedonians, Romans and Ottomans, The Greek homeland was at last free; unified as one people for the first time in history.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Koa -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 3/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_POLYNESIA_KAPU_KUIALUA">
			<Text>Kapu Ku'ialua</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_POLYNESIA_KAPU_KUIALUA_HELP">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]After Attack[ENDCOLOR] Defending Enemy Unit is marked. [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]At the beginning of its turn[ENDCOLOR] it takes an additional 10 "bleed" damage for every mark. Effect can stack up to [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]3[ENDCOLOR] times after battles with 3 different units.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_POLYNESIA_KAPU_KUIALUA_ON_UNIT">
			<Text>Bleeding</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_POLYNESIA_KAPU_KUIALUA_ON_UNIT_HELP">
			<Text>Unit takes an additional 10 "bleed" damage [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]at the start of its turn[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_POLYNESIA_KAPU_KUIALUA_2_ON_UNIT">
			<Text>Heavy Bleeding</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_POLYNESIA_KAPU_KUIALUA_2_ON_UNIT_HELP">
			<Text>Unit takes an additional 20 "bleed" damage [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]at the start of its turn[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_POLYNESIA_KAPU_KUIALUA_3_ON_UNIT">
			<Text>Hemorrhaging</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_POLYNESIA_KAPU_KUIALUA_3_ON_UNIT_HELP">
			<Text>Unit takes an additional 30 "bleed" damage [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]at the start of its turn[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_POLYNESIA_KOA">
			<Text>Koa</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_POLYNESIA_KOA_HELP">
			<Text>Unique Classical Era Unit, only Polynesia may build it. This unit is slightly stronger than the Scout it replaces, has the [COLOR_GREEN]Amphibious[ENDCOLOR] promotion, and deals an additional 10 damage to units at the beginning of their turn.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_POLYNESIA_KOA_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Koa is an effective early scout, able to hold its own against barbarians. It is stronger than the Scout, and can fight equally well across rivers and while embarked. This unit also deals an additional 10 'bleed' damage to enemies it attacks at the beginning of the enemy's turn, making them effective at clearing barbarians and preventing healing.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_POLYNESIA_KOA_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Deadly warriors from the islands of Hawai'i, Koa are named after the Koa tree, from which most of their weapons are fashioned. These warriors were trained extensively in Kapu Ku'ialua, a traditional Hawai'ian martial art specializing in weaponry and the focusing of mana into bone-shattering attacks. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				In battle, Koa warriors were well-versed in many weapons, including knuckle-dusters, slings, and garrotes, but were also capable hand-to-hand fighters. More traditional melee weapons were also used, including wooden daggers, clubs, staves, and paddles. These weapons would occasionally be modified by sewing shark teeth along their edges, creating devastating serrated weapons called 'Leiomano'. These weapons were used similarly to the obsidian-tipped Macuahuitl of Central America.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Laguna -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LAGUNA">
			<Text>Laguna</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LAGUNA_TEXT">
			<Text>When a [ICON_INTERNATIONAL_TRADE] Sea Trade Route originating here and targeting another Civ is completed, receive a [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism boost with the Civ based on your recent [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism output.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_FOOD] Food from Coast and Ocean Tiles, +2 [ICON_FOOD] Food and +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production to Atolls and +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production from Sea Resources worked by this City. Sea Trade Routes gain +75% Range and +4 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_GOLD] Gold to Rialto District, +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and +1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science to Venetian Arsenale, and +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism to Murano Glassworks.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+15% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production of Naval units, and increases Military Units supplied by this City''s population by 10%. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must be built on the Coast.[NEWLINE]Requires a Lighthouse in the City.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LAGUNA_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Laguna is a Medieval-era building, requiring a Lighthouse. It improves the range and [ICON_GOLD] Gold yield of sea trade routes, and boosts the value of sea tiles and resources. The Laguna also increases the [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production of Naval units by 15%, and increases Military Units supplied by this City''s population by 10%. The Laguna additionally provide bonus yields to Murano Glassworks, Rialto District, and Arsenale di Venezia.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LAGUNA_PEDIA">
			<Text>Laguna (eng. Lagoons) are shallow bodies of salt water separated from a larger sea by barrier islands or reefs. Venice itself is situated on the bank of a large lagoon, artificially maintained and enlarged by the dredging of the Venetian canals. The Venice Lagoon is also the largest wetland in the Mediterranean, offering protection as well as a rich source of food to its inhabitants.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Lamassu Gate -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ASSYRIA_LAMASSU_GATE">
			<Text>
				Lamassu Gate
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ASSYRIA_LAMASSU_GATE_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Lamassu are Assyrian protective deities, often depicted as having a human's head, a body of a bull or a lion, and bird's wings. The Lamassu were household protective spirits of the common Babylonian and Assyrian peoples, becoming associated later as royal protectors, and were placed as sentinels at entrances. Depictions of Lamassu are found throughout Assyrian architecture, positioned on the thresholds of buildings and as colossal statues on each side of the city and palace gates. To protect houses, Lamassi were engraved in clay tablets, which were then buried under the door's threshold.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ASSYRIA_LAMASSU_GATE_STRATEGY">
			<Text>
				The Lamassu Gate is an Assyrian unique building, replacing the Walls. It increases the unit supply cap in the city more than the standard Walls. It also grants +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and a Writer specialist slot.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ASSYRIA_LAMASSU_GATE_HELP">
			<Text>
				Unique Wall replacement. Only the Assyrians may build it. Military Units supplied by this City's population increased by 20%.
			</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Landwehr -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_AUSTRIAN_LANDWEHR">
			<Text>
				Landwehr
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_AUSTRIAN_LANDWEHR_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The Austrian Landwehr was one of three components that made up the ground forces of the Austro-Hungarian Dual Monarchy between 1868 and 1918, and it was composed of recruits from the Cisleithanian parts of the empire. Intended as a national defence force alongside the Hungarian Landwehr, the Austrian Landwehr was officially established by order of Emperor Franz Josef on 5 December 1868. Yet, while the Hungarian force was generously supported early on by the parliament in Budapest, legislators in Vienna generally failed to advance the cause of the Landwehr, leaving it by the 1870s as a skeletal force with only the appearance of parity. [NEWLINE[NEWLINE]The 1880s saw an expansion in the force's numbers, as the high command was unable to obtain increases in manpower for the joint Imperial and Royal army and sought to increase overall numbers through the Landwehr. Additionally, Austrian fears of the development of the Hungarian Landwehr caused the Austrian Reichsrat to vote to increase the Landwehr's strength to 135,000. These nationalist interests led to a gradual strengthening and improvement of the force, so that by the start of the First World War, Landwehr units were considered equal to the units of the joint army in readiness and equipment.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_AUSTRIAN_LANDWEHR_STRATEGY">
			<Text>
				The Landwehr is the backbone of the Industrial-era Austrian army. It excels in defending in owned territory and the territory of allied city-states.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_AUSTRIAN_LANDWEHR_HELP">
			<Text>
				The Landwehr is the Austrian replacement for the Fusilier. It gets a combat bonus when fighting in territory owned by Austria and allied city-states.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_IMPERIAL_VIGILANCE">
			<Text>
				Imperial Vigilance
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_IMPERIAL_VIGILANCE_HELP">
			<Text>
				+25% combat bonus in owned territory and territory of allied city-states.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_LANDWEHR_CS_BONUS">
			<Text>
				City-State Defense
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_LANDWEHR_CS_BONUS_HELP">
			<Text>
				+25% combat in the territory of allied city-states.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_YORKSCHER_MARCHE">
			<Text>
				Yorkscher Marche
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_YORKSCHER_MARCHE_HELP">
			<Text>
				+2 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture per turn while in owned territory.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Langskib -->
		<!-- Created by De_Genius on 28/10/2017, incorporated and modified by adan_eslavo on 21/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_DENMARK_LANGSKIB">
			<Text>Longship</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_DENMARK_LANGSKIB_HELP">
			<Text>Early naval unit. Starts with 20 [ICON_STRENGTH] CP instead of the 25 of the Caravel, which it replaces, but is available at Physics. Starts with the [COLOR_GREEN]Viking Exploration[ENDCOLOR] promotion, [COLOR_GREEN]Can move after attacking[ENDCOLOR], and [COLOR_GREEN]Medic I[ENDCOLOR] Promotions. Only Denmark may build it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_DENMARK_LANGSKIB_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Danish Longship is an early ship unit which allow Denmark to have early sea control. This allows Denmark to begin scouting the far seas earlier than the other players to prepare future waves of colonization, defend your colonies abroad and provides support to raids with its bonuses to healing at sea and performing hit-and-run tactics.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_DENMARK_LANGSKIB_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Longships were a type of ship invented and used by the Norsemen (commonly known as the Vikings) for trade, commerce, exploration, and warfare during the Viking Age. The longship's design evolved over many centuries, beginning in the Stone Age with the invention of the umiak and continuing up until the 6th century with clinker-built ships like Nydam and Kvalsund, appearing in its complete form between the 9th and 13th centuries. The character and appearance of these ships have been reflected in Scandinavian boat-building traditions until today.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Longships were particularly notable for their relatively quick speed and light construction. The ships were sturdy and reliable at sea, yet light enough to be carried onto shore or even tipped over as a makeshift shelter for sailors. The ability to move quickly in and out of shore was invaluable during the many raids for which the Vikings would become infamous.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The particular skills and methods employed in making longships are still used worldwide, often with modern adaptations. They were all made out of wood, with woven wool sails, and had numerous details and carvings on the hull.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_DENMARK_VIKING_EXPLORATION">
			<Text>Viking Exploration</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_DENMARK_VIKING_EXPLORATION_HELP">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Embarked Units[ENDCOLOR] starting in the same tile as a unit with this promotion [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]can cross Ocean[ENDCOLOR]. Promotion stays until Embarked Unit leaves the Ocean.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_DENMARK_VIKING_EXPLORATION_CAN_CROSS_OCEAN">
			<Text>Free to Explore</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_DENMARK_VIKING_EXPLORATION_CAN_CROSS_OCEAN_HELP">
			<Text>Unit [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]can cross Ocean Tiles[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>		
		
		<!-- Latifundium -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 10/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_ROME_LATIFUNDIUM">
			<Text>Latifundium</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_ROME_LATIFUNDIUM_HELP">
			<Text>Available at Calendar, the Latifundium can be built on wheat, and any resource normally requiring a plantation. Yields [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_CULTURE] Culture. [NEWLINE]Spawns an Improved [ICON_RES_FIGS] Figs Resource on an adjacent tile to the latifundium after 10 turns, and the Figs tile is automatically claimed by Rome.[NEWLINE]Adjacent Farms receive +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and Adjacent Plantations Receive +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_ROME_LATIFUNDIUM_TEXT">
			<Text>A latifundium was an expansive privately owned farm, enormous landed estates specializing in intensive agriculture. The first latifundia were accumulated from the spoils of war, confiscated from conquered peoples beginning in the early 2nd century BC in Magna Graecia (Southern Italy). Latifundia later expanded with conquest, to the Roman provinces of the Maghreb and in Hispania Baetica, in southern Spain.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]These estates depended on slave labor and serfs for their productivity, often supplied by the enslavement of the very peoples whose land had been taken. The Latifundia quickly started economic consolidation as larger estates achieved greater economies of scale, enjoyed by the political elite as they did not pay land taxes. Owners re-invested their profits by purchasing smaller neighbouring farms, since smaller farms had a lower productivity and could not compete, in an ancient precursor of agribusiness. As the small farms of the Roman peasantry were bought up by the wealthy and with their vast supply of slaves, the now landless peasantry were forced to find work in the cities of Rome, though often resorting to squatting and handouts.
			[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Latifundia became the template upon which later European nations would base their imperial experiments. The Spanish are most noticeable for patterning the Encomienda system after the late Roman Latifundia.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_ROME_LATIFUNDIUM">
			<Text>Build a [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_ROME_LATIFUNDIUM]Latifundium[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_ROME_LATIFUNDIUM_HELP">
			<Text>Constructs a Latifundium, which yields [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture.[NEWLINE]Spawns an Improved [ICON_RES_FIGS] Figs Resource on an adjacent tile to the latifundium after 10 turns, and the Figs tile is automatically claimed by Rome.[NEWLINE]Adjacent Farms receive +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and Adjacent Plantations Receive +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_ROME_LATIFUNDIUM_REC">
			<Text>It will increase [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture.[NEWLINE]Spawns an Improved [ICON_RES_FIGS] Figs Resource on an adjacent tile to the latifundium after 10 turns, and the Figs tile is automatically claimed by Rome.[NEWLINE]Adjacent Farms receive +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and Adjacent Plantations Receive +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Legion (lua code in Ballista.lua)-->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 30/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ROME_PRAEFECTUS_CASTRORUM">
			<Text>Praefectus Castrorum</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ROME_PRAEFECTUS_CASTRORUM_HELP">
			<Text>+60% [ICON_WORKER] Work Rate [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]to all Legion Units within 2 tiles[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ROME_PRAEFECTUS_CASTRORUM_ON_LEGION">
			<Text>Praefectus Castrorum</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ROME_PRAEFECTUS_CASTRORUM_ON_LEGION_HELP">
			<Text>+60% [ICON_WORKER] Work Rate if [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Great General is within 2 tiles[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ROME_PRAEFECTUS_CASTRORUM_EFFECT">
			<Text>Camp Management</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ROME_PRAEFECTUS_CASTRORUM_EFFECT_HELP">
			<Text>+60% [ICON_WORKER] Work Rate [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]from Great General[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Licorne -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 26/10/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_RUSSIA_GRAPESHOT">
			<Text>Grapeshot</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_RUSSIA_GRAPESHOT_HELP">
			<Text>+50% [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Ranged Combat Strength vs [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Melee Units[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_RUSSIA_LICORNE">
			<Text>Licorne</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_RUSSIA_LICORNE_HELP">
			<Text>Unique Industrial Era Siege Unit. Only the Russians may build it. This Unit has better mobility in enemy territory, can move after attacking, and is more effective against Unmounted Melee units.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_RUSSIA_LICORNE_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Licorne is a siege unit that can change the course of battle. Innovative construction allows moving after attacks and no penalty while attacking melee units. Is available earlier than the Field Gun.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_RUSSIA_LICORNE_TEXT">
			<Text>Licorne is the French name given to the Russian 'unicorn' cannons, named for the distinctively shaped handles on the gun barrels. Devised in 1757, Licornes were a flexible design, easy to fire and transport and made in many variants of differing weights and power. Lighter designs are best remembered from their use as mobile horse artillery, a Russian innovation that would change the European theory of combined arms for the next century.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Longbowman -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 6/01/2018 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ENGLAND_AGINCOURT">
			<Text>Agincourt</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ENGLAND_AGINCOURT_HELP">
			<Text>+20% [ICON_RANGED_STRENGTH] Attack Bonus and +20% [ICON_STRENGTH] Defense Bonus vs [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Armor and Mounted Units[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>


		<!-- Madrasah -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARABIA_MADRASAH">
			<Text>
				Madrasah
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARABIA_MADRASAH_TEXT">
			<Text>
				"Madrasah" is Arabic for any type of educational institution; although with a religious component, madrasahs were often secular, and could cover anything from elementary to higher learning. Usually associated with a mosque, madrasahs could even specialize in medicine, law, science, philosophy or the education of women. The first madrasah, the Gama'at al-Qarawiyyn, was established in 859 AD by Fatimah al-Fihri, the daughter of a wealthy merchant. During the rule of the Fatimid, Ayyubid and Mamluk dynasties, the practice of sponsoring madrasahs by the ruling, wealthy elite spread across Egypt and the Middle East. The first Ottoman madrasah was founded in 1331 AD in Iznik, and followed the traditions of Sunni Islam. The madrasahs of the Turks and Arabs would, as Europe suffered through the Dark Ages, keep the best of Western knowledge alive, and blended it with that of the East.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARABIA_MADRASAH_STRATEGY">
			<Text>
				Unique Arabian replacement for the University. In addition to the bonuses of a University, increases Great Person rate. Whenever you make a Faith purchase, the Madrasah generates additional Science.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARABIA_MADRASAH_HELP">
			<Text>
				+1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science from Jungle tiles worked by this City. Gain 33% of the [ICON_RESEARCH] Science output of the City as an instant boost to your current Research when a [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen is born in this City. Reduces [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Illiteracy.[NEWLINE] Whenever you make a [ICON_PEACE] Faith purchase in the city, gain 20 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science (or 100 for a Great Person purchase), scaling with era.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_ALERT_MADRASAH_SCIENCE">
			<Text>
				Making a [ICON_PEACE] Faith purchase has earned you {1_num} [ICON_RESEARCH] Science from your Madrasah in {2_Str}.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Monitor -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_MONITOR">
			<Text>
				Surveillance
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_MONITOR_HELP">
			<Text>
				When starting turn next to a friendly city, that city gains +5 [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength this turn.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Monolithic Church -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 12/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH">
			<Text>Monolithic Church</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The term "monolithic church" (or "rock-hewn church") can be attributed to any church cut from a single stone formation, but is most often used to refer to the complex of 11 churches in Lalibela, Ethiopia. These churches are believed to have been constructed in the 12th century by King Gebre Mesqel Lalibela, a devout Christian. This 'New Jerusalem' is situated in a mountainous region in the heart of Ethiopia, and is an important center of Ethiopian Christianity, pilgrimage and devotion to this day. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Ethiopia boasts many more Monolithic Churches besides those in Lalibela, including many in Tigray. These churches were almost unknown to the outside world until Abba Tewelde Medhin Josief, a Catholic priest, presented a paper to the 1970 International Conference of Ethiopian Studies in which he announced the existence of over 120 rock-hewn churches, 90 of which were still in use. Over the next few years, the total of known churches was raised to 153.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_HELP">
			<Text>Available at Theology, the Monolithic Church can be built on [ICON_RES_STONE] Stone or [ICON_RES_MARBLE] Marble Resources, or on Unfeatured Hills, but not next to each other. Improves sources of [ICON_RES_STONE] Stone and [ICON_RES_MARBLE] Marble. Each Monolithic Church yields [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and [ICON_FAITH] Faith. Monolithic Churches are improved by the completion of Social Policy Trees instead of by Technologies</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH">
			<Text>Construct a [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH]Monolithic Church[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_HELP">
			<Text>Constructs a Monolithic Church, which increases [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and [ICON_FAITH] Faith.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_REC">
			<Text>It will increase [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and [ICON_FAITH] Faith.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Nilometer -->
		<!-- Created by BlueGhost, incorporated and modified by adan_eslavo on 7/01/2018 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VP_NILOMETER">
			<Text>Nilometer</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VP_NILOMETER_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Nilometer is an Egyptian unique building, replacing the Water Mill. It greatly increases the city's [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production output. On construction, 2 Flax resources spawn near the city, which provide additional culture and Production. This building can be built anywhere, as long as you don't have a Well in the City already.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VP_NILOMETER_HELP">
			<Text>Unique Egyptian replacement for the Water Mill.[NEWLINE]+2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for every 5 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens in the City. 2 [ICON_RES_FLAX] Flax Resources spawn near the city.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Oppidum -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 30/10/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_CELTS_OPPIDUM">
			<Text>Oppidum</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_CELTS_OPPIDUM_HELP">
			<Text>Unique Celtic Great Tile Improvement. Will connect Strategic Resources on this tile to the trade network. Gives a +50% [ICON_STRENGTH] Defense Bonus to units stationed on it, and +20HP to a nearby Cities. Adjacent Improvements gain additional bonus yields</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_CELTS_OPPIDUM_TEXT">
			<Text>An Oppidum is a large defended settlement associated with the Celtic late La Tene culture. In Iberia, they are usually referred to as Castro, fortified villages often built in naturally protected areas and full of circular constructions. In times of conflict, the people who lived in open fields moved to these strategically located buildings to ensure their safety. Oppida could also have other purposes such as control of territory or safeguarding of crops.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_CELTS_OPPIDUM">
			<Text>Construct an [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_CELTS_OPPIDUM]Oppidum[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_CELTS_OPPIDUM_HELP">
			<Text>It will increase [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_GOLD] Gold, [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, and [ICON_FAITH] Faith. Gives [ICON_STRENGTH] Defense Bonus to units stationed on it, and +20HP to nearby cities. Provides bonus yields to all non-road and non-great person land improvements.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_CELTS_OPPIDUM_REC">
			<Text>Unit will be consumed[NEWLINE]Unique Celtic Great Tile Improvement. Will connect Strategic Resources on this tile to the trade network. Gives a [ICON_STRENGTH] Defense Bonus to units stationed on it, and +20HP to all Cities in workable range. Adjacent Improvements gain additional bonus yields.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Pairidaeza -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 16/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PERSIA_PAIRIDAEZA">
			<Text>Paradise Garden</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PERSIA_PAIRIDAEZA_HELP">
			<Text>Unique Persian replacement for the Garden.[NEWLINE]Increases the rate of [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Great People generation in City. Receive 30 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture as an instant boost in City when a [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age begins. +3 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and [ICON_GOLD] Gold to all guilds in City.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PERSIA_PAIRIDAEZA_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Pairidaeza is the Persian unique Garden replacement. In addition to the normal bonuses of a Garden, the Pairidaeza provides culture and gold to all guilds in the City. The beginning of every Golden Age produces culture for each city with a Pairidaeza, so be sure to build them in every city, even if you do not have a guild.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PERSIA_PAIRIDAEZA_TEXT">
			<Text>
				A pairidaeza is a specific style of garden consisting of cultivated land within an enclosure. Also known as a “paradise garden,” the pairidaeza is thought to originate in the time of the Assyrian Empire. Its rectangular construction serves to contrast the external wildness of nature with an ordered and beautiful garden. Water was often an important element of their construction—ponds, canals, or even fountains flowed freely within the walls.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]

				As a tool of state, they were invaluable in flaunting a kingdom’s ability to bring life to an area that would otherwise have none. The Achaemenid dynasty melded the pairidaeza with their royal hunting parks, a not so subtle way to show their command over both their empire and the natural world within it.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Pitz -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 16/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MAYA_KATUN_AHAW">
			<Text>K'atun Ahaw</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MAYA_KATUN_AHAW_HELP">
			<Text>Unit gains 5% [ICON_DEFENSE] Combat Strength [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]every 20 Game Turns[ENDCOLOR]. Effect stacks [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]4[ENDCOLOR] times.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MAYA_KATUN_AHAW_1">
			<Text>Hun K'atun Ahaw</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MAYA_KATUN_AHAW_1_HELP">
			<Text>+5 XP. +5% [ICON_DEFENSE] Combat Strength.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MAYA_KATUN_AHAW_2">
			<Text>Ka'a K'atun Ahaw</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MAYA_KATUN_AHAW_2_HELP">
			<Text>+10 XP. +10% [ICON_DEFENSE] Combat Strength. +5% [ICON_DEFENSE] Combat Strength [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]in Forest and Jungle[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MAYA_KATUN_AHAW_3">
			<Text>Oox K'atun Ahaw</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MAYA_KATUN_AHAW_3_HELP">
			<Text>+10 XP. +10% [ICON_DEFENSE] Combat Strength. +15% [ICON_DEFENSE] Combat Strength [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]in Forest and Jungle[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MAYA_KATUN_AHAW_4">
			<Text>Kan K'atun Ahaw</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MAYA_KATUN_AHAW_4_HELP">
			<Text>+15 XP. +10% [ICON_DEFENSE] Combat Strength. +5% [ICON_DEFENSE] Combat Strength [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]in Forest and Jungle[ENDCOLOR]. +10 HP [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Heal inside Friendly Territory[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MAYA_PITZ">
			<Text>Ball Court</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MAYA_PITZ_HELP">
			<Text>Unique Mayan replacement for the Arena.[NEWLINE]Receive 10 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science and 10 [ICON_PEACE Faith] at the beginning of every B'ak'tun. Land Units trained in this City Receive the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]K'atun Ahaw[ENDCOLOR] promotion, gaining new abilities every 20 turns[NEWLINE]Barracks, Forge, and Armory in this City gain +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production. Reduces [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Boredom.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MAYA_PITZ_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Ball Court is the Mayan unique building, replacing the Arena. In addition to the normal bonuses of an Arena, the Ball Court provides Science and Faith at the end of every long count. Land units trained in a City with a Ball Court receive the 'K'atun Ahaw' promotion, which grants new abilities for every 20 turns the unit has been alive.				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Hun: 5XP, 5% :c5strength: CS
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Ka'a: 10XP, 10% Combat Strength, 5% Combat Strength in Forest/Jungle
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Oox: 10XP, 10% Combat Strength, 15% Combat Strength in Forest/Jungle
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Kan: 15XP, 10% Combat Strength, 15% Combat Strength CS in Forest/Jungle, +10 HP on Heal in friendly territory</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MAYA_PITZ_TEXT">
				<Text>The Mesoamerican Ball Game, or 'Pitz' is a game of ritual and cultural significance among the Mayan people. The object of the game is to keep the ball in play for as long as possible by striking back and forth within an sloped arena using the hips, though some variations allowed for elbows, shoulders and even rackets. The earliest archaeological evidence of the game come from a court estimated to be 3400 years old.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
			Over 1300 different ballcourts have been found within Mayan ruins, with relatively little variation in size or layout over thousands of years. Every court is shaped as a narrow alley with gently sloping walls on either side and an enclosed endzone on either side. This gave the court a roughly I-shaped layout. Later versions of the ballcourts include hoops at the midpoint, suspended on the walls. Actually sending a ball through the ring must have been a rare occurrence, since the players could not use their hands or even feet to guide the ball. Moreover, the rings were only slightly larger than the ball itself and were located at no small distance from the playing alley.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
			The game was more than a mere sporting event to the Mayan people, perhaps serving as a substitute for war in the case of a dispute between cities. Later Classical Mayan art suggests a link between the ball game and ritual sacrifice, with winners being decapitated as an offering to the gods. The Maya Twin Myth of the Popol Vuh, describes the game between the Hero Twins, Hunahpu and Xbalanque, and lord of the underworld, One Death and Seven Death. The game was played so the Hero Twins might recover Hunahpu's head which was being used as a ball by the lords (Hunahpu was using a squash for his head until his real one could be recovered).</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Pancerny -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 16/10/2017 modified 30/10/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_POLAND_BOGURODZICA">
			<Text>Bogurodzica</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_POLAND_BOGURODZICA_HELP">
			<Text>Unit gains [ICON_PEACE] Faith [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Kill[ENDCOLOR]. Bonus doubled [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Barbarian Kills[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_POLAND_GRUNWALD">
			<Text>Grunwald</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_POLAND_GRUNWALD_HELP">
			<Text>+25% [ICON_STRENGTH] Defense Bonus [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]in Forest and Jungle[ENDCOLOR] and +10% [ICON_STRENGTH] Defense Bonus [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Marsh[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_POLAND_PANCERNY">
			<Text>Pancerny</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_POLAND_PANCERNY_HELP">
			<Text>A sturdy Mounted Skirmisher. Only the Polish may build it. Earns [ICON_PEACE] Faith from each enemy killed and double the amount from Barbarians. This unit is stronger in both defense and offense than the Heavy Skirmisher, and has additional protection against Ranged Units.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_POLAND_PANCERNY_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Pancerny is a Polish unique unit, replacing the Heavy Skirmisher. It has stronger attack and defense than the Heavy Skirmisher, and takes reduced damage from Ranged attacks. The Pancerny also earns Faith for each enemy killed. As mounted unit, the Pancerny is vulnerable to Pikemen.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_POLAND_PANCERNY_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Towarzysz  Pancerny (Mailed Companion) was a rank of Polish cavalryman from the 10th to 18th century, named for their chainmail armor. During the rule of Mieszko I and Boleslaw I Chrobry in the late 10th century, Pancerni were members of the prince's own force, where their use of mail armor made them unique among the army (druzhyna). [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				With the advent of heavy cavalry the Pancerni often worked in concert with the newer and more heavily armed husaria, augmenting a cavalry charge and chasing down routing enemy soldiers. By the second half of the 17th century, they represented approximately 70% of all soldiers in the Polish military, fighting against Cossacks, Tatars, and the Swedish invasion during the Great Northern War. Once distinct entities, the Husaria and Pancerni were eventually combined to form the ‘Kawaleria Narodowa’, the Polish-Lithuanian National Cavalry. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]

				Pancerni were organized into companies, with each company consisting of 60 to 200 horsemen. Exceptionally well-armored, they used chainmail or platemail armor for upper body, vambraces, helmets, and buckler shields. The most common armaments were sabres, reflex bows and, with the arrival of gunpowder, flintlock pistols and carbines. 
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Pogost -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 14/10/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RUSSIA_POGOST_1">
			<Text>Pogost - Stage 1: Market</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RUSSIA_POGOST_2">
			<Text>Pogost - Stage 2: Intendant's Residention</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RUSSIA_POGOST_3">
			<Text>Pogost - Stage 3: Eastern Orthodox Church</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RUSSIA_POGOST_1_HELP">
			<Text>Gains traits at Banking and Architecture Technology. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Stage 1: Grants +3 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and additional [ICON_GOLD] Gold to all [ICON_SWAP] Trade Routes to/from this city respectively.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Unlocks access to Stage 2.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RUSSIA_POGOST_2_HELP">
			<Text>Stage 2: +1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science. Get more [ICON_GOLD] Gold from [ICON_CONNECTED] City Connections and [ICON_CITIZEN] Population at Banking. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Unlocks access to Stage 3.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RUSSIA_POGOST_3_HELP">
			<Text>Stage 3: Adds [ICON_PEACE] Faith to Shrines, Temples and Churches in the same city at Architecture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RUSSIA_POGOST_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique Russian replacement for the Customs House. Initially, Pogosts are comparatively lackluster, but they develop new traits as the game progresses. The Pogost provides modest increases in gold from trade and culture, then gains significant boosts to gold and science at its second stage, and provides modest boosts to faith generation in its final stage.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RUSSIA_POGOST_TEXT">
			<Text>In many medieval Russian states, Pogosts began as inns and lodging for the nobility and priesthood, but may have doubled as community centers and trading hubs. By the end of the 10th century, however, Pogosts had evolved into administrative and legislative hubs throughout the Slavic states. By 1775 the last Pogost-led administrative district was abolished, and the buildings were repurposed as parishes of the Eastern Orthodox Church.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Prau -->
		<!-- Created by pineappledan; incorporated by adan_eslavo on 23/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_INDONESIA_FLYING_THE_AMA">
			<Text>Flying the Ama</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_INDONESIA_FLYING_THE_AMA_HELP">
			<Text>+2 [ICON_ARROW_RIGHT] Movement Points. Lost after unit upgrade.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDONESIA_PRAU">
			<Text>Prau</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDONESIA_PRAU_TEXT">
			<Text>
				One of the most ancient of seaworthy boat designs, the prau, also known as proa or perahu, are wooden sailing vessels consisting of a large hull (vaka) and a small hull (ama) set in parallel by a crossbeam (akas). Prau are believed to have been developed in Micronesia in the first century AD, spreading quickly throughout southeast Asia. Western accounts of prau first appear in the 16th century, when Magellan made note of their agility in his fateful trip to the Philippines.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]When sailing in strong winds, the crew walk between the hulls along the akas to counterbalance the force of the sail. A skilled prau crew can balance so as to lift the ama out of the water, called "flying the ama", and skim the ocean's surface to reach incredible speeds. Prau continue to be used worldwide, and modern designs can exceed 95km/h in favourable winds. This makes prau some of the fastest ships in the world; not bad for a 2,000 year old!
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDONESIA_PRAU_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Prau is faster and cheaper than the Trireme it replaces and ignores zone of control. It is great for early game scouting and raiding.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDONESIA_PRAU_HELP">
			<Text>Early naval Unit. Replaces the Trireme. Only Indonesia may build it. It's available earlier, moves quickly and ignores zone of control.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Penteconter -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 30/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PENTECONTER">
			<Text>Penteconter</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PENTECONTER_HELP">
			<Text>Dominant Classical Era Naval Unit used to own the seas well into the Medieval Era with its ranged attack.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PENTECONTER_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The first naval unit with a ranged attack. It cannot end its turn in Deep Ocean tiles outside of the city borders.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PENTECONTER_TEXT">
			<Text>The penteconter was an ancient Greek Galley, used for trade, piracy and warfare. The ship was rowed by 50 oarsmen arranged in 2 rows of 25, making the ship long, but relatively narrow. This design made the boat relatively quick, but difficult to turn during a naval engagement.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Pracinha -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_EXPEDITIONARY_FORCE">
			<Text>
				Expeditionary Force
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_EXPEDITIONARY_FORCE_HELP">
			<Text>
				Gain +1% [ICON_STRENGTH] Strength for every Tile between the [ICON_CAPITAL] Capital and this Unit.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_TOURISM">
			<Text>
				Tourism from Victories
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_TOURISM_HELP">
			<Text>
				Earn Tourism toward all civs for each enemy killed.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Prowler -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 20/10/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_IROQUOIS_PROWLER">
			<Text>Prowler</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_IROQUOIS_PROWLER_HELP">
			<Text>A nimble attacker excelling in rough terrain. Only the Iroquois may build it. Cheaper than the Musketman, this Unit can attack from behind obstacles and retreat after enemy attack.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_IROQUOIS_PROWLER_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Prowler is cheap unit that makes perfect use from surrounding rough terrain. His "Indirect Fire" promotion allows him to attack unseen from deep forests and hills, with the aid of reconnaissance or friendly borders. When attacked by an enemy unit, he can withdraw from combat. The prowler's evasiveness makes him an ideal guerilla Unit.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_IROQUOIS_PROWLER_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Unlike many other tribes, the Iroquois had easy access to trade goods at Dutch posts along the Hudson River, and traded for various goods and luxuries. Weapons of war, such as the iron axe and musket, were highly sought after, and by the 1640s the Iroquois were well-equipped to fight their traditional Huron and Algonquian enemies. Common muskets were given in exchange for pelts and food, but often of lighter and smaller caliber than military-grade muskets. The British feared giving high-quality weapons to people who could turn against them, but the Iroquois often found the smaller weapons more suitable to rough terrain anyways. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				War tactics were changed after the Iroquois' acquisition of firearms. The lethality of their new weapons put the Iroquois, never a highly populous group, in a precarious position. The tribes' custom of absorbing refugees and prisoners of war changed as fewer and fewer warriors survived clashes with European arms. Great armies walking with prominent chiefs and shamans were replaced with guerilla tactics, small bands of troops guided by commanders. 
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Qizilbash -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 29/10/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_PERSIA_SAFAVI_AGITATOR">
			<Text>Safavi Agitator</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_PERSIA_SAFAVI_AGITATOR_HELP">
			<Text>Unit gains [ICON_PEACE] Faith, [ICON_GOLD] Gold and [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age Points each turn if it is standing [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]inside Enemy Territory[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PERSIA_QIZILBASH">
			<Text>Qizilbash</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PERSIA_QIZILBASH_HELP">
			<Text>Unique replacement for the Lancer. Generates +1 [ICON_PEACE] Faith, +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold, and +2  [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age Points every turn in enemy territory. Can always be purchased with [ICON_PEACE] Faith. Only the Persians may build it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PERSIA_QIZILBASH_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Qizilbash is the Unique Persian replacement for the Lancer. Stronger than the Lancer, the Qizilbash also generates Faith, Gold and Golden Age Points for every turn they spend in enemy territory. This unit can also be purchased with Faith without needing a religious tenet. Maintaining a strong presence in enemy territory allows Persia to generate Faith for more Qizilbash, and trigger more Golden Ages to increase your army's power.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PERSIA_QIZILBASH_TEXT">
			<Text>Qizilbash was originally a pejorative for the followers of the Safawiyyah Sufi order, who distinguished themselves by wearing bright crimson headwear. The name, which means red headed, became a mark of pride among the Qizilbash, who organized into a Shi'ite Islamic military society in the late 15th century. Though primarily of Turkman origin, the Qizilbash proved instrumental in the establishment of the Safavid Dynasty in Iran.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
			In a campaign to avenge the death of his father Haydar, Ismail I, led 7000 Qizilbash warriors to destroy the Aq Qoyunlu force of 30 000 in Azerbaijan, and establish the Safavid State. By 1510, eleven years later, Ismail brought all of Iran under his control, the first ethnically Iranian monarch to unify Iran in over 850 years. Though they had made him a powerful king, Ismail feared the power and influence of the tribal qizilbash over the Iranian peoples. Ismail and his successors would spend the next 80 years diminishing the political power of the Qizilbash, replacing them with ghulam slave soldiers from the Caucasus. Nevertheless, the Qizilbash held an honoured position within the Safavid empire, both on the battlefield and in the Safavid court.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Qila -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 5/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INDIA_QILA">
			<Text>Mughal Fort</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INDIA_QILA_HELP">
			<Text>Unique replacement for the Castle. 10% of [ICON_FOOD] Food is converted into [ICON_CULTURE] Culture every turn and 1 [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Great Artist Point. Contains 1 slot for a Great Work of Art. Gains +3 [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism at Flight. Requires Walls in City.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INDIA_QILA_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Qila is the unique Indian replacement for the Castle. In addition to the normal bonuses of the Castle, the Qila generates Food, and Culture. 10% of [ICON_FOOD] Food is converted into Culture every turn and 1 Great Artist Point. Contains 1 slot for a Great Work of Art. Additional Tourism when Flight is Researched.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INDIA_QILA_TEXT">
			<Text>The Mughals were an Islamic empire that invaded India in the 15th century, and ruled most of the sub-continent until the mid 19th. During their rule, they constructed elaborate forts across the countryside which served as administrative centers and living quarters for the occupiers. These forts were beautiful structures, fitting palaces for the rulers of a vast empire. Several--including the magnificent "Lahore Fort" and Red Fort of Agra--survive today and remain as some of the largest tourist attractions to India, monuments to the Mughals' power and style.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Ranch -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AMERICA_RANCH">
			<Text>
				Ranch
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AMERICA_RANCH_TEXT">
			<Text>A ranch is a type of farm primarily for the raising of grazing livestock such as cattle or sheep. Ranching is also a method used to raise less common livestock such as elk, American bison or even ostrich, emu, and alpacas.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Ranches generally consist of large areas, but may be of nearly any size. If the ranch includes arable or irrigated land, the ranch may also engage in a limited amount of farming, raising crops for feeding the animals, such as hay and feed grains. As settlers from the United States moved west, they brought cattle breeds developed on the east coast and in Europe along with them, and adapted their management to the drier lands of the west by borrowing key elements of the Spanish vaquero culture. Vast swathes of the American interior were converted to ranchland in a process of colonization which left an indelible mark on the American psyche.  Legends of the frontier, the Old West, Cowboys and Indians still permeate American culture, informing their sense of independence, enterprising spirit and mastery over nature.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AMERICA_RANCH_STRATEGY">
			<Text>
				The Ranch is the American replacement for the Stable. In addition to the regular abilities of the Stable, the Ranch increases border growth, and gives [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture when borders grow. Only America may build it.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AMERICA_RANCH_HELP">
			<Text>
				Unique American Stable replacement. +33% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production when building Mounted Units. Increases the Military Unit Supply Cap from Population in the City by 10%.[NEWLINE]+25% border growth rate in city. Whenever the city borders expand, gain 10 [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, scaling with Era.
			</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Riad -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VP_RIAD">
			<Text>Riad</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VP_RIAD_TEXT">
			<Text>A riad is a traditional Moroccan house with an interior garden or courtyard. The riads were inward focused, which allowed for family privacy and protection from the weather in Morocco. In the central garden of traditional riads there are often four orange or lemon trees and possibly a fountain. The walls of the riads are usually adorned with Arabic calligraphy with quotes from the Quran.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The style of these riads has changed over the years, but the basic form is still used in designs today. Recently there has been a surge in interest in this form of house after a new vogue of renovation in towns such as Marrakech and Essaouira where many of these often-crumbling buildings have been restored to their former glory. Many riads are now used as hotels or restaurants.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VP_RIAD_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Riad is the Moroccan unique replacement for the Garden. In addition to the bonuses of a normal Garden, the Riad grants culture in the city for every 5 citizens in the city, and Gold generation in the city is greatly increased during a Golden Age. Trade routes originating from the city generate additional [ICON_GOLD] Gold, [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, and [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Great Merchant Points.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VP_RIAD_HELP">
			<Text>Unique Moroccan replacement for the Garden. Trade routes originating in the city gain +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold, [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, and [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Great Merchant Points per turn. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+30% [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Great People generation in this City. [NEWLINE]+15% [ICON_GOLD] Gold in the city during a [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Sachem's Council -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 14/10/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_IROQUOIS_DIPLOMATIC_RECIPROCITY">
			<Text>Diplomatic Reciprocity</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_IROQUOIS_DIPLOMATIC_RECIPROCITY_HELP">
			<Text>After creating an [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Embassy[ENDCOLOR] its yields are permanently added to your Capital's revenue if target City-State [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]is an Ally[ENDCOLOR] or only half, if it [COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]is not[ENDCOLOR] one.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_IROQUOIS_SACHEMS_COUNCIL">
			<Text>Sachem's Council</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_IROQUOIS_SACHEMS_COUNCIL_HELP">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture for every 5 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens, +2 [ICON_DIPLOMAT] Great Diplomat Points, +2 [ICON_RES_PAPER] Paper +10% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production of Diplomatic Units and 1 Civil Servant Specialist Slots.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]All Councils gain +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, and all Chanceries gain +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Global Happiness for every Defensive Pact or War.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Great Diplomats gain the [COLOR_GREEN]Diplomatic Reciprocity[ENDCOLOR] Promotion.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_FOOD] Food in City for every City-State Friend, and +2 [ICON_PEACE] Faith for every Ally.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_IROQUOIS_SACHEMS_COUNCIL_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique Iroquoian replacement for the Scrivener's Office. In addition to the normal bonuses provided by the Scrivener's Office, the Sachem's Council  provides faster generation of Great Diplomat units. Great Diplomats also receive a unique promotion, providing Science, Culture and gold for every embassy founded. All Councils in your empire also gain +1 Culture, and all Chanceries gain +2 Gold. The Sachem's Council also provides Happiness for every Defensive Pact and Declared War involving the Iroquois.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_IROQUOIS_SACHEMS_COUNCIL_TEXT">
			<Text>
				According to oral tradition, the five tribes of the Iroquois devoted much energy toward fighting and killing each other until the 1500s. It was at this time that the five tribes united into a powerful confederation, forming an elaborate political system including a bicameral (two-house) legislature much like the modern U.S. Congress. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				In accordance with their unwritten constitution, the confederacy was represented by 50 delegates, or Sachems – all men, each chosen by the clan mother. The 17 sachems from the Seneca and Mohawk tribes met in one house while the 19 Oneida and Cayuga met in the other. The 14 Onondaga sachems acted as tie-breakers and had the power to veto decisions made by the others. In addition to Sachem, who met on Onondaga land to cast their votes, there were advisory council members called Pine Trees. Pine Trees could be men or women appointed for their heroic feats and accomplishments. In 1715 the Tuscarora joined the league, and it was renamed the League of Six Nations. Benjamin Franklin’s dealings with the Iroquois led him to model the United States’ government after theirs. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
					“The soil of the earth from one end of the land to the other is the property of the people who inhabit it. By birthright the Ongwehonweh (original beings) are the owners of the soil which they own and occupy and none other may hold it. The same law has been held from the oldest times. The Great Creator has made us of the one blood and of the same soil he made us and as only different tongues constitute different nations he established different hunting grounds and territories and made boundary lines between them...” [NEWLINE]
				-Excerpt from the Iroquois Constitution
			</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Sambadrome -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VP_SAMBADROME">
			<Text>
				Sambadrome
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VP_SAMBADROME_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Sambadrome (Sambódromo in Portuguese language) is the name given to an exhibition place for the Samba schools parades during Carnaval in Brazil. A sambadrome generally consists of tiered spectator viewing areas surrounding a long alley for the schools to parade down.  The parades attract many thousands of Brazilians and foreign tourists each year.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VP_SAMBADROME_STRATEGY">
			<Text>
				The Sambadrome is the unique Brazilian replacement for the Opera House. In addition to the bonuses of an Opera House, it provides more Culture than the Opera House, and it also provides Golden Age Points and Tourism. The Sambadrome comes with a Musician specialist slot.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VP_SAMBADROME_HELP">
			<Text>
				Unique Brazilian replacement for the Opera House. +7% [ICON_CULTURE] Culture in the City. +33% [ICON_GREAT_MUSICIAN] Great Musician Rate in the City, and all Musicians' Guilds produce +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and +2 [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age Points. +3 [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism at Radio.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Scythed Chariot -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 26/10/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_CELTS_SCYTHE">
			<Text>Scythe</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_CELTS_SCYTHE_HELP">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]On Move[ENDCOLOR] unit inflicts flat damage [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]to all new adjacent Enemy Units[ENDCOLOR]. +1 Sight.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_CELTS_CARNYX">
			<Text>Carnyx</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_CELTS_CARNYX_HELP">
			<Text>+10% [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Ranged Combat Strength vs [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Archer and Melee Units[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CELTS_SCYTHED_CHARIOT">
			<Text>Scythed Chariot</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CELTS_SCYTHED_CHARIOT_HELP">
			<Text>A dangerous unit on open terrain. Only the Celts may build it. This unit is stronger against Archer and Melee Units, has more vision and ignores enemy Zone of Control. After moving, all newly adjacent enemy units take 10 damage. Moving into rough terrain ends all movement.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CELTS_SCYTHED_CHARIOT_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Scythed Chariot is a Celtic unique unit made for destroying enemy lines. Enemies take damage whenever the Scythed Chariot moves adjacent to them, making this unit deadly in open terrain. Make every move count to maximize damage, but be careful not to leave your Chariots exposed to enemies on their turn. A mounted unit, the Scythed Chariot is vulnerable to Spearmen.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CELTS_SCYTHED_CHARIOT_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Scythed chariots are modified war chariots with long blades extending from the wheel axels. Though often dismissed as fanciful storytelling, the use of these war machines has been confirmed in at least a few more credible sources. Scythed chariots featured prominently during the Greco-Persian War, though to little effect against Macedon's well-trained infantry. Use of scythed chariots has been ascribed to Pictish, Irish and Iceni armies, but the claims are often of dubious validity. The only report of a scythed chariot in Britain outside of Roman propaganda comes from the Irish Ulster Cycle, during the adventures of Chu Chulainn. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Although chariots had fallen out of use in continental Europe from the end of the 3rd century BC, Caesar found that they remained significant in British warfare. Caesar encountered both Celtic cavalry and chariots and described how these warriors would throw javelins from their vehicles before dismounting to fight on foot. Celtic soldiers could return to their chariots to quickly retreat or redeploy. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				“They make war not only on horseback but also from 2 horse chariots and cars armed in the Gallic fashion – they call them ‘Covinni’ - on which they use axles equipped with scythes.” [NEWLINE]
				- Pomponius Mela
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Seir Morb -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 9/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SIAM_COASTAL_CANNON">
			<Text>Crouching Tiger Cannon</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SIAM_COASTAL_CANNON_HELP">
			<Text>+25% [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Ranged Combat Strength vs [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Naval Units[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SIAM_CROACHING_TIGER">
			<Text>Crouching Tiger</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SIAM_CROACHING_TIGER_HELP">
			<Text>+15% [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Ranged Combat Strength [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]for every Movement Point left[ENDCOLOR] on Seir Morb. Bonus caps at 60%.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SIAM_CROACHING_TIGER_1">
			<Text>Crouching Tiger I</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SIAM_CROACHING_TIGER_1_HELP">
			<Text>+15% [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Ranged Combat Strength.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SIAM_CROACHING_TIGER_2">
			<Text>Crouching Tiger II</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SIAM_CROACHING_TIGER_2_HELP">
			<Text>+30% [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Ranged Combat Strength.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SIAM_CROACHING_TIGER_3">
			<Text>Crouching Tiger III</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SIAM_CROACHING_TIGER_3_HELP">
			<Text>+45% [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Ranged Combat Strength.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SIAM_CROACHING_TIGER_4">
			<Text>Eye of the Tiger</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SIAM_CROACHING_TIGER_4_HELP">
			<Text>+60% [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Ranged Combat Strength.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SIAM_SEIR_MORB">
			<Text>Seir Morb</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SIAM_SEIR_MORB_HELP">
			<Text>Unique Industrial Era Unit.  Only the Siamese may build it. More powerful than the Field Gun it replaces and has a bonus against naval units instead of a penalty, but does not have the [COLOR_RED]Bonus vs Cities[ENDCOLOR] promotion. Deals more damage in a turn the less the unit has moved and receives [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Cover I[ENDCOLOR] and [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Cover II[ENDCOLOR] promotions for free.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SIAM_SEIR_MORB_STRATEGY">
			<Text>A powerful coastal defense cannon, the Seir Morb is more powerful than the Field Gun it replaces, especially against naval targets, but deals less damage to cities. The Seir Morb receives a combat boost for every remaining movement point when attacking, so pick a good spot and keep it steady.  Location, Location, Location.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SIAM_SEIR_MORB_TEXT">
			<Text>Despite Siam's remarkable diplomacy, they did at times come into conflict with the great imperial powers which threated to swallow them whole. When the French set their sights on Laos, the Siamese mistakenly believed the English would aid them in their plight, and prepared for war. The Seir Morb ("Crouching Tiger") were the most technologically advanced cannons in the Siamese arsenal at the time; coastal artillery which could destroy any French boats foolish enough to enter their harbours. No amount of raw power, however, can account for corruption and disorganization. The French managed to establish their beachheads, and the coastal artillery of Thailand remained unused. It turns out that the proper use of a cannon involves firing it.</Text>
		</Row>


		<!-- Shophet -->
		<!-- Created by pineappledan -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_JFD_SHOPHET">
			<Text>Shophet</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_JFD_SHOPHET_HELP">
			<Text>Unique replacement for the Great General. Disembarks onto water tiles as a Great Admiral. Causes friendly units beginning in the same or adjacent tile to ignore enemy Zone of Control for that turn.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_JFD_SHOPHET_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Shophet is the unique Great General replacement for Carthage, for Hannibal. This unit causes all friendly units beginning in the same or an adjacent tile to ignore an enemy's Zone of Control for that turn. In addition, whenever this unit embarks into a water tile, it becomes a Great Admiral. It returns to Great General status upon disembarking into a city. Use a Shophet to supplement your military strategies when waging war against other civilizations.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_JFD_SHOPHET_TEXT">
			<Text>In the various independent city states constituting Phoenicia proper (coasts of present Lebanon and Syria) and its "Punic" Mediterranean colonies a shofet (in Punic, suffet or suffete) was a non-royal magistrate granted control over a city-state, sometimes functioning much in the same way as a Roman consul.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The term is mostly widely known from the suffetes of Carthage, a former Phoenician colony. Following the overthrow of its monarchy in the 5th century BC, Carthage was ruled by a number of aristocratic councils presided over by two suffetes, who served in similar capacity to Roman consuls.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_JFD_SHOPHET_GENERAL">
			<Text>Admiralty</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_JFD_SHOPHET_GENERAL_HELP">
			<Text>This unit may embark as a Great Admiral.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_JFD_SHOPHET_ADMIRAL">
			<Text>Commandeering</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_JFD_SHOPHET_ADMIRAL_HELP">
			<Text>This unit may disembark as a Great General (must be moved into a city first).</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_JFD_SHOPHET_ZOC">
			<Text>Nearby Shophet</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_JFD_SHOPHET_ZOC_HELP">
			<Text>Ignores enemy Zone of Control.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Unique Names-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_1">
			<Text>Bomilcar</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_2">
			<Text>Hamilcar Barca</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_3">
			<Text>Hannibal</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_4">
			<Text>Hannibal Barca</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_5">
			<Text>Hasdrubal II</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_6">
			<Text>Hasdrubal Gisco</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_7">
			<Text>Hasdrubal the Boetharch</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_8">
			<Text>Mago I Justin</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_9">
			<Text>Mago II</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_10">
			<Text>Mago III</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_11">
			<Text>Himilco I</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_12">
			<Text>Himilco II</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_13">
			<Text>Hasdrubal the Fair</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_14">
			<Text>Ad Herbal</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_15">
			<Text>Carthalo</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_16">
			<Text>Hannibal Monomachus</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_17">
			<Text>Maharbal</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_18">
			<Text>Sophonisba</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_19">
			<Text>Hannibal the Rhodian</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_20">
			<Text>Hanno the Elder</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_21">
			<Text>Hanno the Great</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_22">
			<Text>Aderbaal</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_23">
			<Text>Bodashtart</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_24">
			<Text>Philosir</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_25">
			<Text>Abdmelqart</Text>
		</Row>
	
		<!-- Shotelai -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 12/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ETHIOPIA_MAIM">
			<Text>Maim</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ETHIOPIA_MAIM_HELP">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]After Attack[ENDCOLOR] Defending Enemy Unit is marked. Marked unit has reduced [ICON_ARROW_RIGHT] Movement [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]next turn[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ETHIOPIA_MAIM_ON_UNIT">
			<Text>Hobbled</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ETHIOPIA_MAIM_ON_UNIT_HELP">
			<Text>Unit has reduced movement [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]next turn[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ETHIOPIA_MAIM_2_ON_UNIT">
			<Text>Maimed</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ETHIOPIA_MAIM_2_ON_UNIT_HELP">
			<Text>Unit has reduced movement [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]this turn[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ETHIOPIA_HOOKED_WEAPON">
			<Text>Hooked Weapon</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ETHIOPIA_HOOKED_WEAPON_HELP">
			<Text>+25% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength vs [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Mounted Units[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ETHIOPIA_SHOTELAI">
			<Text>Shotel Swordsman</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ETHIOPIA_SHOTELAI_HELP">
			<Text>Unique Medieval Era Unit. Only the Ethiopians may build it. Has bonus damage against Mounted Units, unlike the Longswordsman it replaces. Enemies attacked by this Unit have -1 [ICON_MOVES] Movement on their next turn.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ETHIOPIA_SHOTELAI_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique Ethiopian replacement for the Longswordsman. This unit specializes in combating Mounted opponents and hobbling retreating units. </Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ETHIOPIA_SHOTELAI_TEXT">
			<Text>Shotel are dramatically curved double-edged swords used exclusively by the ancient Ethiopian Empire. Almost semicircular, the shotel could be used to hook shields, or even reach around them to strike an opponent. The sword could also be used to hook and unhorse a mounted soldier, bringing them to the ground. Warriors armed with Shotel were called 'Shotelai'. Elite corps of these Shotelai were employed by the armies of Amda Seyon I, comprising an elite force within his host.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- SPAD -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 11/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_FRANCE_SPAD">
			<Text>SPAD S.VII</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_FRANCE_SPAD_HELP">
			<Text>Unique Modern Era Unit. Only the French may build it. This Unit is cheaper, and has a longer range than the Triplane it replaces. Receives the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Quick Study[ENDCOLOR] Promotion for free.[NEWLINE]Does not require Oil.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_FRANCE_SPAD_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The SPAD S.VII is France's early air superiority fighter. With a longer range and a cheaper cost and no need for oil, these fighters will help create a strong French presence in the air. The SPAD S.VII's quick study ability ensures these fighters are the toughest aces in the sky.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_FRANCE_SPAD_TEXT">
			<Text>
				World War I saw rapid technological and tactical changes in how wars were fought, not the least of which was the first use of aircraft for scouting, support, and bombing. These new machines opened an entirely new theatre of war, a new avenue to gain an advantage over the enemy. Despite their promise, the first aircraft were slow, clumsy, and unreliable thanks to their underpowered combustion engines. This all changed in 1915 when Marc Birgikt invented a new V8 engine boasting 150 horsepower and weighing only 330 pounds. The French high command saw this new motor’s obvious value as an aircraft engine and set about in commissioning a new fighter aircraft designed around this new powerhouse: The Societe Pour L'Aviation et ses Derives, or ‘SPAD’ S. VII. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				By late 1916 SPAD VIIs were beginning to see action, and saw wide adoption by allied pilots for the rest of the war. Though lacking in maneuverability compared to the older Nieuport fighters, the SPAD VII more than made up for this deficiency in sheer speed, travelling in excess of 205kmph, and capable of safe dives of more than 400kmph. Entirely new tactics had to be created by pilots to leverage this unmatched speed, which gave the SPAD the ability to safely avoid or escape pitched battles. The added stability in diving was especially appreciated over the old Nieuports, which had a bad habit of shedding their wings during maneuvers. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Air superiority became a constant arms race against newer and better German designs and engines. By the end of the war, the SPAD VII's single .303 Vickers machine gun was outmatched by German fighters, which carried at least two machine guns. The heavier and faster SPAD XIII replaced the SPAD VII by late 1917, and would carry France to the end of the War. Though at times unreliable and hard to maneuver, the SPAD series would go down in history as the fastest and most powerful of WWI fighters, and continued to be used by the French as a training plane until it was retired in 1928.
			</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Standschützen -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VP_STANDSCHUTZEN">
			<Text>
				Schützenstand
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VP_STANDSCHUTZEN_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The Schützenstand were originally rifle guilds and rifle companies that had been formed in the 15th and 16th centuries, and were involved time and again in military operations within the borders of the Austrian County of Tyrol. A Standschütze was a member of a Schützenstand ("shooting club"), into which he was enrolled, which automatically committed him to the voluntary, military protection of the state of Tyrol (and Vorarlberg). In effect they were a type of Tyrolean local militia or home guard.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VP_STANDSCHUTZEN_STRATEGY">
			<Text>
				The Schützenstand is an Austrian unique building, replacing the Arsenal. It is cheaper than the Arsenal and provides more defense. It allows for faster construction of land military units in the city. It also provides +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture per city-state ally.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VP_STANDSCHUTZEN_HELP">
			<Text>
				+2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture per city-state ally. +20% production toward land military units.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Increases city Defense Strength by 25 and Hit Points by 200. Military Units supplied by this City's population increased by 10%.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Tersane -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 1/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_OTTOMANS_TERSANE">
			<Text>Tersane</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_OTTOMANS_TERSANE_HELP">
			<Text>Unique Medieval Era Building. [NEWLINE]When a Sea Trade Route originating here and targeting another Civ is completed, receive a [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism boost with the civ based on your recent [ICON_CULTURE] Culture output.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+50% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production towards Cargo Ships and +30% [ICON_PRODUCTION] towards Naval Melee Units. Naval Melee Units trained in this City receive the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Prize Ships[ENDCOLOR] Promotion.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Only Ottomans may build it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_OTTOMANS_TERSANE_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Tersane is the unique Harbor replacement of the Ottomans. In addition to the bonuses of a Harbor, the Tersane increases the yields of work boats. The building also greatly improves production towards trade and military vessels, greatly improving the Ottoman's naval capabilities. All Melee Ships built in this city also receive the Prize Ships promotion, allowing them to capture defeated enemy units.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_OTTOMANS_TERSANE_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The Turkish word 'Tersane' is derived from the Venetian 'darsane', from which the English word 'arsenal' is also derived. Though never at the forefront of shipbuilding technology, the Ottomans enjoyed over a century of naval dominance in the Mediterranean following their conquest of Constantinople in 1453. The largest Tersane, constructed at the Golden Horn across from Constantinople, housed over 160 docks, drydocks, storehouses and supply depots, making it one of the largest centers of trade, commerce and industry in the Mediterranean. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Ottoman naval power was maintained through its tremendous shipbuilding capacity, as well as its allegiances to the Barbary corsairs of North Africa. This pre-eminence was finally ended at the battle of Lepanto, where a combined Spanish and Venetian armada delivered a crushing defeat to the Ottoman's, capturing or destroying more than two thirds of the Ottoman's navy. Their response was to build 250 new vessels within six months. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				"You come to see how we bear our misfortune. But I would have you know the difference between your loss and ours. In wresting Cyprus from you, we deprived you of an arm; in defeating our fleet, you have only shaved our beard. [NEWLINE] Grand Vizier Mehmed Sokullu, on the defeat at Lepanto, and the capture of Cyprus, which the Ottomans had taken earlier the same year
			</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Tophet -->
		<!-- Created by pineappledan -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TOPHET">
			<Text>Tophet</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TOPHET_HELP">
			<Text>Provides [ICON_PEACE] Faith and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture in the City. [NEWLINE]Receive 10 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture in the City whenever a Unit is purchased, scaling with era, and Units purchased in this city receive full XP from buildings.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TOPHET_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Tophet is the unique Shrine replacement for Carthage. In addition to the normal bonuses of a Shrine, the Tophet provides Culture whenever a unit is purchased in the City. Military Units purchased in a City with a Tophet are not affected by the normal half XP penalty for purchasing.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TOPHET_TEXT">
			<Text>
				"Tophet" is a Hebrew term for a place of worship and human sacrifice to the Canaanite gods, and has become a colorful synonym for hell within Judeo-Christian theology. Usually located outside cities, Tophets were holy places where sacrifices to the gods could be presented to the heads of the Phoenician pantheon, Ba'al Hammon, the god of weather and vegetation, and his consort, Tanit.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Regular sacrifices were made to ensure the prosperity of Carthage. After the ceremony, ashes of the burnt offering were placed within a vessel and stones were placed on top of the funerary urns to seal them within the Tophet. Child sacrifice, once prevalent throughout the Near-East, was a persistent hallmark of Carthaginian religious life long after contemporary cultures had shunned the practice. Modern archaeological evidence suggests children were sacrificed in times of great stress such as wars, plagues, and natural disasters as an act of divine supplication.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_ALERT_TOPHET_CULTURE">
			<Text>
				Purchasing a unit has earned you {1_num} [ICON_CULTURE] Culture from your Tophet in {2_Str}.
			</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- University of Coimbra -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VP_UNIVERSITY_OF_COIMBRA">
			<Text>
				University of Coimbra
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VP_UNIVERSITY_OF_COIMBRA_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Opened in 1290, the University of Coimbra is one of the oldest centers of higher learning in the world, and the oldest in Portugal. The university was founded by King Dinis as the Lisbon Estudo Geral, originally with faculties of Arts, Law, Canon Law and Medicine. As the only university in Portugal for 350 years, the University of Coimbra became a focus of educational, political, and social influence in Portugal.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VP_UNIVERSITY_OF_COIMBRA_STRATEGY">
			<Text>
				The Universiy of Coimbra is the unique Portuguese replacement for the Oxford University. It does not require a University, and provides a free University in the city. In addition to the normal bonuses of the Oxford University, it gives all naval units the ability to gain science from exploration, and generates Gold and Production in the city for every Feitoria built in foreign lands.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VP_UNIVERSITY_OF_COIMBRA_HELP">
			<Text>
				Unique Portuguese replacement for the Oxford University. Gain a free University, and a Great Scientist appears near the City. +75 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture every time you research a Technology, scaling with Era. Contains 2 slots for Great Works of Writing. Reduces [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Illiteracy. +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold to Universities. All naval units gain the Age of Discovery promotion. Whenever a Feitoria is built in city-state territory, permanently gain +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production Cost and [ICON_CITIZEN] Population Requirements increase based on the number of cities you own.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+3 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science if Themed.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_AGE_OF_DISCOVERY">
			<Text>
				Age of Discovery
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_AGE_OF_DISCOVERY_HELP">
			<Text>
				Gain [ICON_SCIENCE] Science from exploring.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Waag -->
		<!-- Created by De_Genius on 17/11/2017, incorporated and modified by adan_eslavo 13/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NETHERLANDS_WAAG">
			<Text>Waag</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NETHERLANDS_WAAG_HELP">
			<Text>Unique Dutch replacement for the Bank. Available earlier.[NEWLINE]When you spend [ICON_GOLD] Gold to purchase Units or invest in Buildings in this City, 15% of the cost is converted into [ICON_RESEARCH] Science. +3 [ICON_GOLD] Gold to Caravansary and Customs House in this City, and +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold to Market in this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+2% [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Great Person Generation and +1 [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength in City for every Luxury Resource traded on Empire[NEWLINE]Reduces Poverty slightly.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_GOLD] Gold: +3 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_SILVER] Silver: +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold, +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_GEMS] Gems: +2 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NETHERLANDS_WAAG_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Waag is the Netherlands' unique replacement for the Bank. In addition to the normal bonuses of a Bank, the Waag comes earlier than the Bank, and provides bonuses to Great Person Generation and defense for every luxury imported or exported in the Empire. Be sure to keep peaceful and lucrative relationships with your neighbors; a surprise war with a trading partner could suddenly weaken your city's defenses!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NETHERLANDS_WAAG_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Waag ("weigh house") are the public buildings in which goods were weighed for market. Prior to international standards of weights and measures, the Waags performed an indispensable service in preventing the fraudulent sale of goods. As public control of the weight of goods was very important, Waags were run by local authorities who would also use them for the levying of taxes on goods transported through or sold within the city. This necessitated weigh houses be near a market square or town centre.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Of particular note is the Amsterdam Waag, built in the 15th-century on Nieuwmarkt square in Amsterdam. Originally, the building was one of the gates in the city wall along the moat formed by the current Singel canal. A number of guilds were housed on the top floors of the building: the blacksmiths' guild, the painter's guild, the masons' guild and the surgeons' guild, each with its own entrance gate. In 1632 Rembrandt van Rijn was commissioned to paint the surgeons at work, and the resulting The Anatomy Lesson of Dr. Nicolaes Tulp made his reputation. In 1691 a theatrum anatomicum was added, which became famous for admitting members of the public to witness human dissections.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- White Tower -->
		<!-- Created by FieryCharizard7 on 20/11/2017, incorporated and modified by adan_eslavo on 6/01/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ENGLAND_WHITE_TOWER">
			<Text>White Tower</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ENGLAND_WHITE_TOWER_HELP">
			<Text>Unique replacement for the Hermitage. Only England may build it
			[NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture for every 4 [ICON_CITIZEN] Population in city.
			[NEWLINE]+2 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture for all Castles on Empire, and -25% Spy stealing rate on Empire 
			[NEWLINE]+3 [ICON_GOLD] Gold to Constabulary and +3 [ICON_FOOD] Food to Arsenal in City.
			[NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_HAPPINESS] Happiness on Empire for every enemy spy killed on Empire.
			[NEWLINE]Contains 3 slots for Great Works of Art/Artifact, and comes with a free Great Work of Art. 
			[NEWLINE]+5 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and +5 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture when themed.
			[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Available earlier, requires Castle in City.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ENGLAND_WHITE_TOWER_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique English replacement for the Hermitage. This National Wonder produces +1 Culture for every 4 Citizens in the City, and 2 culture for every castle in the empire. The White Tower reduces the stealing rate of enemy spies on empire, and gives Happiness for every enemy spy killed. Your citizens will love you if you can keep a tight lid on English secrets, so station spies in your cities to take advantage of this wonder.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ENGLAND_WHITE_TOWER_TEXT">
			<Text>The White Tower is a central tower, the old keep, at the Tower of London. It was built by William the Conqueror during the early 1080s, and subsequently extended. The White Tower was the castle's strongest point militarily, and provided accommodation for the king and his representatives, as well as a chapel. The Tower of London covers an area of 18 acres and its magnificent architecture covers almost all the styles which have flourished in England. Throughout its long history, the Tower has been many things to England: A tyrant's castle, and treasury; a menagerie, and a mint; a palace, and a prison. Today, the Tower of London is a vast museum which boasts, among its many treasure, the Crown Jewels of England.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_THEMING_BONUS_WHITE_TOWER_NATIONAL">
			<Text>Treasury of {2_CivAdjective} Treasures</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_THEMING_BONUS_WHITE_TOWER_GLOBAL">
			<Text>Treasury of Global Treasures</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_THEMING_BONUS_WHITE_TOWER_HELP">
			<Text>To maximize your bonus, make sure all slots are filled with artifacts and either from the city owner or from different owners.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_WORK_THE_CROWN_JEWELS_QUOTE">
			<Text>
				"On the contrary. Every Bison dollar will be worth five British pounds. For that is the exchange rate that the bank of England will implement after I kidnap their queen."
				[NEWLINE]-M. Bison
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_WORK_THE_CROWN_JEWELS">
			<Text>The Crown Jewels</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Xiafan Guanjun -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CHINESE_XIAFAN_GUANJUN">
			<Text>Xiafan Guanjun</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CHINESE_XIAFAN_GUANJUN_HELP">
			<Text>Sturdy Renaissance era ranged naval unit. Only China may build it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CHINESE_XIAFAN_GUANJUN_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Xiafan Guanjun is a Chinese unique unit. It is much sturdier than the Frigate it replaces, is available earlier, and has the Supply promotion. When stationed in a city-state territory, gain 2 Influence with that city-state per turn.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CHINESE_XIAFAN_GUANJUN_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The Xiafan Guanjun (lit. "The Foreign Expeditionary Armada") was the great treasure fleet of the Ming Dynasty. Seven voyages were made from 1405 to 1433 AD, all headed by the legendary admiral Zheng He at the behest of Yongle Emperor. The Treasure Fleet ranged as far as the Arabian Peninsula in their task of projecting Chinese influence across the South China Sea and beyond, bringing many smaller nations under the suzerainty of China.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				
				The ships of the Xiafan Guanjun were some of the largest wooden ships ever constructed, some measuring an estimated 137 meters (416 feet). It would be another century before European ships could match the size and power of the Chinese, making China the undisputed naval superpower of the 15th century. Despite this raw power, the voyages were primarily concerned with diplomacy, bringing envoys and even kings before the emperor to present tribute and perform the 'kowtow', an act of reverence indicating their recognition and subservience to China.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				
				"As an engine for carrying man and his commerce upon the high and stormy seas as well as on the vast inland waterways, it is doubtful if any class of vessel… is more suited or better adapted to its purpose than the Chinese or Indian junk, and it is certain that for flatness of sail and handiness, the Chinese rig is unsurpassed."[NEWLINE]-H. Warington Smyth
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_KOWTOW">
			<Text>Kowtow</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_KOWTOW_HELP">
			<Text>Can enter rival territory. +2 Influence per turn when stationed within a city-state's borders.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost-->
		
		<!-- Yassa Court -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 29/10/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MONGOLIA_YASSA_COURT">
			<Text>Yassa Court</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MONGOLIA_YASSA_COURT_HELP">
			<Text>Unique Classical Era Building which can be built in non-occupied cities. Eliminates [ICON_OCCUPIED] Extra Unhappiness from an Occupied City. +20% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production towards Ranged, Siege, Mounted and Armor Military Units. Conquering enemy city starts 10-turn long [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] WLTKD. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Slightly reduces [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Crime, Boredom, Illiteracy and Religious Tension. Building cost is slightly increased with number of Cities.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Only Mongols can build it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MONGOLIA_YASSA_COURT_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique Mongolian replacement for the Courthouse. Can be built in non-occupied Cities. In addition elimination Unhappiness in Occupied Cities, this building reduces unhappiness from Crime, Illiteracy, Boredom and Religious Tensions, and increases production of all Land-based military units, except Unmounted Melee. Conquering Cities triggers a small WLTKD. It is also slightly cheaper than the Courthouse.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MONGOLIA_YASSA_COURT_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Yassa was a secret written code of law created by Genghis Khan. The word Yassa translates into "order" or "decree". It was the de facto law of the Mongol Empire even though the "law" was never actually made public. The Yassa seems to have originated from decrees issued in war time, and was later codified and expanded to include cultural and life-style conventions. By keeping the Yassa secret, the decrees could be modified and used selectively. It is believed that the Yassa was supervised by Genghis Khan himself with the help of the high judge of the Mongol Empire: His stepbrother, Shihihutag. Genghis Khan appointed his second son Chagatai (later Chagatai Khan) to oversee the execution of the laws.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Yellow Brow -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 3/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SHOSHONE_BIG_HORSE_DANCE">
			<Text>Big Horse Dance</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SHOSHONE_BIG_HORSE_DANCE_HELP">
			<Text>Adds [ICON_STRENGTH] Defense Bonus [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Fortifying[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SHOSHONE_BIG_HORSE_DANCE_PERFORMED">
			<Text>Big Horse Dance Performed</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SHOSHONE_BIG_HORSE_DANCE_PERFORMED_HELP">
			<Text>Unit [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]is Fortified[ENDCOLOR]. [ICON_STRENGTH] Defense Bonus added.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SHOSHONE_YELLOW_BROW">
			<Text>Yellow Brow</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SHOSHONE_YELLOW_BROW_HELP">
			<Text>Unique Renaissance Era Unit. Only the Shoshone may build it. This Unit is slightly stronger than the Tercio it replaces. Has the Anti-Cavalry promotion, fights at full strength when damaged, and has double the normal strength from fortifying.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SHOSHONE_YELLOW_BROW_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Yellow Brow is unmatched for its ability to hold ground. Never one to retreat, the Yellow brow fights at full strength regardless of health, and has double the normal bonus from fortifying. This unit is very effective against enemy cavalry</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SHOSHONE_YELLOW_BROW_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Yellow Brows (Ohamupe) were one of two military societies within the Shoshone, playing an integral role in hunting, scouting, and policing within their Shoshone bands. Yellow Brow braves would keep their heads shaved into a cockscomb 'mohawk', and paint their exposed heads yellow, hence their common English name. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				The Yellow Brows were composed of only the bravest and most daring of the young men, tasked with keeping order on hunting expeditions, scouting, and soldiering. The Society was never more than a few hundred young men, and membership was through appointment by graduating members, who would elect their replacement. A young Yellow Brow was expected to act and speak in a contrarian way as a sign of membership.  For instance, when asked if he would like to join the Yellow Brows, it was expected that the young man would say 'No' as a sign of willingness to join, or 'Yes' if he wished to decline. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				In battle, they were led by a warchief who carried a long cane tipped with a stone or metal dagger.  The cane was used to grab and unhorse opponents, or as a No-Retreat signal. If the enemy was gaining the upper hand, the chief would drive his staff into the ground and the braves would defend him to the last. Yellow Brows were banned from leaving their chief's side until another member of the tribe came and pulled out the staff, releasing the braves from their charge. Fleeing battle after the staff had been planted resulted in dire consequences for any returning Yellow Brow. Such dishonorable conduct was met with abject mockery and banishment from the tribe.
			</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>
	<IconTextureAtlases>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>EAGLE_FLAG</Atlas>
			<IconSize>32</IconSize>
			<Filename>eagleicon.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
	</IconTextureAtlases>
</GameData>
