
<GameData>
	<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TOPHET">
			<Text>Tophet</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TOPHET_HELP">
			<Text>Provides [ICON_PEACE] Faith and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture in the City. [NEWLINE]Receive 10 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture in the City whenever a Unit is purchased, scaling with era, and Units purchased in this city receive full XP from buildings.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TOPHET_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Tophet is the unique Shrine replacement for Carthage. In addition to the normal bonuses of a Shrine, the Tophet provides Culture whenever a unit is purchased in the City. Military Units purchased in a City with a Tophet are not affected by the normal half XP penalty for purchasing.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TOPHET_TEXT">
			<Text>"Tophet" is a Hebrew term for a place of worship and human sacrifice to the Canaanite gods, and has become a colorful synonym for hell within Judeo-Christian theology. Usually located outside cities, Tophets were holy places where sacrifices to the gods could be presented to the heads of the Phoenician pantheon, Ba'al Hammon, the god of weather and vegetation, and his consort, Tanit.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
			 Regular sacrifices were made to ensure the prosperity of Carthage. After the ceremony, ashes of the burnt offering were placed within a vessel and stones were placed on top of the funerary urns to seal them within the Tophet. Child sacrifice, once prevalent throughout the Near-East, was a persistent hallmark of Carthaginian religious life long after contemporary cultures had shunned the practice. Modern archaeological evidence suggests children were sacrificed in times of great stress such as wars, plagues, and natural disasters as an act of divine supplication.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_ALERT_TOPHET_CULTURE">
			<Text>
				Purchasing a unit has earned you {1_num} [ICON_CULTURE] Culture from your Tophet in {2_Str}.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_JFD_SHOPHET">
			<Text>Shophet</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_JFD_SHOPHET_HELP">
			<Text>Unique replacement for the Great General. Disembarks onto water tiles as a Great Admiral. Causes friendly units beginning in the same or adjacent tile to ignore enemy Zone of Control for that turn.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_JFD_SHOPHET_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Shophet is the unique Great General replacement for Carthage, for Hannibal. This unit causes all friendly units beginning in the same or an adjacent tile to ignore an enemy's Zone of Control for that turn. In addition, whenever this unit embarks into a water tile, it becomes a Great Admiral. It returns to Great General status upon disembarking into a city. Use a Shophet to supplement your military strategies when waging war against other civilizations.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_JFD_SHOPHET_TEXT">
			<Text>In the various independent city states constituting Phoenicia proper (coasts of present Lebanon and Syria) and its "Punic" Mediterranean colonies a shofet (in Punic, suffet or suffete) was a non-royal magistrate granted control over a city-state, sometimes functioning much in the same way as a Roman consul.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The term is mostly widely known from the suffetes of Carthage, a former Phoenician colony. Following the overthrow of its monarchy in the 5th century BC, Carthage was ruled by a number of aristocratic councils presided over by two suffetes, who served in similar capacity to Roman consuls.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_JFD_SHOPHET_GENERAL">
			<Text>Admiralty</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_JFD_SHOPHET_GENERAL_HELP">
			<Text>This unit may embark as a Great Admiral.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_JFD_SHOPHET_ADMIRAL">
			<Text>Commandeering</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_JFD_SHOPHET_ADMIRAL_HELP">
			<Text>This unit may disembark as a Great General (must be moved into a city first).</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_JFD_SHOPHET_ZOC">
			<Text>Nearby Shophet</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_JFD_SHOPHET_ZOC_HELP">
			<Text>Ignores enemy Zone of Control.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Unique Names-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_1">
			<Text>Bomilcar</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_2">
			<Text>Hamilcar Barca</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_3">
			<Text>Hannibal</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_4">
			<Text>Hannibal Barca</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_5">
			<Text>Hasdrubal II</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_6">
			<Text>Hasdrubal Gisco</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_7">
			<Text>Hasdrubal the Boetharch</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_8">
			<Text>Mago I Justin</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_9">
			<Text>Mago II</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_10">
			<Text>Mago III</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_11">
			<Text>Himilco I</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_12">
			<Text>Himilco II</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_13">
			<Text>Hasdrubal the Fair</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_14">
			<Text>Ad Herbal</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_15">
			<Text>Carthalo</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_16">
			<Text>Hannibal Monomachus</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_17">
			<Text>Maharbal</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_18">
			<Text>Sophonisba</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_19">
			<Text>Hannibal the Rhodian</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_20">
			<Text>Hanno the Elder</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_21">
			<Text>Hanno the Great</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_22">
			<Text>Aderbaal</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_23">
			<Text>Bodashtart</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_24">
			<Text>Philosir</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_PERSON_JFD_SHOPHET_25">
			<Text>Abdmelqart</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>
</GameData>