<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<GameData>
	<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_AUSTRIAN_LANDWEHR">
			<Text>
				Landwehr
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_AUSTRIAN_LANDWEHR_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The Austrian Landwehr was one of three components that made up the ground forces of the Austro-Hungarian Dual Monarchy between 1868 and 1918, and it was composed of recruits from the Cisleithanian parts of the empire. Intended as a national defence force alongside the Hungarian Landwehr, the Austrian Landwehr was officially established by order of Emperor Franz Josef on 5 December 1868. Yet, while the Hungarian force was generously supported early on by the parliament in Budapest, legislators in Vienna generally failed to advance the cause of the Landwehr, leaving it by the 1870s as a skeletal force with only the appearance of parity. [NEWLINE[NEWLINE]The 1880s saw an expansion in the force's numbers, as the high command was unable to obtain increases in manpower for the joint Imperial and Royal army and sought to increase overall numbers through the Landwehr. Additionally, Austrian fears of the development of the Hungarian Landwehr caused the Austrian Reichsrat to vote to increase the Landwehr's strength to 135,000. These nationalist interests led to a gradual strengthening and improvement of the force, so that by the start of the First World War, Landwehr units were considered equal to the units of the joint army in readiness and equipment.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_AUSTRIAN_LANDWEHR_STRATEGY">
			<Text>
				The Landwehr is the backbone of the Industrial-era Austrian army. It excels in defending in owned territory and the territory of allied city-states.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_AUSTRIAN_LANDWEHR_HELP">
			<Text>
				The Landwehr is the Austrian replacement for the Fusilier. It gets a combat bonus when fighting in territory owned by Austria and allied city-states.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_IMPERIAL_VIGILANCE">
			<Text>
				Imperial Vigilance
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_IMPERIAL_VIGILANCE_HELP">
			<Text>
				+25% combat bonus in owned territory and territory of allied city-states.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_LANDWEHR_CS_BONUS">
			<Text>
				City-State Defense
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_LANDWEHR_CS_BONUS_HELP">
			<Text>
				+25% combat in the territory of allied city-states.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_YORKSCHER_MARCHE">
			<Text>
				Yorkscher Marche
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_YORKSCHER_MARCHE_HELP">
			<Text>
				+2 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture per turn while in owned territory.
			</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>
</GameData>