<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 9/17/2015 8:17:06 PM -->
<GameData>	
	<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_INDABA">
			<Text>Indaba</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_INDABA_HELP">
			<Text>When expended, grants 60XP to a stacked unit and 15XP to every adjacent unit.</Text>
		</Row>		
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU3_GENERAL">
			<Text>InDuna</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU3_GENERAL_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The InDuna is a Zulu unique unit. May construct a Citadel. +15% Combat bonus to all Land units within 2 tiles. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Expending an InDuna gives 60XP to the unit that was stacked with it, and 15X for adjacent units.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU3_GENERAL_HELP">
			<Text>
				Unique Zulu Great General that grants a Combat Bonus to all nearby troops and experience when expended.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU3_GENERAL_TEXT">
			<Text>Leadership was not a complicated affair for the Zulu military. An inDuna guided each regiment, and he in turn answered to senior izinDuna who controlled the corps grouping. Overall guidance of the host was furnished by elder izinDuna usually with many years of experience. One or more of these elder chiefs might accompany a big force on an important mission, but there was no single "field marshal" in supreme command of all Zulu forces. Regimental izinDuna, like the non-commissioned officers of today's army, and yesterday's Roman Centurions, were extremely important to morale and discipline. This was shown during the battle of Isandhlwana. Blanketed by a hail of British bullets, rockets and artillery, the advance of the Zulu faltered. Echoing from the mountain, however, were the shouted cadences and fiery exhortations of their regimental izinDuna, who reminded the warriors that their king did not send them to run away. Thus encouraged, the encircling regiments remained in place, maintaining continual pressure, until weakened British dispositions enabled the host to make a final surge forward.</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>

	<IconTextureAtlases>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>ZULU3_GENERAL_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>256</IconSize>
			<Filename>3ZuluGeneral256.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>ZULU3_GENERAL_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>128</IconSize>
			<Filename>3ZuluGeneral128.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>ZULU3_GENERAL_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>80</IconSize>
			<Filename>3ZuluGeneral80.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>ZULU3_GENERAL_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>64</IconSize>
			<Filename>3ZuluGeneral64.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>ZULU3_GENERAL_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>45</IconSize>
			<Filename>3ZuluGeneral45.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>

		<Row>
			<Atlas>UNIT_ALPHA_3IZU_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>32</IconSize>
			<Filename>3IzuUnitAlphaAtlas.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
	</IconTextureAtlases>
</GameData>