<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by Tomatekh -->
<GameData>
	<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_HORSE_FATHER">
			<Text>Father of the Horse</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_HORSE_FATHER_HELP">
			<Text>+15% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength for all Mounted Units within 2 tiles.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_3UC_SOFA">
			<Text>Sofa</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_3UC_SOFA_HELP">
			<Text>Skirmisher Unit excelling at supporting your Cavalry. Only Songhai may build it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_3UC_SOFA_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Sofa is a Songhai unique unit, replacing the Crossbowman. It serves as an excellent support unit starting with the Medic I promotion and a 15% Damage increase to all Mounted units within 2 tiles. The Sofa has a slightly lower defensive strength, but is relatively cheap to train.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_3UC_SOFA_TEXT">
			<Text>Sofa is a Mandinka term for slave soldiers who served in the army of the various Empires of West Africa. Originally, the Sofas were horse  grooms of the soldier nobility, the Farari, but their role slowly changed to become skirmishers and soldiers in their own right. Sofas were recruited from "jonow" (slaves) captured in battle or bought from afar. The institution of slavery in the Mali and Songhai Empires heavily rewarded loyalty, and jonow could rise to civil or military positions of prominence. Jonow became part of their master's clan, and were often freed after a certain amount of years. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Sofas were equipped with two quivers, and their bow was small by European standards, so sofas employed deadly poisons and fired in arcs to give their arrows strength.</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>

	<IconTextureAtlases>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>UNIT_ALPHA_SOFA_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>32</IconSize>
			<Filename>MaliUnitAlphaAtlas.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>

		<Row>
			<Atlas>SOFA_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>256</IconSize>
			<Filename>SofaIcon256.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>SOFA_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>128</IconSize>
			<Filename>SofaIcon128.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>SOFA_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>80</IconSize>
			<Filename>SofaIcon080.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>SOFA_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>64</IconSize>
			<Filename>SofaIcon064.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>SOFA_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>45</IconSize>
			<Filename>SofaIcon045.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
	</IconTextureAtlases>
</GameData>